"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get it all right, don't wonder why
Even though trouble's on the way
Live for yourself
You can do what you want
Don't give up on your dreams
Better make a start
Open up your eyes
You will find your own way
Don't want to miss the sign
Life is like a trick or treat
Doesn't matter what people may say
What they say
No more live in chains
Hold your thoughts and you'll be fine
Get it all right, don't wonder why
Even though trouble's on the way
Takes ya all night, make it all right
So come on now, the world is waiting
Get it all right, don't wonder why
Even though trouble's on the way
Now or never, make it better
So come on now, the world is waiting
"By the end of summer vacation,
Akina's Eight-Six, which had won so many
races, was famous throughout the area."
"Kyoichi Sudo's Lan-Evo Squad,
the Emperors, defeated the Night Kids,
Myogi's best, in a fierce dogfight,
and declared their plan to conquer Gunma..."
Mako, that cornering wasn't tight enough!
You would normally choose a tighter line.
You were off by five inches.
Uh, yeah...
Someone is coming down the pass.
--That's Mako's Sileighty!
--So cool.
That's Usui's fastest Sileighty, "Impact Blue"!
Not good!
This isn't like you! Try to concentrate.
What's the matter?
"Beyond Impact Blue..."
So, that's what happened.
You got dumped by that Iketani guy, then.
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
No wonder you were driving so weird!
You're the type whose
driving reflects your feelings.
You race with your emotions.
What's wrong with you?!
Listen, Iketani!
Being in love means that you
accept everything about the person.
Just hurry up and go meet her now!
I'll lecture you later!
I'll be waiting for you
under that billboard where we first met.
The boss is right.
Mako was always honest with me... but I...
I'm certifiable!
My feet hurt.
I hate high heels.
Please, God, I just need one more chance!
Traffic?!
I'll never wear high heels again.
I just can't see how anyone
could break up with you.
He looked like he was
head over heels for you.
Maybe there was a misunderstanding.
I thought so, too, so I kept on
waiting for him after that...
But he never called you?
Right.
Why don't you call him?
I can't be that pushy.
I waited there for three extra hours.
The fact that he hasn't called
means that he's not interested in me.
I guess you really liked him, huh?
Enough to affect your
driving abilities, anyway.
Yeah. I would've given it to him.
Given what?
My virginity.
I just can't tell if you're naive or bold, really!
Anyway, what was so special about him?
It's hard to explain.
He was sincere and gentle.
When we talked about cars,
we got really into it, and time just flew by.
Hello?
Shingo! Long time no talk. How are you?
I'm good.
The reason I called you is...
What? Really?
The Lan-Evo Squad was in Myogi?
Did you hear the news, brother?
Lan-Evos with Tochigi plates
showed up in Myogi, too.
I see.
I hear the Night Kids lost badly.
That idiot Nakazato had
to lose to those outsiders.
I know who they are.
Kyoichi Sudo is their leader.
He's a racer from the Nikko Irohazaka course.
What?
Kyoichi...
What are you plotting now?
--It's been a while, Shingo.
--Yeah.
Anyway, you Night Kids are pretty pathetic.
That's a nice way to greet us.
This is Sayuki. We grew up together.
Hi.
She's cute!
He's the one who raced them.
This is Nakazato.
Nice to meet you.
How could you lose to
them on your home turf?
I'll protect Gunma.
I'll bury your evil plan deep in Myogi's ravine!
What?!
This can't be happening!
But it's not over yet!
If I don't stop them...
...who will?!
They're a Lan-Evo team called the Emperors.
It was right after Takeshi lost to
the Red Suns in an uphill race,
and he hadn't gotten over it yet.
--You were out of sync.
--I guess.
He's inconsistent and doesn't
do well under pressure.
Why don't you stop talking now?
But nobody else can drive an R32 like he can.
I'd say he's the best R32 racer around here.
But even he couldn't keep up,
which means that Lan-Evo is fast.
They said they would wipe out
all of Gunma in one month.
They'll be here, too.
Be careful, Sayuki.
Myogi and Usui are very close together.
Oh, yeah? That's more like it.
People don't call us "Impact Blue,
Usui's fastest" for nothing.
She's aggressive.
I'm just trying to help you.
You're better off avoiding them.
What do you mean by that, Shingo?
Are you saying we have no chance at all?
I didn't say that!
Bouncy!
Don't underestimate us girls!
We don't back down from anyone!
Amazing...
Is that all?
I'm leaving, then.
She's just so stubborn.
Don't come crying to me!
Hey, Takeshi, I brought you here
because I wanted her to know
how dangerous the Emperors are.
You could've helped.
Are you listening to me, Takeshi?
Bouncy... Amazing.
Anyway, I hear a Lan-Evo
team called the Emperors
is attacking Gunma.
I've heard that, too.
--Everyone's talking about them.
--Yeah.
I heard they cut the Night Kids' sticker in half
and put it upside down
on one of their spoilers.
Who would do such a thing?
Are they really coming here, too?
What will you do if they come, Sayuki?
That's a stupid question.
Isn't that right, Mako?
Right. We'll take anyone's challenge
because we're Usui's fastest, "Impact Blue."
That's how we feel, so help us out, okay?
The moment you see their Lan-Evos,
call me on my cell phone.
Yeah.
It's been two days, but the Lan-Evo
Squad hasn't shown up yet.
Maybe they're not coming to Usui.
Part of me will feel relieved if they don't.
I haven't been at the top of my game lately.
If I had to face them right now,
I'm not sure I could run my best race.
But I do want to clear this haze from my mind.
I want to forget about Iketani.
Come on!!
Sayuki?!
What are you doing in my bathroom?!
This isn't the time for a relaxing bath, Mako!
What's going on?
I came to pick you up! We're going.
Going where?
To Usui Pass!
Those Lan-Evos are here!
Just hurry up and put on your underwear.
Just give me a second!
This is embarrassing!
Here come the Lan-Evos!
It's the Emperors, all right. They really came.
--Did you call Sayuki and Mako?
--Yeah.
What? The Lan-Evos are there?
Yeah, the Emperor guys you told me about.
We're on our way there.
Got it.
Takeshi!
The Lan-Evo Squad showed up in Usui.
They did?
Let's go, Takeshi.
Yeah.
I see nothing but FR drift punks here, too.
I must say that Gunma's level is pretty low.
Let's go back and tell Kyoichi about this.
Yeah.
Hey, guys...
If you're here to race,
we'll take your challenge,
'cause our Sileighty is the fastest car around.
Hey, Shingo...
Is anything going on between
you and that Sileighty girl?
You mean Sayuki?
We're just childhood friends, that's all.
We lived close to each other
and went to the same school.
--I see.
--Yeah.
Wait a minute, Takeshi.
You like girls like that?
Well...
You don't want her.
She's a strong-minded rebel.
She's not the kind of girl
who listens to anyone's advice,
but even if they are the fastest in Usui,
they have no chance against those Lan-Evos.
I admit that their drifting
technique is amazing.
Maybe no one in Usui could touch them,
but they have almost no
experience with pure speed racing--
the kind that requires remarkable control.
I must say their control isn't crisp enough.
They'll be outclassed by a serious 4WD car.
I know you know what
I'm talking about, Takeshi.
I don't mean to say that they're
slow just because they're girls,
but they have no chance.
A Sileighty, huh?
With girl drivers.
Let's play a little, 'cause this looks fun.
Hey, I don't know if that's a good idea.
We're just scouting.
You may get yelled at by Kyoichi later.
Don't be such a tight-ass!
We came all the way here.
I see no harm in having a little fun.
As long as I win.
But what if you lose to them?
Don't insult me with your "what ifs," Ren.
How could my Evo IV
lose to these bimbo drivers?
Hear that, Mako? That does it.
He shouldn't have said that.
People who insult girl racers are the worst.
Fine, I won't go easy on you.
Her eyes are getting serious.
She's fast when she looks like that,
'cause her emotion is the fuel.
This is a downhill race.
Since Usui Pass is narrow,
it'll be a "cat and mouse" race.
If the mouse gets away, it's over.
If not, we keep switching
positions until someone wins.
Are you okay with that?
That's fine.
Then go ahead and choose
which position you want first.
I'll follow you first...
...so I can check out your behind.
Let's start, then.
After exiting the first corner,
we'll go full speed.
That's the start of the race. Got it?
Yeah, okay.
Hey, are you gonna be okay?
Don't make me repeat myself.
I'm one of the top racers in the Emperors.
I'm 200% sure that my Evo IV
won't lose to a Sileighty driven by two girls.
Let's go!
I refuse to lose to a guy
who insults girl racers.
Mako, you look fired up.
Are you ready, Sayuki?
Okay.
An easy win.
His Evo IV can't possibly lose to a Sileighty.
They're really doing it.
When it counts, women have more courage.
Can they defeat the Emperors,
who defeated the Night Kids?
That Evo IV is a high-powered 4WD car.
Anyone else would've run away.
But if Sayuki and Mako can't beat that guy,
no one else can.
Right. I don't know who
named them "Impact Blue,"
but they're Usui's fastest.
All we can do is believe in them,
because Sayuki's blue Sileighty
is the best here.
They're not bad.
This is their course, so they
know how to attack it.
No cars ahead. Drift right through here!
My Evo I V's drift is far better
than an FR's pitiful drift.
It's a high-speed 4WD drift
with the engine full blast!
Mako, you're doing great.
Grip the next corner and hug the inner wall!
We're about even so far.
I'm not sure if it's the Evo IV itself
or the driver's technique that's
letting him keep up with us.
Like you said,
swinging drift involves many variables.
It all depends on how you use the tires.
Yeah.
When was the last time
you saw this Sileighty race?
Sometime last spring.
Then she may have changed.
I've experienced it, too.
After a painful loss,
a talented racer can change big-time.
Yeah.
There are talented FR racers
like Akina's Eight-Six in this world.
There is an FR racer who can beat a 4WD car.
But that Eight-Six is an exception.
I guess it would've been a different story
if those girls had ever had a
chance to see that Eight-Six race.
Hmph, insolent chick drivers!
I won't lose, no matter what!
Amazing! Her driving is totally different.
Her steering has definitely gotten tighter.
Her driving probably got this way
after the race against Akina's Eight-Six.
Mako has woken up!
You're amazing, Mako! We can win this race!
That Evo I Visn't as sharp at the corners.
He's not as great as I thought he was.
He's probably not the one who
defeated the Night Kids in Myogi.
In that case, I hate to keep
showing him our behinds.
We'll finish him at the next corner, C-121!
I know you know this,
but you're much faster on
the straightaways tonight.
You'll be entering the
corner at a higher speed,
so don't forget to adjust for that!
Good, no cars ahead. Go!
If those girls can clear this corner,
my Evo IV certainly can!
I'm going wide!
I can't stay on the same line!
It's over, Mako.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, don't tell Kyoichi
anything about this, okay?
Sure.
Sayuki, where's the Lan-Evo Squad?
You're late, Shingo.
We're already done.
What? It's over?
I see. Don't be discouraged.
We lost on our home turf, too.
What are you talking about?!
We won.
I said we won.
They won?!
Mako was amazing.
She's a genius.
Don't tease.
Let's go home.
See ya, Shingo.
Hey, we came out here to root for you.
That Sileighty is giving off a blinding aura.
They're the real thing!
You're amazing, Mako.
Maybe last night's Lan-Evo wasn't that good.
That's not true.
He was pretty good.
It would've been a tough race
had we raced him before
we raced Akina's Eight-Six.
Less-angled cornering has
been our focus since our loss,
and you executed it perfectly.
But at C-121, when we went for the kill,
you went back to your flashy, dramatic drift.
I guess I entered that corner way too fast.
I get scared thinking about it now.
It wasn't funny last night.
I thought I was gonna die.
You sure are an emotional racer.
You suddenly change into someone else.
I feel kind of relieved now.
But I still have a long way to go.
I feel like I'm chasing after something
that's beyond that blue sky.
I don't need a man for a while.
Just watch me, Iketani!
Bang!
Have you caught a cold, Iketani?
No, I don't think so.
"Early Autumn: Crispy Autumn"