"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Blastin' off to the wicked show,
splitting the air with that sputterin' noise
Let's go, ride that thing
to the throwdown party
Determination that never
backs down, the dogfight
I wanna feel the thrill of the
screams in the phat red zone
A brief flash, like a comet
The brightness lasts a second, but I don't care
Someday, I wanna tell of that
glimpse of precious scenery
Yes, right now it's a purely instinctual dogfight
If it's a thrilling dream
you're after, it's right here
A wind that shatters the heat haze, backfire
C'mon, throw away yesterday,
right now it's a rocket dance (Dogfight!)
If the wish you can't scream aloud hurts,
then hurry and come here
You're big time gambler
Foolishness is a beautiful contour
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Tha loud sound is everywhere
Sideswipe, a 5G heavyweight
Runnin' right to the line, a hair's breadth
between offense and defense
Ba-ba-baaam!
Yo, I can step on the gas for
an easy victory, I still got it
"Strawberry Picking
And all you can eat"
"Touge Tea House""Restaurant"
I pulled it off somehow.
It was a pretty tight race.
The car's settings were all wrong.
I noticed it soon after the race started,
but there was nothing that could be done.
The only thing to do was hold back on the
accelerator handling to try to save my tires.
Still, that was impressive how you noticed
the opponent's weak point
at the last moment.
I guess.
"Sadamine Touge
Barbecue Garden"
"Touge Tea House"
It was the smallest thing.
Something caused her to wobble.
She recovered well, but after that
her acceleration speed was sluggish,
and it looked like I could ram her
from behind. That's when it hit me.
Maybe the car had a peaky engine
with a substantial turbo lag.
It's powerful at straight vertical racing,
but weak when it comes to horizontal racing.
If I'd noticed that sooner, I might
not have had such a hard time.
Do not forget today's
accelerator handling, Keisuke.
When we return to Akagi, practice it
repeatedly till it is part of your repertoire.
While not flashy, it is a
technique of great importance.
It will dramatically increase your range
of tactics to improve tire performance.
Yeah. So this is just as you'd planned, eh?
I'm sorry.
There's nothing for you to apologize for.
You ran the best race you could, right?
Their driver was simply a notch above you.
I thought he would become more
panicky, placing wear on his tires,
but he has a genius-like ability to
adapt to the conditions of a race.
He may be our opponent,
but all I can say is, "Well done."
Well, next up is the downhill.
I intend to do my best as well.
"Act 9: Kyoko's Confession"
I'm taking the lead?
That's right. It's a bit unexpected, but
their guy chose to come from behind.
How's the check coming?
The check's complete. You can go anytime.
All right, stand by.
Please line up the cars
at the starting line.
Don't do anything reckless, Nobuhiko.
I know.
I already know I can't keep up with him...
But if I can watch the Eight-Sixrace for
even that much longer, then I have to.
As a racer, and not only for my own hobby...
...but for the second challenge
match with the Saitama area.
--Fujiwara.
--Yes?
Once the race starts, hold back for a
while and keep pace with the rear car.
Even if a little distance opens between you,
pull him along without shaking him off.
Once you clear the first hairpin,
you can do as you like.
You can even increase your speed
all at once, ending the race sooner.
Do you understand?
Not until after the first hairpin.
Okay.
Good. Fumihiro!
Yeah.
All right, beginning the countdown!
In five seconds!
Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
So you came, Wataru.
With the two ace drivers of
Project D coming to Saitama,
there's no way I could stay away.
It's started, huh? The downhill.
I wish I could watch it...
Now that your race is finished, it's like I'm
relieved enough that I've gotten hungry!
There's still lots of food in Van #1 left
over from our convenience store run.
Oh, really? Well, I'm going
to go eat something.
What about you, Keisuke?
I'm fine.
All right then.
Um...
Really, thank you so much for everything.
What the heck? I didn't do anything
for you to go thanking me like that.
You did. You fixed my FD for me.
Oh, that? Forget it. We settled that
before we'd even started racing, right?
But...
I've got something to be
grateful to you for, too.
I made a few new discoveries
during today's race.
You're a really great driver, and fast.
I'm not just saying that. I don't do flattery.
I said some harsh things at first, but I
take them back. That was wrong of me.
Y-You don't have to...
All right then, let's consider the matter closed.
Um, I...
I enjoyed it. Today's race.
I've never enjoyed anything so much.
He's incredible. Or rather, he's dangerous!
His corner entry is insane!
Um...
Um... Um, here's the thing.
Are you dating anyone right now, Takahashi?
No, not really. There's no one like that.
As it is, I'm too busy to get involved
with some chick, and racing cars is--
Thank you very much!
H-Hey!
What was that about? Weirdo.
A little hard for me to come out...
He's so smooth, it's like he's gliding...
It's as if I could get sucked right in.
But why am I able to keep
up with him, even barely?
Because there's less of a slope here
compared to just after the start?
I can't believe that would be the only reason.
He should have more skill than just this.
My heart is pounding. I'm as excited as when
I'd just bought my car and run my first race.
All five senses are completely engaged,
imprinting themselves upon me.
All right, show me! Show me the true nature
of your superhuman speed and technique!
Once the race starts, hold back for a
while and keep pace with the rear car.
Even if a little distance opens between you,
pull him along without shaking him off.
Once you clear the first hairpin,
you can do as you like.
Do you understand? Not until
after the first hairpin.
How was it, Nobuhiko?
What are your thoughts after having gone
up against the Gunma area's downhiller?
"How was it?" He ended the
race after the first hairpin.
When I went up against that Eight-Six,
it was a close race that
could have gone either way.
After all, we took it as far as the fifth race.
Because this course has a mix
of uphill stages, don't you think?
If it were a purely downhill course,
I wonder whether the race
would have lasted that long.
Jeez! Way to hit a person where it hurts.
The Eight-Six's downhill certainly
was enough to give me goose bumps.
But...
...there was one thing that bothered me.
I felt like the driver of that Eight-Six
kept pace with me on purpose.
Why would he do that?
I don't know. Maybe I'm just
reading too much into it.
In any case...
Thanks to what he showed me,
I've come up with my own solution.
A way to beat that Eight-Six.
To beat the Eight-Six?!
That's right. The one and only way.
A time trial race?
It's incredible, huh? His acceleration.
I wonder what kind of course record he'll set.
But today's race was just the opening
move toward the second round
of the Saitama battle.
We couldn't ask for worthier opponents.
And we'll stop them... Project D!
Thank you very much!
Welcome!
Hey!
Oh jeez, you again?
What kind of a greeting is "Oh jeez"?
Especially after I brought
a printout of D's homepage.
Whoa, really?!
Show us that please, Kenji!
As always, they are victorious.
They won the downhill and the hillclimb,
and even set a course record.
Incredible, isn't it?
They've run a string of courses for the
very first time, and haven't lost once!
That world of theirs is a little
hard to even imagine, huh?
I'd sure like to go watch!
Yeah... Saitama isn't that far.
What do you say we go cheer
them on at their next race?
That'd be great! It's settled. Let's go, for real!
"Japanese Paper"
"Japanese Paper Village
Entrance"
Great job, Kyoko! It's awesome
that you were able to ask him that!
Especially given how little
experience you've had.
Right?! I think so myself!
The fact that he doesn't have
a girlfriend is doubly lucky!
I bet he's got Kyoko on the brain right now!
I don't know...
Of course he does!
You've already let him know
that you're interested in him,
which should make him feel good,
no matter what kind of guy he is.
Aagh! What should I do?!
My darling, actually thinking about me?!
Now, now.
I...
I want to be cute. I've never
once thought this before, but...
...I want to be cute, so badly.
Keisuke... He's pretty popular
with the ladies, right?
What are you talking about?! That was sudden!
It's just, well, I kind of got that impression.
Yes, Keisuke's popular. Of course he is.
That's no reason to go bringing it up now.
Yeah...
Anyway, these past few years, he doesn't
seem to have any interest in women.
Huh?! Why not?
I guess because it's too much hassle.
I'm sure that he broke up
with the last girl he was dating
after he bought the FD
and joined the Red Suns.
He's the type of guy who puts all
his concentration into one thing.
Unlike Ryosuke, he's not efficient
enough to balance two things at once.
He said he broke up with her because he
was busy and couldn't make time to meet.
Still, he was out racing the
mountain pass every night,
so he was probably completely occupied.
Huh?
Hey, that black FD...
There she is!
Hello.
Hello...
I-I wonder if she came to see Keisuke.
Probably.
There's no "probably" about it.
Of course she did!
He's back!
You came all the way here?
I heard this was your home course.
Do you race every day, even when
there's no expedition planned?
Not every day, but...
I've got an assignment
regarding accelerator handling.
Right now, I'm sort of
focusing on that as I'm racing.
As fast as you are, you still get "assignments"?
Incredible! You all really
are on a different level.
Look... What are you doing here?
I thought if I came here I could see you...
And I wanted to see you, no matter what.
Have I bothered you?
What do you think they're talking about?
Shh!
This time I'll be perfectly clear.
If you've got no other
business here, don't come again.
Why?! Do you hate me?
It's not a matter of hate or like.
Then why?
Look, if you come here, it'll be a bother.
Wait! Listen, please!
I won't get in the way.
I can just watch, right?
I'm fine just being able to watch you race.
I swear I won't get in the way,
so please don't hate me so much.
I've never felt this way before, not once.
I don't know what else I should do...
I... I like you.
This is the first time I've
ever liked a man so much.
I can't put it very well,
but you're special to me.
Really!
So... I want to see you, no matter what!
That's all right, isn't it?
If I come because I just want
to see you... It's okay, right?
If I come again...
You don't get it at all. What I meant
when I said it'll be a bother.
If you were so terrible, I'd just
ignore you and that'd be the end of it.
But I can't do that, which is
why you'll get in the way.
Do you get it now?
If you're here, you're in the way.
That's all I have to say. Don't come here again.
You all right with this, Keisuke?
Whether I am or not, there's nothing I can do.
Sorry, but I'm going home for the day.
We'll get to the rest tomorrow.
Yeah...
Am I flustered? I don't have time for that now!
But if I let my guard down
even a little, I'll get left behind.
Takumi has gotten more and
more incredible since joining D.
I can't go fooling around
with some girl right now...
Not while he goes racing every day!
Do you get it now?
If you're here, you're in the way.
That's all I have to say. Don't come here again.
If I really think about it, what my
darling said makes sense, too.
What should I do, I wonder?
Liking someone so much like this...
It probably only happens once in a lifetime.
I can't give up.
I won't get discouraged
over something like this.
I won't give up!
Um...
Nobuhiko! Over here.
Thank you, I found him.
You're late.
Sorry. There was more traffic than I expected.
I'll introduce you. This is my cousin Nobuhiko.
Hi.
And this is the guy I told you about, Sakamoto.
'Sup?
I tell you, this guy is fast. He drives
a Ferrari and he's kind of a fanatic.
You won't find a more
perfect driver for our plan.
If Wataru recommends you, I'm sure
there's no doubt. We're counting on you.
Okay, hurry up and let us hear it, Nobuhiko...
The strategy you came up
with to beat the Eight-Six.
All right. We have data on
Project D's expeditions up till now...
...and the Eight-Six's racing capabilities,
which I observed with my own eyes.
I've performed a cumulative
analysis of both, and as a result,
through process of elimination, I was
able in my own way to derive an answer.
Quit usin' all that complicated talk.
Just say it so it's easy to understand.
Neither one of us here
was born as smart as you.
Agreed. Take it easy on us.
Actually, what I'm trying
to say is extremely simple.
Sakamoto, have you ever driven an FR?
Yeah.
Sakamoto can drive anything. He's driven
FRs the longest. He's really good.
Then we're okay. The fact is,
I brought it. Our ultimate weapon.
"Ultimate weapon"?
This.
Th-This is our ultimate weapon?
Are you being serious, Nobuhiko?
Hey, the coming of a new generation
Calling now for the arrival of a new era
How long are you going to
pretend you've forgotten?
(Tension that seems like it'll
rip my heart) This heartache...
Within those eyes,
something that can't be held back...
(Yeah, this image that won't let me go)
...stares intently at the night
Yes, the two who didn't even know how
to reach out and touch someone's
heart are already, from here...
(Hey, the coming of a new generation,
Check it, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Strike the sleeping dream awake
(Skillz enough to rend the night!)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
A risky tune that rocks the times
Blast my desire
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
break what you wanna break)