"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
Come out! Akina's ghost!
"Act 4: Into the Battle!"
--How about the booster?
--Okay.
Don't forget to check the air pressure, too.
Right...
I bet today's race will be another easy win.
--It won't even be close.
--Shut up and keep working!
What is it...?
Hey, get me that lug wrench.
What are they doing?
They're changing the FD's tires.
They seem to have several spares in that van.
They're changing the tires
to suit the conditions...
They act like professionals...
Crap...
It's ready to go any time, Keisuke.
What? Ah...thanks.
Isn't it past 10 yet?
Well... It's about 9:40...
Dammit...!
It hasn't come yet...
Brother, that Eight-Six...
...irritates me!
I was convinced that it could represent Akina...
Was I ever wrong! I've lost all my enthusiasm!
Now I'm going for the best time,
and I'll run away from them.
And I'm going to humiliate them.
If I don't, I won't be able to stand it!
Iketani, it's almost time.
Yeah... I know!
What's that?
Iketani!
Iketani!!
Itsuki...
What...What about the timed run?
We're going to start in a bit.
Good! I'm in time!
And who's representing the Speed Stars?
Well...
Kenji, get ready... at least mentally...
Yeah...
You're representing the team?!
Good luck! I'll be cheering you on!
This is the starting line.
Are you ready?
This is the finish line.
Everyone is in their designated positions.
You can start any time.
Roger!
So...should we start now?
He didn't come after all...
I'm counting on you, Kenji.
Yeah...
Are you kidding? This is my opponent?
Kenji.
You look pale.
You're sweating...
We're even feeling kinda
sick just watching you.
That's easy for you to say... But...
Toughen up! Get mean!
All right. We'll start the countdown.
Damn...!
10 seconds!
Wait a minute!
This is the finish line. A regular car
just passed us and went up there.
You don't want to pass it during the race...
Should we wait until it reaches the top?
This is a public road.
There's always going to be regular cars!
Forget about it! Start us!
All right.
Wait a minute!
Can you ask him what make that car was?
Could you tell what kind of car it was?
Well... I think it was a car
with flip-up headlights...
I think it was probably a Trueno, an Eight-Six...
Give that to me!
What color was the Eight-Six?!
Why are you guys so curious about that thing?
It was black and white.
It's a Panda Trueno.
He's here!
He showed up! My prey.
What are you going to do?
Is it okay to begin the countdown?
Not yet!
Wait until the Eight-Six arrives.
My real opponent shouldn't be
the 180 next to me. Right?
Yeah, that's right.
Kenji, you can go back now.
Yeah... That's quite a relief...
Your eyes are watering.
Yours, too!
He came through for us...
...so that he could protect the
Akina street racers' pride...
That's enough for me...!
Now I can start feeling like I don't
care about who wins or loses.
What is this...?
It seems strange...
There are people at each turn...
What are they doing here...?
I think I came to a weird place...
Oh, well, I guess it's all right...
If I win, I get a full tank of gas.
And I can go to the ocean without any pressure.
What's up, Takeshi?
Nice technique!
The way the back end moved
when it pulled out of the corner...
...was a nice touch.
What?!
Didn't you see it?
If you say so... But...
To us it just looked like a regular
Eight-Six with a brat driving it.
A car driven by a street racer
who is at a level where
he can maneuver it as easily
as his own hands and feet...
...has an aura about it.
Ryosuke Takahashi's driving has a strong aura.
His younger brother
Keisuke's aura is still weak.
But that Eight-Six was emitting a strong aura.
If he represents Akina...
...the winner is up in the air.
He's almost here.
He really came.
The fastest man on Akina's downhill!
The legendary super technician!
We'll show the Takahashi Brothers
Akina's real strength!
Come on, Eight-Six!
I'm looking forward to seeing
who gets out of the car.
It's been a while since I've been so excited.
He's kept us waiting for so long...
But such an obvious
strategy won't work on me.
I'll be watching you very closely.
Here it comes!
Give him a path! Show him to the starting line!
What's that car?
Everyone was waiting for that car.
But it's an Eight-Six.
Crap! Where did all these people come from?!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Excuse me...!
Oh, the Eight-Six! Is it...?!
Takumi!
Wow! It's him!
So this is the guy...
Takumi!
What's going on?!
What happened to your father?!
My father told me to show up.
Even if the car is here, without
your father, what good is it?
What?!
What are you going to do, Iketani?
--This isn't... what you said...
--Because you said... we're all right...
--I knew I shouldn't have come.
--Kenji has to race after all...!
Damn my old man! He really irritates me!
Takumi! Didn't your father say anything else?!
He just told me...
...to beat the FD on Akina's downhill.
What?!
Did he tell you to drive?
Yes...
Can you beat...
...Keisuke Takahashi?
Well... I can't be sure until we really race...
I've beaten him before...
You won once before...?!
A full tank of gas is riding on this race...
...so if you let me, I'll win no matter what.
Excuse me... Excuse me...
Takumi! You idiot!
Ouch! What are you doing?!
Takumi! Just how stupid are you?!
I'm so embarrassed watching
you that I'm blushing!
Move your car right now!
Don't interfere with the race!
Get in that Eight-Six now!
Wait a minute, Itsuki.
Iketani! I'm so sorry!
He is so stupid that he
doesn't understand anything.
Please forgive him!
Takumi... Do you, by any chance,
also deliver tofu, along with your father?
Now I do all of the deliveries.
For the past five years.
For the past five years?
Now I understand. Takumi!
All right. I'll put you in
charge of the downhill race.
What are you talking about, Iketani?!
If a novice like Takumi
tries the Akina downhill,
within minutes he'll cause
an accident and he'll die!
Don't worry about it. You need
to step aside and just watch.
Thanks for coming, Takumi.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah...
I'm sorry that we kept you waiting.
Really! I'm tired of waiting!
You're pretty young...
What's your name?
Takumi Fujiwara.
I'll remember your name.
I'm Keisuke Takahashi.
I won't make the same mistake twice.
Is it really all right?
It's totally foolish to race
an Eight-Six against a FD.
There's a huge difference in horsepower,
and the FD is the best
domestic cornering machine.
Both in the straights and in the turns,
the Eight-Six is outclassed!
We just need to have faith in him...
Then we'll begin the countdown.
--Roger!
Ten seconds to green!
Nine! Eight!
Seven! Six!
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
Fast! Keisuke Takahashi's FD!
350 horses are no joke.
His shifting is perfect.
It's no match.
At full acceleration, the Eight-Six
looked like it was standing still.
Takumi...
Coming off the line, that Eight-Six
has 150 horsepower at most.
It's not quite the monster
Keisuke was talking about.
The reason why it can shift so fast
is that it has tranny gears for a rally.
It must be perfect for the hairpins on Akina.
Still, there's no reason
Keisuke's FD would be beat out by it.
The monster isn't the car...
...but the driver?!
I won't give him a break.
I don't like using the
straightaways to pull ahead,
but this is a timed run.
I'll never even see that
Eight-Six in my rearview mirror.
What's that?!
This is the first corner! It's great!
The Eight-Six's line is incredible!
It wasn't more than 5 cm from the guardrail!
I've never seen anyone corner at that speed!
What?!
He's closing the gap?!
He's getting closer?!
It must be my imagination!
It's impossible!
Are... Are you serious?!
Takumi's father was once a great street racer?
Yeah.
I've seen him several times,
but he's just the gruff owner of the tofu shop.
I guess you really can't tell much
about a person by just looking at them.
According to Mr. Tachibana, he's still
the fastest on the downhill in Akina.
Anyway, that's who sent Takumi in his place,
so we should just believe in Takumi.
Yeah... It's much better than if I had run.
But even if his father is fast, Takumi is...
It sounds like Takumi beat
Keisuke Takahashi once before.
What?!
Takumi defeated Keisuke Takahashi?! No way!
I can't believe it! That spacey Takumi?!
He didn't even know what an Eight-Six was!
What?! What's in that Eight-Six?!
At incredible speed, it came
in with the rear end free
and it passed through
at an unbelievable speed!
It wouldn't be surprising if it
went airborne at any moment!
We've got shivers going up our spines!
He's caught up to me?!
What's happening? I must be going crazy!
Up to second gear, they're the same,
but the stretch is different...
If the straight is even a
little long, he'll pull away...
This is the straightaway
in front of the skating rink.
The two of them just passed by!
He's on Keisuke's bumper!
Akina's Eight-Six is unbelievably fast!
Is this for real?!
Keisuke's FD has never had
anyone keep up with it this far!
Man, I've got goosebumps...
On this long straightaway,
Keisuke pulled away,
but after this, there are many
hairpins. It may be a problem!
Did you hear him, Ryosuke?
We miscalculated...
We didn't know Akina had such a great driver...
Great attack!
That Eight-Six's attack was aggressive.
It was an incredible kamikaze technique!
He's got no sense of fear on the downhill.
In the straights, I'm faster.
But he's caught up to me.
That means I'm losing in the corners.
To be caught by a less powerful car
is the ultimate shame for a street racer!
I'll die before admitting that!
My old man...
Unless I pass that car,
he won't admit that I won...
There's no other way...
I guess I have to do that...
A full tank of gas is riding on this...
The setup point is in the next
five consecutive hairpin curves!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irete nani ka wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
Finally, the race has begun, hasn't it, Takumi?!
--Yeah...
--Did you do any special practice for this battle?
No, not particularly...
It's the usual way I deliver tofu...
I see! The regular run you do
is helping you, isn't it?!
--I suppose so...
--By the way, do you have any
secret plan for passing the FD?!
Well, yes... It's not exactly a secret plan, but...
A date with Natsuki in the Eight-Six
with a full tank of gas is riding on this,
so you have no option but to win!
--Yes...
--Next time, Initial D!
Something will happen in the
five consecutive hairpin curves!
Don't miss it!