"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
Oh, man! You guys stink!
Wataru hasn't gotten any better.
--Yeah.
--Here they come!
--Crap!
--Clear the road!
Hurry! They're here!
Watch and learn from the best!
That's awesome!
No one else can drive like that.
Go ahead and pass it.
An oncoming car at the turn's exit! Go wide!
It's clear!
Leave three inches. It's sandy!
Exactly! You're looking sharp!
No one can touch you now!
"Act 16: The Angel of Usui"
What?!
No way!
A girl you just met gave
you her phone number?!
Am I supposed to believe that?
What's the catch, really?
Really, Iketani!
The world isn't that simple!
I, uh, I...
Racers don't need girls!
Besides, if there's no catch, it's not like you.
What do you mean by that, Kenji?
Are you putting me down?
No, but it sounds too good to be true.
I hate seeing you jealous of my happiness.
Her long brown hair waving in the wind
and her seductive eyes glancing at me.
I'm positive God sent me this beautiful angel
because I'm an honest, hardworking man!
I'm off to Karuizawa tomorrow to see Mako.
Well, back to work!
Hey, why don't we follow
him and check her out?
Good idea!
I wanna see her with my own eyes.
But what if Iketani finds out?
Don't worry!
He's lost in a fantasy world right now.
Let's go see what she really looks like,
this angelic Mako.
Hey, leave Iketani alone.
We won't bother him.
When she dumps him, we'll cry with him.
That's friendship!
When she dumps him?
I doubt she's as pretty as he says she is.
He exaggerates everything.
--He gets obsessed, too.
--Right.
I think we were in junior high
when we went fishing at Akina Lake.
The fish weren't biting,
but I managed to catch a
small one right before we left.
He was, like, "Wow, it's huge!"
He went crazy.
It was this big.
People came to take a look at it.
I was so embarrassed.
He exaggerates. That's how he is.
Kenji, look to your left.
Crap!
I was lost in the story and
didn't realize I'd sped up.
So much for tailing him.
Sorry, Iketani!
Forgive us!
We just wanted to see what she looked like.
Seriously!
We had no intention of bothering you two.
Don't be mad, okay?
We'll turn around at the next interchange.
Oh, man. You don't have to go home.
I don't mind introducing you to her.
--You sure?
--All right!
But...
...don't follow us after that,
or I'll be really mad!
Cool!
Anyway...
...these are my friends.
Hi, I'm Mako Sato.
--Hi...
--Hello.
--Shall we, Mako?
--Yeah.
Shoo, shoo!
We're not dogs.
This isn't a dream.
Unbelievable.
It's shocking to see Iketani
with such a pretty girl...
Racers don't need girls.
Let's cry together, Kenji.
What?
Are you saying that I can't find a girlfriend?!
It's just a joke!
What should we do now?
Well, during this season,
Karuizawa isn't the place
for three guys to hang out.
Shall we go to Usui Pass?
Sorry...
So, what kind of cars do you like?
I liked, uh...
I admired the last generation RX-7.
An FC!
Hey, you have good taste.
You're a racer, aren't you?
Oh, um, is it that obvious?
Normally, I try to drive like everyone else.
So, Mako, what do you think of street racers?
They're okay. I like cars myself.
You do?!
Street racers usually have
better skills than normal drivers.
You can buy expensive cars with money,
but you can't buy technique.
I have much more respect for
those with good driving technique
than for those with fancy imports.
She's a good girl... an ideal girl!
So, this is Usui Pass.
I've never been here,
but it's much curvier than I had imagined.
It looks tough.
One corner after another,
and the road is narrow.
It doesn't look anything like Akina Pass.
I wonder who the fastest is here at Usui Pass?
Um, Iketani?
Yes?
How would you feel about a girl
who liked to drive the passes
and acted like a street racer?
--A Sileighty?!
--Yes.
They say a blue Sileighty is the fastest now.
And surprisingly, its driver is a woman.
A woman?!
--A female racer...
--Yes...
I'm totally okay with it, really.
As a matter of fact, I'd feel more
comfortable if she were a racer.
--Really?
--Yeah.
Now I get it.
She wants to be a racer,
which is why she likes an FC.
A Sileighty with a woman driver.
A Sileighty...?
--Is that an import?
--No.
It's a 180 with a Silvia front end on it.
Silvia and 180, so "Sileighty."
Its driver is the fastest at Usui Pass,
and is a woman.
I gotta see that!
You can see her there at night, usually.
It's not wise to challenge her, though.
No locals even come close to her.
It's called Akina Speed Stars.
I built the team.
We have a young racer who they say
is the fastest at Akina Pass.
Speed-wise, I'd say I'm right behind him.
What's wrong, Mako?
No, it's nothing.
Sorry, I must be boring you with my car talk.
No, it's not that.
I love cars, too, so it's fun.
Really? I'm glad.
So, do you also admire great
drifting skills and all that?
Sure.
You need a lot of experience, like I have,
to use that technique, though.
It's dangerous.
So, you're good at drifting?
--Sure.
--I'm happy for you!
Yeah?
Thank you for a wonderful day.
--So, Mako...
--Yes?
Well, I'm wondering if you have...
...you know, someone...
...you're seeing right now.
I don't have a boyfriend.
So, call me again, Iketani.
Wow!
Can you hear me, Iketani?
Wake up, Iketani.
Um, I'm...
Why are you here?!
We couldn't go back, 'cause
we were worried about you.
So, how did it go?
Today was a fine day, indeed.
You hungry? Dinner's on me!
We can also check out
the racers at Usui Pass.
It sounds like it went well.
I guess miracles do happen.
--Wow!
--They're good.
Every driver here has good skills.
Hey, Takumi?
You've never been to other passes, right?
How was it?
Well, I mean, I wasn't the one driving,
so I really can't say.
Are you sure? Your eyes were pretty serious.
Yeah?
They look totally different now,
as if you're a different person.
Could you race here?
I wouldn't know until I tried it.
--There!
--The Sileighty?!
--Continuous reverse drift!
--What the...?!
She's good!
--Did you see that?
--The narrow road made it intense!
I told Mako that I was good at drifting,
but I still panic when the rear slides out.
I seriously have to work at it,
or I'll lose my angel!
--Let's head down.
--Yeah, okay.
Every pass has a great racer.
He's going pretty fast, isn't he?
We got three people here.
I can't keep up.
We'd better give him some room.
He seems out of sync,
and his car's acting weird.
How can you tell?
I'm not positive, but that's
probably what's going on.
Probably?
He spun out!
Takumi was right.
Crap! A car's coming!
That was close!
Who is this idiot?!
As the rear slides out, he panics
and spins out of control.
It's a beginner's mistake.
Hey, S13!
Move out of the way, or you'll
put other drivers in danger!
I'm moving...
That's so embarrassing!
Let's act like we don't know him.
Sorry about that...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
So, it's Mako whose Sileighty
is the fastest at Usui Pass.
I wanna die!
--A day off?
--He hasn't called, either.
This is very rare for a workaholic like Iketani.
He must've taken it real hard.
He didn't say a word after
what happened last night.
At a rest area on the way back,
his eyes were dull from shock.
I felt too bad to say anything to him.
I had a bad feeling about this.
She was too cute to be his girlfriend.
Like I said, racers don't need girls.
Itsuki the Lonely Driver... that's my title.
I hope he'll snap out of it soon.
Telephone, Koichiro!
Tell them I'm sleeping...
It's probably Kenji.
It's a girl named Mako Sato!
Did you want to talk to me?
Yeah...
If you're here to make fun of me, please don't.
No, I'm not here to make fun of you.
I never suspected it was you.
I saw your Sileighty drift
through the narrow road.
The fastest at Usui Pass...
You could've warned me about that.
I'm sorry.
I've never told anyone about this.
It was shocking to me, too,
and I realized that I owed you the truth.
The truth?
I'm really the quiet type.
It's hard to believe that a quiet type
could drift that dynamically.
I'm one of those people whose
character changes behind the wheel.
No matter how fast I drive,
men don't see me as girlfriend material,
so I've decided to put an end to this.
I'm quitting racing after this summer.
To make this summer memorable,
I would like to race
Akina's Eight-Six at Usui Pass.
Wha...?
That's my wish.
In return for my wish...
...I'll give you my virginity.
Wait a minute! That's nonsense!
--Am I not good enough?
--That's not it.
He's my friend,
so I can't sell him out like that.
I get it now.
Her true intention...
...was not me, but Takumi.
Otherwise, a pretty girl like her
wouldn't be interested in someone like me.
I understand.
I'll do what I can.
--Really?
--Don't get me wrong, though.
I'm not doing this
because of your proposition.
Iketani...
I just want to make your wish come true.
It's okay...
...because for a short while,
I was falling for her.
I just want her to be happy.
I'd probably be laughed at for this,
but I really liked her.
I loved her...
...even though I was mistaken.
Ai ni tsukare hate samayotteta koro
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa
Mujaki na hitomi ni miserarete yuku
Sake bara no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku kimi o daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi o shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi o kanadeyou...
Kagayaku mirai e
Kazoe kirenai hodo tashikame aou
Jounetsu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani o ushinattemo
kono ude o hanasanai
Utsukushiku karen ni sake...
Kiseki no hana yo
Mako, how can you be interested in Iketani?
I don't know...
And you made that big proposition.
Maybe that was a little too much...
There're tons of good-looking guys,
so why Iketani?!
But I kind of like him...
--I really don't get it!
--Shush!
Next on Initial D: "Sudden-Death Death Match."
Don't miss it!