"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it's an era
where it travels in a second
But you don't know what
choice you should take
"Money can't buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don't realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can't even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let's warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That's our law!
--Whew! I'm beat!
--Ooh... That was rough...
Why do we have to practice so hard?
--I'm starving. Let's get some pizza!
--Count me in!
For real? With Natsuki Mogi?
Now that is one fine babe.
Everyone wants a piece of that booty!
Yeah, well, she'll do whatever I tell her to.
It's time I broke her in.
What do you mean, "break her in"?
You know what he means!
Girls are all the same.
They act like they don't want it at first,
but then they come around.
The other day I called her up to the roof, and...
"Locker"
I think it's time you shut
the hell up, before I make you!
Just who do you think you are?!
The little squirt doesn't know his place!
Cut it out, Takumi!
I've had enough of listening to you bastards!
Why, you little...!
--Back off, Takumi!
--You punk!
"Act 7: A Racer's Pride"
You're rude, Takumi.
When a person has a cute girl with him,
do you think he should be off
in his own little world? Really!
I just asked if you have a girl you like.
I have someone I can't help thinking of a little.
Iketani! Hey! Where'd Iketani go?
Iketani?
Oh, you mean Iketani, whose terrifying
screams echoed across Mt. Akina
as he rocketed down the dangerous
three-corner road and passed out!
That Iketani just left on a delivery.
He took the pickup truck.
Oh... If Iketani's not here,
then maybe you can help, Takumi.
Could you deliver some papers
to the Yamada shop for me?
You can take my car.
Uh, sure.
Hey, boss. Um...
You know, I have a license, too.
Why do you always ask Iketani
and Takumi to run errands?
Well, you see... put your hand on
your chest and tell me what you feel.
--Now do you understand?
--No...
Simply put, I can trust
Iketani and Takumi to drive.
As for you, though...
...you'd bring my car back with a
dent the size of your caved-in chest.
Well, there you have it.
You just wait and see.
Once I get my own Eight-Six,
I'm gonna be the fastest racer around...
Whoa, an R32!
Welcome, sir!
What a ride! The R32's the bomb!
N-Night Kids!
Hey, kid. My name's Nakazato.
Someone back on my turf
told me I could contact
a member of the Speed Stars at this station.
Tell me this. When can I find
that Eight-Six at Akina?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Aren't you a member of the Speed Stars?
Me... a member of the Speed Stars... Cool...
I guess I came to the wrong place.
Wait! No, you're at the right place!
Actually, that Eight-Six guy and me,
we're down like brothers.
What?!
Yeah, people call us the Eight-Six Duo.
We're the fastest down-hillers on our team.
Really?
Yeah, well... actually, he may be
a bit faster than me, but still...
I didn't know anyone on the
Speed Stars could race at that level...
Yeah, um... Well, never mind that.
Say, I can deliver him a message if you want.
After all, he's my bro.
All right. Tell him this.
10 o'clock this Saturday night.
10 o'clock this Saturday night...?
Nakazato of the Night Kids will be
waiting for him on top of Mt. Akina.
Waiting on top of Mt. Akina... What?!
It'll be a race to the bottom!
Wait! That's a... Hey!
Uh, you know... Wait a second, please!
Hey, wai...
Oh, now I've really done it!
Did he just challenge Takumi?
Oh, no! What am I going to tell Takumi?!
Takumi!
What are you all panicked about?
Never mind that.
Say, if you're free this Saturday,
you want to go racing at Mt. Akina?
--No.
--Why not?
Sorry, but I don't drive a car
unless it's absolutely necessary.
Takumi!
Thanks a lot. Come on in and have some coffee.
Okay.
Hey!
Not good. This is not good.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Takumi.
Let me ask you something.
Suppose--just suppose--a racer
were to challenge you to a race.
You'd accept, of course, right?
No way. I'm not into that scene.
What?! Don't say that!
What's it matter to you?
Um... well... uh... That's beside the point.
You know, if a racer receives a challenge,
he has to stand up and accept it!
Well, that may be true for a racer.
But I'm no racer.
No racer?
Besides, being forced to accept
challenges just isn't my thing.
Not good. This is definitely not good...
What'll I do?
Only two more days to go.
Eight-Six, Ryosuke Takahashi,
your days are numbered.
I'll show you who's number one!
Iketani!
You accepted a challenge from
the Night Kids of Mt. Myogi?!
Why were you keeping something
that big a secret from us?!
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's no use trying to deny it.
The word's out all over town.
Eight-Six and R32 going at it on the downhill!
Eight-Six? That's news to me!
What?! The word is, Nakazato came
to this gas station in person
to issue the challenge!
Takumi. Have you heard anything about this?
No, not a word.
No one knows about this? What's going on?
S-Sorry!
Itsuki... you didn't...
I... I accepted the challenge!
Please forgive me!
Yesterday, Nakazato of the
Night Kids really came here.
He came by when Iketani
and Takumi were out. I...
I couldn't help but pretend to be
a member of the Speed Stars...
...and before I knew what was happening...
...he had already issued
the challenge and driven off.
Why didn't you tell us about this before?!
I was going to tell you, I swear.
I was just waiting for the right moment.
Takumi, I'm sorry. I messed up.
Please forgive me!
It's a bit late now...
Forgive me... Please forgive me...
Looks like the R32's out again tonight.
He's racing against the
Eight-Six tomorrow night, right?
I'm definitely going to watch that!
If Nakazato of the Night Kids
is challenging the Eight-Six
that beat Keisuke Takahashi,
there's no way we can miss that!
On the surface it may seem like a race
between the Speed Stars and the Night Kids,
but it's really a battle
between Nakazato's pride
and the pride of the Red Suns'
Takahashi Brothers!
No matter how the race turns out,
Ryosuke Takahashi's not going
to just sit back and watch.
The summer nights are
starting to heat up already!
Oh, man...
What are we going to do?
Everyone around town's
talking about this race.
It's too late to back out now.
Maybe I'd better ask Takumi to race.
Even Takumi might not have
what it takes to go against the R32.
That Night Kid Nakazato is as famous
a racer as the Takahashi Brothers...
It'd be a tough battle. It might
even be over from the get-go.
On second thought, maybe I
shouldn't ask him after all.
There you go.
Hey... Dad.
Is an R32 any good?
R32? Yeah... That's a fast car...
Could you win? In a downhill...
...against the R32?
Yeah. I'd win against any
car I raced, R32 or not.
Do you think... I can win?
I don't know...
It'd be a close race.
Why are you asking?
You gonna race an R32?
No...
I'm... I'm just asking...
See ya.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Now it's against an R32...
I'd better adjust the Eight-Six's settings...
It'd be a close race.
I thought I'd find you if I
came here around this time.
It was about this time the night I first met you.
So you're going against Nakazato
from the Night Kids, huh?
You're the talk of the town.
For your information, I don't
recall accepting that challenge.
What?!
He came to challenge me while I was away.
I don't intend to race him.
What do you mean you
don't intend to race him?
Night Kid Nakazato issued a
personal challenge to you, right?
Why don't you just accept it?
Show him who's the fastest! You can beat him!
Why does it matter to you?
This is between him and me.
No, it's not just between you two!
It's because you beat me!
If you lose to anyone, it's gotta
be to the Takahashi Brothers!
Until one of us beats you,
you can't lose to anyone else!
Not even to the R32!
I said I wasn't going to race him!
I have no reason to.
Reason? Does any racer need a reason to race?
Who ever said I was a racer?
I'm in no mood for jokes!
Are you being sarcastic?!
In order for your technique
to be as good as it is,
you must have practiced for years!
Why would someone drive
like a racer if he's not a racer?!
I don't drive like I do because I like it.
I have to in order to help out at home.
Stop denying it.
No one can get as good
as you if they hate driving.
That's not it... You wouldn't understand.
You're the one who doesn't understand!
Could someone who hates
racing ever master drifting?
Only a person who loves the sport
could master something like that!
Maybe you don't realize it, but you're a racer.
Deep down you love driving! You hear me?!
If you love driving, then that
makes you racer enough!
And if you're a racer, then you should
be proud of your driving skills!
Accepting challenges is a racer's pride!
You make me sick.
Do I really like driving...
...but just don't realize it?
Still...
...being forced to accept every
challenge that comes along...
That isn't for me!
Hey! Itsuki! Where's Takumi?
He's on the late shift today.
Oh...
Iketani...
I'm going to go to Mt. Akina
tonight to apologize to Nakazato.
Itsuki...
I'll get down on my knees if I
have to and tell him the truth.
Maybe he'll understand.
Besides, the Speed Stars had
nothing to do with this...
You don't think we can
convince Takumi to race?
No. I know him better than anyone,
and he'll never do it...
He hates being forced into things
or having to follow others' orders.
He looks real mellow,
but once he says something,
there's no changing his mind...
Stubborn... just like his father.
He doesn't understand why
racers have to accept challenges.
The whole system offends him.
When someone tries to force
him to do something, he snaps.
One time in eleventh grade, he flipped out
and beat up a group of
seniors after soccer practice.
What?! Takumi did that?
Boss, I finished cleaning up outside.
Thanks.
No problem. See you tomorrow, then.
Takumi!
Come and have a seat.
Okay...
You know, I overheard some talk.
You're going to race an R32 tonight?
What? I'm...
Don't do it, Takumi. That guy's bad news.
Uh... No, I wasn't...
No, no. I know what you're going to say.
I've known everything from the beginning.
I know it wasn't your decision to take this race.
Itsuki was the one who screwed
up and accepted it, right?
Yeah...
You know, you're too nice sometimes.
You gotta stop bailing your
friends out all the time.
Trust me. Whatever you do,
don't race that R32.
There's a lot you don't know about cars.
Do you even know what an R32 can do?
Is an R32 that amazing?
Gotcha! He took the bait...
It's beyond amazing.
That car's in a class by itself!
Its driving system combines everything good
about FR and four-wheel drive.
It's a beast!
An Eight-Six or GT-R is no match for it.
If the driver was an amateur,
you'd have a chance,
but you're up against a famous racer, right?
Dad didn't tell me this.
He said it'd be a close race.
Hey.
You with me?
You just became famous yourself
by beating that team from Akagi.
You shouldn't ruin your name so fast...
It's not wise to go up against someone
you have no chance of defeating.
You hear me?
Since your opponent's driving an R32,
no one would call you
a coward for backing out.
A coward?!
Boss...
Thanks for the warning...
...but I could care less
about my fame as a racer.
So you aren't going to back down?
No.
Hearing about how amazing that car is
has only made me want to see it in action.
I'm not afraid of an R32 or any other car.
Whew!
He's exactly like his father...
"Temporarily Closed
Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Temporarily closed?
Dad never said anything about this.
How's he going to make
money if the shop's closed?
Oh, no! The car!
If he went out drinking, I'm really in trouble.
He won't be back until morning!
I can't do anything without a car.
I should have asked to borrow it this morning!
Look at the crowd!
There's even more people out
tonight than at the Akagi race!
Why did so many people come tonight?
You know they're not here to see the R32.
Yeah, they want to see that Eight-Six drift!
They say he barrels through
corners as if they're straightaways!
I can't wait to see this!
Oh... I see...
Uh, if he happens to show up,
could you ask him to call home?
Thanks...
It's no use... I can't find him...
Damn!
Where the hell are you?!
Give me back my Eight-Six!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
So no one intervenes
Never stop, I don't want to stop
Even if you cry because of a sacrificed love
Aim for the peak, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! The warning chime is so cheap!
The sheep should clear the road
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy motivation is total stimulation
You tried to escape,
but anywhere is a safety zone
Something is within your grasp
and something is forgotten
Even if the world ends it will never change
Beasty shout, no one can touch you
Cross over now to the time of an intense dream
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Like a streak to the peak
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind,
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let's ignore the constraints of logic
'Cause they're a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
Don't look back on your love or your past
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
Kenji, who do you think will win
this battle Itsuki got us into,
the R32 or the Eight-Six?
Of course, I'd like to say the Eight-Six...
...but I don't know if even Takumi
can beat a GT-R, the fastest domestic.
The biggest question is if
Takumi will even come to race!
If he doesn't show up,
then Kenji will once more...
Don't say it!
Next time on Initial D, "Time's Almost Up!"
Takumi, please get here soon!
Don't miss it!