"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it's an era
where it travels in a second
But you don't know what
choice you should take
"Money can't buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don't realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can't even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let's warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That's our law!
What's going on? I'm so tense I could die.
I wanna go to Mt. Akina so bad.
I'm not really sure if I love
driving that much, but...
For the past five years, come rain or snow,
I've driven Mt. Akina more often than anyone.
Anyway, that's the story.
So I'm taking the car, Dad!
You'd better hurry, Takumi! It's almost time.
--It's him!
--He's here!
Oh, no! They found me!
It's too late to run.
I'm dead!
What the hell are you doing
sitting in the middle of the road, Itsuki?
Ta... Ta... Ta...
Get out of my way! I'm gonna run you over.
Takumi! You came!
Yeah.
Sorry, Itsuki... for being late.
Takumi...!
A street racer should race
if he's challenged, right?
Takumi...!
Wait... don't...
"Act 9: Battle to the Limit!"
Jeez, he's young!
Bet he hasn't even had his
license for more than a year!
Where'd a kid like this learn his technique?!
I thought for sure I'd be
facing a guy older than me!
So that's a GT-R...
It's beyond amazing.
That car's in a class by itself.
Its driving system combines everything
good about FR and four-wheel drive.
I'm Nakazato... one of the Night Kids.
What's your name?
Takumi Fujiwara.
I'll remember that.
What do you say we get started?
--Who do you think's gonna win?
--Nakazato, of course!
--R32!
Now you tell me
that heavy understeer during full throttle
is the better setting if you have skills,
but if maneuverability is suddenly different,
don't you think Takumi's going to
panic when he charges into corners?
Maybe you should've warned him...
It wouldn't have done any good.
He's not exactly a driver
who drives with his head.
What?! Then all the more reason to tell him!
It's all right.
You don't have to worry.
See, he might not be too sharp upstairs...
..but his body and his senses are finely tuned.
It's too late to think first and react
to the information you feel
on your back through the seat.
Your arms and legs have to move
unconsciously to control drifting.
That's why you don't need to worry!
He has this great sense of knowing
when and how to accelerate
while the car is drifting.
So even if the suspension
setting is a little different,
it won't matter to him in the least.
He'll make minor adjustments
and just ride it out.
See, the Eight-Six is a car that trains its driver.
Here's the goal.
The road's clear of regular traffic,
so anytime you're ready...
Iketani! We can go anytime!
All right!
I'm gonna start the countdown!
Start in ten seconds.
Takumi! I'm counting on you!
Keisuke...
We're gonna have the best seats
in the house for tonight's battle!
Now hop in! They're about to start!
5...
4... 3...
2... 1...
Go!
The R32 is ahead!
Yeah, but Takumi's not too far behind!
Here they come!
Get your seat belt on!
Hey! That's the FC.
Ryosuke Takahashi just dashed out!
Is he trying to horn in on the race?!
What the hell...?! Is it going
to be a three-way super battle?
Suddenly, it's turned into a
race for the fastest in Gunma!
The GT-R driver... He's slowing down...
Is he waiting for me?!
It'd be a waste to lose
him on the straightaway.
I wanna have a battle here!
The real starting line comes
as soon as we hit the first corner!
Hey, look at that!
Nakazato's easing up on the gas
and waiting for the Eight-Six!
Hope his overconfidence
doesn't end up costing him
in the last half of the race!
Here they come!
The first corner... and all
three cars, taking it in a row!
Wow! Just like Bunta said!
What the hell...?!
No way, mister!
Pulling stunts like that
ain't gonna get you caught up to me!
Getting to eyeball it from this close up...
That drift looks just like a work of art!
A four-wheel drift in full throttle, and
he's barely applying the countersteer!
Do you realize how incredible that is?!
He's pushing that Eight-Six to its outer limits
and controlling it like it was
his own hands and feet!
Even I can't control the FC like that!
It's exciting!
Yeah, maybe, but little by little,
Nakazato is gaining ground!
Can the Eight-Six win this one?!
Yes! This is it!
It's like I can feel the blood
rushing through my veins!
This is the battle I've been waiting for!
Ready, boy? I'm really gonna cut loose now!
Let's see how far you can keep up!
Hey...
Something's different...
Something's different with the car!
Even if I floor the gas,
the car doesn't lose control.
Does this mean I can step on
the gas sooner than before?
When I was at work today,
did Dad fiddle with it?!
'Cause it sure wasn't like this
when I made the deliveries this morning!
Now I get it!
That's why he was out before!
He was working on this!
Don't know why...
But anyway, it does feel
a whole lot better this way!
Because it doesn't slide too much...
I can push it all the way!
--Yow!
--Amazing!
That's some un-freakin'-believable drifting!
That's the first time I've seen a guy
drift all the way through that corner!
Yeah, he's nuts!
He'd never be able to do it if he didn't
have total mastery over his speed!
What the heck was that?!
That's no kind of drift I've ever seen before!
Incredible! That's drifting I'll never forget!
Man, oh, man!
The Eight-Six is still on the R32's tail!
He's doing it!
Looks like Takumi's sticking
right behind the R32!
Mind-blowing!
I mean, Nakazato's an ace...
Line him up with Ryosuke
Takahashi, another superstar,
and you got a battle royal brewing already!
And my best friend's racing against
both of 'em?! Unbelievable!
I mean, that is too cool!
Well, yeah, but...
...Ryosuke Takahashi and his
FC aren't even in the race.
He's acting more like a third-person witness.
Right. Takumi's up against Nakazato here.
His R32 has the Eight-Six at a disadvantage...
But with Takumi at the wheel,
the Eight Six'll pull through in the end!
Oh, yeah. Takumi will take it, for sure!
Right, guys!
He's creeping further and further away!
Nakazato's got a big mouth,
but it looks like he's got
the skill to back it up!
Look at how he distributes the load,
subduing the understeer while driving!
He really knows how to
draw out the GT-R's power.
Not pretty to look at...
This is not the time to take it easy.
Hey, bro...
Whose side are you on, anyway?!
If the kid loses this one, it's all over!
The real contest is only about to begin.
The first half has comparatively
more long straightaways...
Lots of gentle slopes, too.
There are lots of
disadvantages for the Eight-Six.
But the inclines are gonna start
getting rougher right around here.
Perfect for a downhill
specialist to strut his stuff!
All right! This kind of low-gear hairpin curve
is right up the R32's alley!
All I gotta do is cut my speed
by slamming on the brakes...
Going downhill, like it or not, the front
wheels still have to bear the load,
so its weakest point, the pushing
understeer, hardly occurs.
Furthermore, accelerating from a low gear
is what this car does better than any other!
The fastest machine on the racing circuit...
...is the toughest machine even on open roads!
The R emblem on the rear
is the legendary symbol for invincibility!
Can you get close enough to read it?!
Hey, Iketani...
What?
I've been thinking.
'Till now, I thought Takumi
was just a unique racer
who's fast only when he's racing on Akina.
But if he raced on a different mountain pass,
how well would he drive?
Don't you wonder about that?
Well, sure, I've mulled it over...
But right now, all I'm thinking
about is the battle at hand!
Win, Takumi!
Takumi!
Oh, man!
My eyes can't keep up with him!
Looks like he's finally kicking out the jams!
His inside tires are gripping the rim of the road!
This is the one! The trick that I lost to!
Didn't think I'd ever get
the chance to see it again!
Ryosuke's stopped with the chatter.
Meaning there's no time for that now?
I've ridden shotgun with him tons of times...
But this is the first time I've
seen him driving like this!
I've never seen him so serious!
"Akina Skate Center"
Getting closer...?!
The Eight-Six is catching up to me?!
Impossible!
Brilliant! Catching up to me after all that...
All my prejudices about the
Eight-Six being a 10-year-old car
have just been blown away!
It's a first-rate fighting machine!
Okay, the kid gloves are off!
Man, this is the best rush I've had in ages!
In fact, this has gotta be the
hottest road race I've been in
since getting this car!
When it comes to hairpin turns,
he can't match the R32!
No matter how close the
Eight-Six sticks to the R32,
the distance between them
always widens after a hairpin!
Man, that Nakazato's got guts, too...
Attacking the road like that,
downhill in a heavy-ass R32!
Wha-What the...?!
The Eight-Six closed the gap
at the high-speed corner?!
Going over 100 kilometers an hour
while doing a four-wheel drift
close enough to graze the guardrail?!
I don't think any of it has to do
with the car's capabilities!
That guy... has got a screw loose!
If he makes one slip-up, he's roadkill for sure!
But now I understand his secret!
With a lightweight like the
Eight-Six, if he loses speed once,
it takes like forever to get it back up again.
He never lets himself lose a fraction
of speed more than he has to!
Now I finally get why,
when I raced against him,
he could always catch up to me,
no matter how many times I lost him!
Crap!
I can't shake him!
Just the opposite!
He's hanging on to me for
longer and longer periods!
The bastard... is tough!
Nakazato's clearing the guardrail
by a good 20-30 centimeters.
No matter how fast you are,
that's about right.
Yet the Eight-Six's bumper
is almost close enough
to the rail to make sparks!
That guy's in a league of his own!
How?! How can he control a drift
with that kind of precision?!
Since I've been steering
hard and using the ABS,
the load on the front tires has
been a lot heavier than I thought!
This race is suddenly getting
much more challenging!
The five hairpins are coming up...
That's where he left you in the dust.
And I bet that's gonna be
a key point this time, too.
An R32 versus an Eight-Six...
Who would've thought the
battle would be this fierce?
Both of those cars are
being taken to their limits.
But which one of them
is gonna take the prize?!
I'm at the hairpins! And I can hear 'em coming!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
So no one intervenes
Never stop, I don't want to stop
Even if you cry because of a sacrificed love
Aim for the peak, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! The warning chime is so cheap!
The sheep should clear the road
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy motivation is total stimulation
You tried to escape,
but anywhere is a safety zone
Something is within your grasp
and something is forgotten
Even if the world ends it will never change
Beasty shout, no one can touch you
Cross over now to the time of an intense dream
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Like a streak to the peak
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind,
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let's ignore the constraints of logic
'Cause they're a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
Don't look back on your love or your past
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
Ryosuke, most expected the R32
to have a great advantage.
The R32 is 4,640 mm long and 1,720 mm
wide, and weighs a thousand...
In other words...
In other words, the R32 is 4,640 mm
long and 1,720 mm wide...
In other words, traveling
downhill, Takumi might...
In other words, the R32 is 4,640 mm long and...
All right already! Next time on Initial D,
"The 5 Consecutive Hairpins"!
Don't miss it!