Hey, the goal is all on the satnav.
Space out and go on, no problem.
100% safety, 0% risky?
Don't stress over minor things,
just toss that out the window.
Who decides what's right?
Don't bother about stuff like that.
You just have to stay focused on
All the things you love, and beyond the raging storm.
(So now it goes above and beyond)
To infinity!
Outsoar the Rainbow.
Don't just stand and watch.
Amp up your senses and fly high.
Let go and fly free even farther.
(Ain't no satisfied, so never stop to fly)
Infinity.
(You can reach the goal on your own)
Initial D
Crawling desperately several thousand times.
Only they are the ones that deserve to look back and talk.
History will prove that someday.
I'm scared, Mom.
Mom, Mr. Hojo complimented me again yesterday.
Everyone tells me I'm awesome
saying Mr. Hojo's team members
can't follow me from behind.
Oh, I see.
Mom, is this something I can brag about?
This is the first time in my life that
older people have complimented me.
I'm happy for what you can do,
but you have to be modest, Shin.
Don't be overconfident.
There are many drivers out
there who are faster than you.
That may be true
But more than anything, it was a blast.
It's not like I want to be number one
but the truth is, no one
could stay behind me.
Mom, I've heard that
there will be a major street race soon
and Mr. Hojo said he
might ask me to participate.
Street racing?
Yes, but when Mr. Hojo talks
about it, he sounds really scary.
It's like he's a different person from
his usual, kind self, so I don't like it.
So I'm not really interested in doing it.
Mom was right after all.
There must be a lot of fast drivers.
I'm no good at all.
I shouldn't have done this.
I don't like this anymore.
I want to quit and drive off.
Act 4  [ Dream ]
Could you be
Yes, you must be.
I hate this, I hate this
If so, I can do it.
As I thought, your biggest
advantage is your racing line.
If you're the type of driver
who aims to stay on his line
then you'll be disappointed when you fail to do it.
That's the impression I got
while watching you from behind.
Don't hate me.
It was a little too aggressive,
but at least, I didn't hit your car.
I got passed!
I got passed on this course!
There they are.
Those wings
This feedback from the front
But from here on, it's a slow section.
When it comes to a technical section,
my car is properly tuned.
Even if I don't use it, I'll pull
away with just my concentration.
There will be no second round.
A disappointing report just came in.
Shinji was overtaken in the second hairpin.
Facing reality, I'll say this again
No, I have to admit that I've
underestimated Fujiwara Takumi.
He's already exceeded my expectations
by keeping up with Shinji's cornering work
then he passed him and went ahead.
That's hard to believe.
Shinji must feel the same way.
I'm glad I recruited him for this battle.
Only Fujiwara Takumi can put
this much pressure on Shinji.
He may not have realized this, but he has a strong passion for driving within him.
Once he realizes it, his abundant experience will spontaneously drive him forward.
Mom, I must have become
overconfident without realizing it.
All those compliments made me conceited.
How embarrassing for me
to let a fast driver like him pass.
I was clueless beyond belief.
Maybe I just got too excited by all the spectators.
It's not like me to want to be a hero.
Despite a strong sense of self-consciousness, I'm just an ordinary, timid, wallflower type.
A boring guy who's not popular with girls.
That's who I, Inui Shinji, am.
But my...
My true self...
just doesn't want to lose in racing.
I've driven this road more than anyone else.
This is the only thing I'm good at
so in this battle, I just can't
All the fast drivers we know don't take their foot off the brake pedal, even after finishing deceleration at a corner's entrance.
That's to dive deeper into the corner while
keeping the weight on the front tires.
To be exact, your speed
changes through a corner
in order to decelerate at the entrance,
and accelerate at the exit.
But Inui Shinji doesn't change his speed
from the entrance to the exit while cornering.
No deceleration or acceleration means the
whole tire's grip acts in the lateral direction.
Theoretically, it allows him to
achieve the optimum cornering speed.
Wait a minute, Brother.
Does this mean the benefit of his
driving style is not just faster speed, but
Right, the tires.
Tires?
I can kind of see it.
When you tackle a corner hard
by delaying the brake timing
the entire vehicle weight
will be on the outer front tire.
On the other hand, if the speed doesn't change in the corners, the tire wear can be evened out.
The downhill is particularly
hard on the front tires.
Even if you drive at the same pace,
if your tire wear is less
it'll give you a definite advantage
at a critical moment near the goal.
This is bad.
I can feel a dangerous aura behind me.
His tension was down a while
ago, but it's back already.
Damn, I need concentration more now than ever.
If I lose it, I'll be done for.
I've prepared for a technical section.
If you think you can pass, try it.
He cleared the individual corners in the lead.
The tide's on our side.
There's not much left.
I hope this ends without a hitch.
Anyhow, strange things keep
happening one after another.
It's unusual for this type of battle
to have three position changes.
There's no straightaway, and the
road is narrow on this mountain pass.
It's impossible to switch
the lead so many times.
That means such a theory doesn't apply to them.
If you assume it's impossible, you can't do
anything and you don't even try to make a move.
As soon as you wonder whether
you can pass or not, it's too late.
No matter how reckless you have to be,
only a strong motivation of getting ahead
will successfully make you pass your opponent.
If you think that way,
every corner is a passing point.
Every corner is a passing point?
At least, that's the kind of battle they're fighting.
I can't explain it.
That's the reality before them.
The front tires
Not good enough.
He's started to leave some room.
Maybe I can go.
No, I'll go!
I'll do it, no matter what!
There was contact!
If my assumption is correct
Inui Shinji's cornering can only be achieved by an exceptional level of experience with this course.
Even if you can drive at the same speed, you can't
use your tires the same way he does, not even Fujiwara.
He must really be fighting against the understeering.
Wear on the front tires causes understeering, which can't be controlled by any technique.
A slower entry into the corner
is the only way to cope with it.
You must be struggling, but not
all of your chances are lost yet.
Your last trump card is the high revolution zone.
It's a matter of switching your
mindset and adjusting to the situation.
Ordinary drivers can't do it
but if it's him
Listen, Fujiwara.
This is an important point, so listen carefully.
The modified 20-valve 4AG in your Eight-Six is a
super high-rev unit, capable of more than 10,000 rpm.
But when we started Project D, Matsumoto and I
decided to change the engine's output characteristics.
We increased the mid-range torque to give it
more consistent power delivery than before.
It's a result of optimizing both
durability and combat potential, but
unlike before, it doesn't produce a lot of power at the highest range of engine rev.
We've been racing with the rev
limit at 9,000 until now, but
this time, we'd better prepare a strategy for
using the higher range, which we haven't used.
But a higher rev doesn't
make me go faster, right?
It depends on the situation.
Let me explain.
Sounds close.
They must be right over there.
There!
I can't turn.
He got us.
I never thought I'd see such a shocking scene.
But that was a dirty move.
He boldly hit him on the side.
That may be true, but it's unusual for
Takumi to be passed so easily on the inside.
Takumi lost speed for some reason.
His cornering speed is the
fastest in the northern Kanto area.
His unmatched super high speed drift is
Gone, you say?
That means he has no hope.
That can't be true. Don't fool around.
There's no way Takumi can lose.
I can't accept that, no matter what!
I just can't
It's Takumi!
He will turn this around!
Crap, I'm really in trouble.
Even if we enter a second round,
I won't be able to defeat him with these tires.
But a higher rev doesn't
make me go faster, right?
It depends on the situation.
Let me explain.
It's true that you don't gain much power even if you rev higher than 10,000 rpm.
Instead, a higher rpm means each gear
can rev the engine to a wider range.
In a situation where your opponent tops off his engine power, and wonders when to shift up
if you keep your foot on the accelerator without hesitation, you can gain 0.3 - 0.4 seconds.
It'll be about the half the length of a car.
In a dead heat, there'll always be a situation where you can make use of your advantage on a mountain pass.
I want you to find out where you
can do that during today's practice.
It'll be your last resort,
which will strain the engine
so you don't want to use
it unless you have to.
I have no other option but to attack.
I'll pass one more time!
Please hold out, my Eight-Six.
There!
No way! You're there?!
His headlights are off! That's ridiculous!
You're in my way.
I still have some grip left on the rear tires.
I won't lose in the
acceleration at the exit.
The road's so narrow, I feel choked up.
I can't trace my line
but I don't want to lose!
I've gotta step on it!
The next is
the last corner!
I'm sorry I couldn't give
you better strategic advice.
Don't worry about it.
This was entirely my mistake.
I over-revved too much, but
somehow it went higher than the limit.
When your Eight-Six's engine
blew and you spun 180 degrees
you cut the clutch to
regain your tire grip, right?
In the end, the difference in the level of experience mattered in a dogfight.
I wished so hard to win.
Maybe my Eight-Six recognized it, and
sacrificed itself to give me one last chance.
Takumi!
You did it, Takumi.
You're the hero of the Gunma racers.
Well, um
I'm sorry, I couldn't
I couldn't become a hero.
It's okay.
Seriously, you did great.
No one's blaming you.
I'm glad you're safe.
This loss will definitely help Shinji
become much faster and much stronger.
Retire for good?!
It's sad, but I think it's the ultimate farewell.
This car's been Takumi's arms and legs, writing a number of legendary episodes.
It probably deserves to be put
to rest quietly with no losses.
Is that the only way?
It's really sad, isn't it?
Say
Can I keep this car at home?
I'll fix it little by little with my own money.
But, as Yuichi says, it's reached its limit.
It's not for a battle or anything.
I just want to keep it.
I understand how you feel.
Well, if you insist
Alright!
Nice shot, Takumi!
You're far better, like going at full throttle.
I'm just
That's not true.
You're getting better and better.
You can't even compare it to the other day.
This is just between us.
We've received some inquiries about Keisuke
and Fujiwara from several professional teams.
Really? That's awesome.
If they step up,
that'll be so inspiring to us.
Our dream never ends, does it?
The real Project D goes on from here.
Isn't that right, Ryosuke?
I hereby declare!
I'll become a pro.
You'll be successful. No doubt!
I guarantee it.
You moron.
You're the designated driver.
This is yours.
Oh great
The sun is about to set.
I don't know what this sadness is about.
An unforgettable summer is going to end.
Kaori
Ryosuke, your dream
I want to train Gunma drivers who
can compete around the world.
I want to keep finding diamonds in
the rough, who can fly out from here
train them, and send them off.
That's my dream. After all,
the D in Project D stands for "dream."
Ryosuke, I'm glad I met you
and I'm happy you've made
so many wonderful friends.
Goodbye, Kaori.
I got no impression.
This town is made by the imitation.
Wanting your sensation.
In this silly simulation.
I wanna rage my dream.
I got no impression. I feel gray.
The distortion is too strong.
Imitation all over town.
You seek reality with so much passion.
I can't get close because of your devotion.
I feel your frustration in your shout.
Taste your vibration.
You shake me up in the sensation.
Rage your dream.
You dash through time.
Ladies Golf Championship
Even the wind glows bright.
Rage your dream.
Just remember one thing.
Feel the wind.
I'll be waiting.
Rage your dream.
In the never-ending street
without looking back at your love or your past
Twin Ring Motegi
you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
You live in the present.
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
I don't let others meddle in.
Never stop.
I don't want to stop
even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
The sheep should make room.
Because I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
Your motivation is easy.
Everything is simulated.
Even if you want to break out,
you'll end up in a safety zone.
You obtain something while you lose something else.
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout.
No one can handle it.
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a streak to the peak.
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Knock down in comma zero one second.
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
The puffery, full of logic
is bothering, so let's ignore it.
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
You dash through time.
Even the wind glows bright.
Rage your dream.
Just remember one thing.
Feel the wind.
I'll be waiting.
Rage your dream.
In the never-ending street
without looking back at your love or your past
you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
You live in the present.
Even today, young drivers keep on racing.
Wrestling to realize their dream.