"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Hakone's fog is nice.
It hides the dirty side of reality.
When I stand still like this, there's
nothing other than absolute silence
and overwhelming loneliness.
This is the state of nirvana, right, Kaori?
Ever since I lost you, I feel like
I've been standing in the fog.
I'm going to have a race against
Ryosuke where we both bet our lives.
I'll send one of us to your side.
So make a choice.
This time, follow your heart, Kaori.
Long time no see, Ryosuke.
You look a little neater, huh?
It's been a while, Hojo Rin.
Senpai.
I've heard the story.
I called Ryosuke's cell,
but it seems to be turned off.
I left a message,
but I haven't heard back.
I've been told that he's not
in the college lab either.
If Ryosuke secretly modified his FC,
I'm sure he must have a reason for it.
Matsumoto is the one who's been
tuning and maintaining the FC
so I've tried calling him to find
out if he knows something, but
I can't reach him either.
Something is definitely not
right with both of them missing.
If that's the case, I'll just ignore this.
Huh?
I mean, for the time being it's
pointless for us to get upset over this.
How could you not be?
Aren't you worried?
My brother must have a
significant reason for doing this,
including going solo behind our back.
He's always been been like this.
You know that, don't you?
He always makes the right choice.
He'll come back and feign
ignorance as if nothing happened.
Just have faith in him and wait.
There's no point in worrying.
Let's just act like we normally do.
What we should be doing now
is preparing for the final battle.
That's what my brother
would say if he were here.
There's no need to worry
about a remote possibility.
He's Japan's most ingenious street racer.
Don't forget that.
Act 9  [ Grim Reaper ]
Ryosuke
I'll be waiting here, so please
pick me up when you're done.
I plan to return to Gunma
in your car's passenger seat.
I haven't thought about any other way.
Even if it takes several days, I'll be waiting...
Even if it rains, to the point where I get soaked...
In other words, if you
don't return, I'll die here.
I can really see you doing that.
I'll return no matter what.
Thank you.
It's a promise, Ryosuke.
Please come back safely.
A white FC?
Yeah.
A guy saw it when he was
visiting Akagi the other day.
Do you mean Takahashi
Ryosuke is making a comeback?
There's no way.
It's probably a copy by a hardcore fan.
That could be the case.
Remember those impersonators the other day?
That's not likely.
Akagi is Takahashi Ryosuke's home ground.
Any impersonator would
get caught immediately.
He's right.
Hey, did Takumi say anything?
Not a thing.
I'd better call him.
If he ignores his best friend like he did the other day, I'll chew him out.
Ryosuke did?
No, I don't know anything about it.
Maybe it's just a look alike.
Okay, bye.
What's wrong?
Another impersonator?
Um, no, I don't think it's that serious.
But come to think of it, we have
to thank those impersonators.
After all, I met you because of them.
I guess so.
Hey, Takumi, why don't we go
somewhere together again?
We've been to the beach,
so how about the mountains?
This is way too risky.
I've never seen such a high speed
downhill stage like this anywhere.
It's really disadvantageous to be in
the lead position against a local.
He hasn't had time to become familiar
with the renewed FC after his hiatus.
But all I can do now is believe in the super driving
sense from his days as Akagi's White Comet.
Ryosuke
Three years ago
Eh?
I fell in love with someone.
She was my senior by one year at college,
and a type of person I hadn't met before.
Free spirited, half childish, half mature.
Sometimes strong willed, but sometimes weak, a person with lots of contradictions.
But that's probably why I was attracted to her.
I lost my head over her to the
extent that I couldn't control myself.
It's out of character for me, I guess.
I haven't told anyone about this, but can
you bear with my little story, Matsumoto?
Cornering potential is equal, but my
car has significantly greater power.
As for braking, his car has the
advantage because of the lighter weight.
It will become more apparent
toward the end of the battle.
But that works fine for me.
If I can't stop, I won't be able to
avoid slamming my car into his.
There will only be one round.
If you manage to get away, you win.
But I won't let you.
Ryosuke
Why do you think you were born?
Have you ever thought about it, Ryosuke?
There you go again.
Another philosophical question.
Don't dodge my question, try to answer it.
What do you really want to do?
Do you really want to succeed your parents?
Are you attending college because
you actually want to become a doctor?
You can't be happy with that.
It's rather sad if you can't
choose what to do with your life.
You're hitting a sore spot, Kaori.
What makes you happy?
What makes you truly happy?
Don't you have a dream?
What is your dream, Ryosuke?
Any news?
I spotted the Grim Reaper's R32.
It'll pass by your location,
chasing a white car at high speed.
Please be very careful, Ikeda.
Got it.
I've finally got you, Grim Reaper.
Team Spiral is proud to be the
neighborhood watch of Hakone.
We won't forgive anyone who breaks
the rules of the mountain pass.
Your insolence ends today.
Anyway, who's driving that white FC?
How reckless of you to take the lead
position against the Grim Reaper.
He must have nerves of steel.
Could that be
him?!
Ryosuke, there's something I haven't told you yet.
I have a fiancé chosen by my parents.
I'll have to marry him in a few years.
That's a bad joke, Kaori.
Do you really want to
follow your parents wishes?
That's not like you at all.
You just don't know the true me.
Then I'll begin to discover it from now on.
I'm not going to give you up.
No
Please give up.
Why are you crying?
I'll protect you no matter what.
What's wrong, Ryosuke?
I see a slight hesitation in your corner entries.
Are you scared of this
super high speed stage?
Or is it because of your hiatus?
You're so naive, Ryosuke.
If you're spacing out, I'll wake you up.
He did it already.
Rear wheel drive cars are defenseless against that kind
of push right after the turn in when the car is unstable.
The Grim Reaper did it on purpose.
Please recover.
Wow, that was incredible.
That's more like it.
That was my way of saying "Hi."
I can control the car.
It's well tuned, as always, Matsumoto.
Now I know I can push myself
to the limit without hesitation.
Here comes the next one. It'll be harder.
The Grim Reaper is acting
differently from before.
He's seriously trying to...
He missed?!
The Grim Reaper's serious
attempt to crash was dodged.
What incredible acceleration.
There's no more doubt about that FC.
The charismatic driver, who was once
the best in northern Kanto, has returned.
What made him do that?
Ryosuke...
What's going on?
The Grim Reaper is acting strange,
showing true hostile intent.
The other guy is well aware of it,
but he isn't even trying to escape.
This is no ordinary battle.
It looks like I ran into
an extraordinary situation.
Just like you, Ryosuke.
Your earlier hesitation is gone.
You've got incredible adaptability.
You're a much better
driver than I expected.
Are you nearby, Kaori, watching us?
I dedicate this battle to you.
Even if I die here tonight, I won't regret it.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I'm sorry, Hojo.
I can't marry you.
Hold on, that's so abrupt. Tell me why.
This has nothing to do with
our parents arrangement.
Don't you know that I love you
from the bottom of my heart?
This is scary.
Their tension is off the scale.
I'm having a hard time keeping up with them,
much less cutting in between them.
Besides, that Takahashi Ryosuke,
I heard he was the logical type, but that's not true.
Only a genius could pull off this kind of driving.
It's almost a miracle for a
non local to maintain this high pace.
This course is so unique that even the
locals don't push themselves to the limit,
because you only have one life.
So fast.
His handling of the rotary
engine is almost an art.
So, even being known as the logical type, it's because he
has both the sense of a genius and an all too clever mind?
That's the true nature of Takahashi Ryosuke.
But the Grim Reaper will show his
truly frightening nature up ahead.
Ryosuke.
You're a mysterious person.
You're younger than me, but more
composed, which irritates me a bit.
But you're always honest,
kind and strong minded
the type of person who
can make a woman happy.
I'm not sure if I can be the one.
Maybe I don't deserve your feelings.
I wish I could
be by your side forever.
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.