"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
He pushed me from behind at a corner...
That punk did it again!
Darn...
I'll do it.
Duct tape or whatever,
I'll accept the challenge!
Takumi, wait up!
Takumi?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't let him drag you into it.
This whole thing is ridiculous!
Don't do it, Takumi!
I won't lose, no matter what.
"Act 14: Evolving Drift!"
Welcome!
Welcome! Come this way, please!
Regular or super unleaded?
Welcome!
Can I empty the ashtray for you?
What? Takumi is doing
the duct tape death match?
That's definitely not a good idea.
He snapped because of Itsuki.
I understand his feelings, but it's reckless.
Today is Saturday. Where is Takumi?
He's off today,
and Itsuki is in the hospital,
so we're short-handed.
I know Takumi is good,
but I don't know about
a duct tape death match.
After work, I'll go convince him not to do it.
We gotta make him stop.
Yeah.
Mind helping me out a little?
Welcome!
Without a sense of justice,
the world would be in darkness...
I can't blame Takumi for his choice.
No one can stop him now.
What if we let him?
No. It's too risky against an FF.
I was surprised. This is the
first time you've called me.
I've been upset about something.
I was thinking, and suddenly thought of you.
Somehow I felt relaxed...
I'm glad you called.
How is Itsuki, by the way?
He was wearing a seatbelt
and isn't as bad as he looks,
but they still have to do some more tests.
I should go see him.
He would be happy to see you.
"Souvenir"
You're scaring me a little today, Takumi.
Oh, sorry!
You seem different.
But I like you like this, too.
"Takahashi"
Hey, brother!
--What's wrong?
--The Eight-Six of Mount Akina
took the duct tape death match challenge
from the Night Kids' Number Two.
--What?
--His opponent is an EG6.
What's he thinking?
A duct tape death match is an FR killer.
It's common sense that it heavily favors an FF.
It's common sense...
...but he is racing.
When he races, common sense
goes out the window.
Should we check it out?
Hello...?
We're closing. The fried tofu is all sold out.
No, we didn't come for... is Takumi home?
Takumi?
He took the Eight-Six and left this afternoon.
No idea where he went.
Bunta... have you done a
duct tape death match before?
Yeah, a long time ago.
What if Takumi did it?
Takumi?
Well, he's still a beginner,
so he might end up going down the cliff.
Let's look other places, Iketani.
Yeah.
Sir, if he comes home,
please convince him not to do it.
Thank you very much.
A duct tape death match...
Let's get going, Shingo.
Yeah.
Don't worry, Eight-Six of Mount Akina.
The victory is 100% mine.
You'll end up at the bottom of the cliff.
I'll see you.
Call me, okay?
Sure.
Now...
A lot of people are here.
I was hoping for a small crowd.
After all, we came to talk him out of it.
Here come the Night Kids!
I only see you and your slow S13.
Where is the Eight-Six?
Ignore him.
I wonder where Takumi is?
It's almost time. He should
be here any minute.
Here comes the Eight-Six of Mount Akina!
Fujiwara Tofu Shop?
What is this?
Takumi, it's not too late.
Don't do this ridiculous race!
Why?
I won't lose to someone like him.
He drives an FF! Don't you know that?
Wait... you're the punk from the other night.
You wasted my time.
What are you babbling about?
I hope you're not discussing backing down.
Iketani, I'm doing this no matter what.
It's 10:00...
It's almost starting.
I believe in you, Takumi. You can win.
Please win!
Will he be okay?
Shouldn't we have stopped him by force?
All we can do now is believe in him.
It's set.
They've set up the finish line.
It's time to start.
Okay.
I'll count down! Ten seconds...
Eight... Seven... Six...
Five... Four...
Three... Two... One...
Go!
It's started...
Stay calm, Takumi.
Shingo purposely eased up on
the gas pedal to stay behind.
So that he can watch the
Eight-Six go down the cliff.
No human can drive an FR under
this rule without crashing it.
That Eight-Six won't last three corners.
Don't be cocky.
The B-16A engine is the best there is.
If I wanted, there's no way
I'd be behind a 4A-G engine at the start.
I just wanna see how many
corners you can clear.
But I wonder if he can really
make any of those corners?
Here they come!
Hey, isn't that Eight-Six coming in too fast?
This could get ugly.
Aren't you going slower than usual?
You're enthusiastic,
but aren't you forgetting something?
Here it goes... it's over.
I pulled it out. I'm lucky.
I thought I was gonna sprain my wrist.
He regained control!
Wow! I was sure he'd lost it.
I'm too old for this.
Hey, hey, what happened to your enthusiasm?
I can't just stand here.
Let's follow them!
I don't think so, Iketani...
With our skills, we won't catch up with them.
I'm not trying to catch up with them.
In case something bad happens to Takumi,
we can reach him quicker.
Hey, wait for me!
I'm getting the hang of this.
How is he...?
He continues to clear the
corners with little counter.
Unbelievable.
A duct tape death match
can't be mastered instantly.
The safer you try to go,
the deeper you sink-- just like an ant-lion trap.
I had to train myself for hours
before I finally mastered
cornering with my right hand
duct-taped to the wheel.
On a straight line, engine power is crucial.
No NA 10-6DOHC engine in the world
can out-perform the B-16A.
The sound of revving up to the red zone...
It's ecstasy! It's to die for!
You see? I can pass you whenever I want.
Maybe you should panic a little.
Let's get going!
"Skate Center"
My heart speeds up before each corner
with anticipation that the crushed Eight-Six
may suddenly appear.
Hey, don't say that!
I'm sure it'll end without any disaster...
Yeah, but...
...Takumi's abilities surprise me every time.
I can keep the speed up nicely...
It's faster not to steer
too much when cornering...
Darn, why?
He's unaffected by my pressure.
He was unstable at the beginning,
but he gets sharper as we go.
They'll be here soon.
It sounds like both are still in one piece.
If he couldn't reach this spot,
I'd be wrong about him.
That Eight-Six wouldn't be a worthy target.
There!
Oh, no! Someone is coming up!
He four-wheel drifted through one lane
without crossing the center line.
What technique!
He did it like it was nothing.
He didn't panic about passing by a car, either.
Is his hand really taped to the wheel?
Maybe it came off a long time ago.
Perhaps he adapted to the situation quickly.
You mean...
You can attack a corner
by shifting the weight without steering.
He learned that quickly.
He's unreal.
Without a doubt, he is evolving.
Darn, what a fake!
It'll be hard to label him
as a fake if he keeps that up.
But I'm not like Nakazato.
All I have to do is win, no matter what it takes.
Don't feel bad.
The Eight-Six of Mount Akina
will simply turn into metal junk.
Wow! After a spin, he turned 360 degrees
and started driving again
as if nothing ever happened.
He got lucky. Pure luck.
Darn, he would've been done
had it been a high-speed corner.
That's all right. The victory is mine anyway.
I hate that you're still going,
but I'm too familiar with
the rules to lose this race.
I'll leave you behind.
I'm pissed off! He did that on purpose.
I refuse to lose to scum like you!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irete nani ka wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
I won't forgive him...
I don't want to lose to him...
Is that you, Takumi?
I won't forgive him...
I don't want...
...to lose to him!
Anyhow...
Next on Initial D...
"Takumi's Fury!"
I won't lose...
Don't miss it!