"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
What the hell?!
I can't believe it.
Did I just see the ghost of a
street racer who died here?
The first counter-steer to the right
was actually a feint setup
for the next left corner.
That was the perfect drift
of a driver with ultimate
knowledge of this mountain pass.
Keisuke! Did you see that Eight-Six?
Yeah.
My pride is torn to shreds.
To think that the latest Touge
(mountain) Spec-tuned FD
could be defeated by some
ten-year-old beat-up Eight-Six.
What the hell is that Eight-Six?
"Act 2: Revenge! The Rumbling Turbo"
Hello. Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hey, Takumi! Takumi!
How late are you going to sleep?
Wake up and get the phone.
It's Itsuki, isn't it?
Just pick it up!
"Speed Dial" / "Hold"
Hey. What's up?
Takumi! Over here!
--Did I surprise you?
--Yes.
I answered the phone thinking it was Itsuki.
I've been wondering if it's all right
that maybe you and I could be friends again.
I didn't know we weren't...
We never had a fight, right?
You guys were talking about
cars at school yesterday, right?
Can you drive, Takumi?
Yeah. I just got my license.
Okay, then let's go for a drive
during summer vacation.
You do the driving,
and I'll make lunch for us.
That's all right, but...
...the car is used for business,
so it is pretty sad-looking.
I don't care about that.
It has a stereo, doesn't it?
I don't care what kind of car it is.
I don't mind at all.
Really?
It will definitely be fun.
I'm excited about it.
"Awano Souvenir Shop"
If possible, let's drive somewhere far.
That's it! Let's go to the ocean!
It will be summer, so we can swim!
"Customer Parking"
"Kitamura"
No doubt about it. It's an Eight-Six.
I'd even bet on it.
The fastest downhill car on Mt. Akina...
...is the Eight-Six from the tofu shop.
This one?
"The fastest downhill machine"...
It looks like any ordinary Eight-Six.
An early GT-Apex model.
Totally stock, except for the fog lights.
There's no way this kind of car can
be faster than the latest machines.
What am I thinking,
searching all over for this car?
What the...?
Iketani!
Takumi?
What are you doing around here?
What? Is this your house?
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Yes.
What were you doing in front of my house?
Um, well...
I had some things to do,
and I just happened to pass by.
More importantly, Takumi...
You really don't know
anything about cars, do you?
Huh?
Yesterday, you said you didn't
know what an Eight-Six was, but...
...the car at your house is an Eight-Six.
What? Hold on a minute.
That's not an Eight-Six.
I'm pretty sure it says "Trueno" on the back.
Right. A Trueno is an Eight-Six.
The AE86 chassis Levin and Trueno
are also known as the "Eight-Six."
What?
What?! An Eight-Six at Takumi's house?!
Are you serious, Iketani?
Yes, I'm serious.
Takumi, you jerk!
Why did you keep it a secret?!
What could I do? I didn't even know.
If it's a Trueno, just say it's a Trueno.
You said it's an "Eight-Six,"
but normal people don't call it that.
Why, you...!
By the way, let's have a little talk.
Next Saturday, maybe you could
borrow the Eight-Six for a bit?
--Why?
--Isn't it obvious?
To go watch the Speed Stars
and Red Suns meet, of course!
Since yesterday's incident,
I'm really into the street racing scene!
Don't you want to see Akagi's
fastest drivers, the Takahashi Brothers?
Not really.
What?!
How can you say that?
Even to your own friend?!
I beg you...
Give me a ride in the
Eight-Six on Saturday, please?
Hey, you guys.
What are you standing around for?
A customer is waiting.
Yes, yes! I'm sorry!
Welcome!
You're putting on brand-new tires?
You must have spent a lot.
It's only the tires, but I need
high grip to reduce my times.
I'm also replacing the brake pads.
On the downhill, braking is crucial.
Will you run, Iketani?
Yes. I'll run the downhill.
I'll attack Akina's downhill
as if I've got a death wish.
Don't overdo it.
One mistake on the downhill can be fatal.
I understand.
I understand, but I have to
overdo it just a little bit...
...for the pride of our hometown.
That Eight-Six...
It hasn't appeared today, either.
Maybe the driver wasn't a local?
No, that's impossible. He was totally
familiar with this mountain.
I want to face him again.
If I don't get my revenge,
then I won't calm down!
Show yourself...
...Ghost of Akina.
I don't give a damn about the Speed Stars.
I came here to face you.
Wow! The one and only Drift King,
Keiichi Tsuchiya! I can't believe it!
It looks like he can control it
just by using the gas pedal.
Takumi...
Don't you wish we could go out
right now and drift just like this?
--Sure.
--Check out this drift! Awesome!
Sure.
Takumi...
Hey! You keep saying, "Sure. Sure."
Do you even know what drift is?
Sure, I know what drift is.
Well, then, can you tell us what it is?
In a curve...
Don't say "curve." It's not cool.
Street racers say "corner."
Okay, in a corner...
...you make the front tires slide
so that the car won't face the inside.
What?!
That's a good one, Takumi!
If the front tires are sliding,
that's called "understeer,"
which is totally uncool
and for people with no skill.
A true drift isn't in the front--
it's in the rear.
You're really funny.
--That was great, Takumi!
--It definitely was!
Iketani, you're the one
who doesn't understand.
While in the middle of a drift,
the car is basically understeering.
That was the highly advanced answer of those
who have mastered the four-wheel drift.
I'm impressed.
Customers are here! Get to work.
Yes, sir!
--Welcome!
An FD...
Could it be Keisuke Takahashi?
High octane, fill it up.
Yes, sir.
You're a real enthusiast.
I see. I thought I had seen
that S13 somewhere before...
The Speed Stars.
Can I ask you one thing?
You'd be the one who'd know...
Is there a ghost on Mt. Akina?
The ghost of a super fast Eight-Six.
Wow. Is he planning to fly with this?
Please don't joke around with me, sir.
The part about the ghost was a joke,
but it's a black-and-white panda Trueno.
On the outside, it's a normal Eight-Six...
...but inside, it's an incredible monster.
There's no way a local like
you doesn't know about it.
Well, fine then.
If that's your secret weapon
for this Saturday's meet,
then I just got my wish.
Tell the driver of that Eight-Six
that I won't lose to the same guy twice.
The reason I lost last time
is because I didn't know
the course and I got careless.
Thanks for coming.
Keisuke Takahashi lost?
What did he mean?
I don't know anything about such an Eight-Six.
Could it be...?
The Eight-Six I saw at Takumi's house
was a panda Trueno.
Was the boss telling the truth?
The fastest on the downhill
is still that Eight-Six?
"Green Shopping Street"
All right, that's it for today.
Isn't this a lot more than usual?
It's fine. Just don't spill any.
I know.
Your face is sleepy as usual, Takumi.
Sorry, but I was born with this face.
Don't forget the Eight-Six on Saturday.
I know. You're so persistent, Itsuki.
If I don't make sure about it,
you might back out on me.
Please, Saturday, come quickly!
I'm totally excited!
Hey, if both of us aim to become street racers,
maybe someday we'll be
known as the fastest on Akina.
I don't really care either way.
Well, even if you tried,
it'd be hopeless for you.
After seeing you scream in
the back seat of Iketani's car,
it's obvious you don't have an ounce of talent.
But I'm different!
I was a little bit scared,
but I was able to look at the
corner exit with my teeth clenched.
Even Iketani has faith in me!
He must think Takumi is hopeless,
but I have a bright future!
Huh? Takumi?
Takumi!
Takumi! Takumi, wait a second!
What's wrong with you? I know
you're jealous of my talent,
but aren't you being a bit cold?
I'm not...
And then Rumiko told my boyfriend
all about it. He got really mad!
I saw.
You like that kind of stuff?
Of course not!
It must be a crime to let them
make their skirts that short.
The school should make a new rule...
Lucky!
Good morning, Takumi!
Mogi?!
That's right. I have to talk
to you about something.
Come along, quickly!
What is this?! What the hell is going on here?!
What's wrong?
Well... I...
There's something I want to tell you.
What is it?
Well...
I...
I bought a new bathing suit!
It's totally cute.
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
Bingo.
I was so happy that I just had
to tell somebody about it!
Wanna see it? Are you
wondering what color it is?
You want to see it soon, right?
Well, I want to, but...
I'll let you see as much as you like
when we go to the ocean, okay?
Until then, just... you... wait... and... see.
How about this Sunday? Are you free?
Yes. I have a break from work.
Okay, it's decided. It's a promise.
A promise should never be broken.
There are only two kinds of people that I hate.
People who break their promises
and people who smoke.
Damn. It's too tough.
The corners that I never thought of as corners
are becoming more and more dreadful.
These corners that I am so familiar with
have now begun to show their fangs!
It's no use. Even if I push myself to the limit,
I can't cut my times down.
I thought that if I gave it more throttle,
I could cut my times down.
But it's not that simple.
Is this the limit of my technique?
There's no way I can compete with them.
Hello! Excuse me!
Hello?!
Excuse me!
I can hear you. Give me a minute.
Sure.
Welcome.
Is this the Eight-Six driver
and the fastest on Akina?
Is this the guy who defeated
Keisuke Takahashi's FD?
What do you want?
Sir?
Fried tofu, please.
Coming right up.
What am I doing?!
Um... I...
My name is Iketani,
and I'm with a street racing team
called the Akina Speed Stars.
The truth is, I heard this strange rumor
that the fastest downhill driver on Mt. Akina
is an Eight-Six driven by
the owner of a tofu shop.
I don't know who told you that, but it's not me.
Please don't play dumb!
I searched the whole city, and this is
the only tofu shop with an Eight-Six!
Here you go. 140 yen.
Thank you.
Well... I'm kind of in a tough situation.
Can you please listen to what I have to say?
What a bother. Right in
the middle of my work...
But you're not doing anything!
I'm the only customer here!
That was rude, saying something like that...
I'm sorry, but I'm desperate.
The truth is, a team called the Akagi Red Suns
challenged us to a time attack battle.
The Red Suns have some drivers
with awesome technique.
Nobody on our team can compete with them.
But since this is our mountain,
we definitely don't want to lose!
So what do you want me to do?
Mr. Fujiwara... Please teach me
how to tackle Mt. Akina.
That's an impossible request.
Please! Even just enough to make
me a tenth of a second faster!
I beg you!
I know how you feel,
but driving technique cannot be
improved in two or three days.
In order to make your car do what you want,
you have to think continuously
and practice on your own.
When I was actively racing,
I was tackling Akina even in my dreams.
Technique isn't something that can be taught.
It's something you find on your own.
Sorry... I can't help you.
Mr. Fujiwara, I'll be back again.
"Think continuously and
practice on your own..."
I've done that, but my times
haven't improved a bit.
Why not?!
Dammit! No matter how hard I try,
I just can't understand it!
I can't avoid it! Please! Get to the inside!
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irete nani ka wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
Okay, today's guest is the stubborn
owner of the Fujiwara Tofu Shop,
Mr. Bunta Fujiwara.
Mr. Bunta, according to your theory,
driving technique cannot be taught.
You must find it on your own, right?
--That was really cool. I was impressed.
--Thanks...
Well, can you please tell us
the next episode's highlights?
You should just wait and see.
Anyways, please look forward
to the next episode of Initial D!