"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
So you're off this week? No D expeditions?
That's right. It'll take a little
while to fix Keisuke's car,
so that plus time off comes
to an interval of one week.
That last Saitama trip seems
like it sure was a handful...
It really was.
They were a terrible bunch,
coating the course with oil and so on.
If you guys go out across the whole country,
you're bound to run into all sorts of types.
But I never thought someone would
attack us during our practice run.
It made me think we can
never let our guard down...
But you keep on winning!
I've started to feel kinda like,
"Of course Takumi's gonna win!"
Recently, he's lost a lot of
that newbie shine, huh?
Yeah, but the fact he's kept winning since
his first race has to weigh pretty heavy.
It's a lot of pressure.
With this latest race, I really thought
that Keisuke is an amazing person.
He refuses to give up, or...
No matter how impossible the situation seems,
for him, the only thing to do is race.
His tenacity ended up saving a
race everyone thought we'd lost.
He pulls everyone around him
into action, making them energized.
When I see that, I know I have
to work hard to keep up.
It's so much pressure...
Yeah, I guess so. I mean, you've made
it this far without having lost once.
That must be a heavy burden on you drivers.
We can't even imagine it, huh?
Yeah... "We"?!
Hey. Been waiting long?
No. What's with this FC?
It's my brother's car. He almost
never lets me borrow it, but...
I forced him to let me. Anyway, get in!
Okay!
"Act 18: Last Drive"
What do you wanna eat?
This is to thank you for before,
so whatever you want is on me.
You wanna take the Kan-Etsu
Expressway into Tokyo?
We could do that, but I don't
like places that are too busy.
If possible, I'd prefer Gunma to Tokyo.
You're okay with that?
Sure! After all, you have this car,
so rather than the big city with all the traffic,
it'd be better to go somewhere
we can have a relaxing drive.
Okay.
Wow, what an incredible view!
The cars look like ants!
I wonder which way the Kan-Etsu is...
Project D is done going to Saitama, right?
Where will you be heading to next?
--Ibaraki.
--Wow, you're going far!
I... It's okay, right?
I can keep going to support
you at your races, right?
You can ignore me if you want.
I won't get in the way.
I just want to watch! And...
And I could be helpful like
last time, even if it was a fluke...
I swear, you...
How can I put this? I don't know
if it's youth or innocence, but...
Once you've decided something,
there's no changing it, is there?
You're the type that can take
corners without hesitation,
not even knowing what lies ahead.
So the answer's "no"?
Enough about this. Let's talk after we eat.
I don't know about you, but I'm hungry.
Hello, Ryosuke? It's me.
We have an idea of how to address
all the FD's planned repairs.
I thought I'd let you know.
I see. Sorry for asking so much, Fumihiro.
No, no. Nothing of the sort.
This will result in a dramatic boost
of the FD's racing capabilities.
This is going to be a complete overhaul.
Yes. Going forward, we will
face a string of difficult races.
We have to make the burden on
the driver even a little lighter.
Okay. Tomorrow, Kenta and I will go
scout out the next course as planned.
Understood. Be careful, and come back safely.
Okay.
It doesn't seem real.
If someone we didn't know saw us, I bet
we'd look like a couple out on a date.
I've never known such happiness.
It's like being a rotary engine that
can keep running in the red zone!
So this is the feeling of the person
you like being right next to you.
I don't want to ruin this. It's my first true love!
Incredible... Being on the roads of Akagi
in my darling's passenger seat!
Even though he's running at a
slow pace, I can tell the difference.
It's ultra smooth...
Everything about him is on a different level!
This is incredible, too! When he shifts up,
you don't feel the change in G forces.
I've never seen anyone per form
such delicate clutchwork
while driving on a winding road!
This is what it's like to achieve
near mastery of driving techniques?
Your driving sure is incredible.
You think? It's not like I was really going at it.
Maybe that's what made it easier to tell.
You were completely at ease,
almost considerate toward
the clutch and gearbox.
It's not as if I'm always like that.
When I get serious and go on the offensive,
I can get sloppy, kick the clutch around...
Being out on the road and pushing our cars
to their limits puts a lot of stress on them.
That's why when driving normally, I've gotten
in the habit of treating them with more care.
Huh?
Oh, it's Keisuke!
This is unusual. He's brought a girl!
Who's that? Your girlfriend?
Shut yer hole! Where do you get off?
Get the hell out of here! Get goin'!
Jeez!
Up until I got my 4WD license,
I hung out with a pretty bad crowd.
I got into a lot of fights, rebelled against
my parents... I caused a lot of problems.
Looking back, I was just being an idiot.
But at the time, I didn't have any goals,
and every day I was bored and angry.
I understand. I know that feeling.
My parents gave up on me, but my brother
was the only one who knew how I felt.
Even now I can't forget...
That time, he took me in
this FC to Mount Akagi.
Suddenly, he opened her up
full-throttle on the downhill.
It was such a shock. I really
thought we were done for!
I totally thought he was taking his no-good
younger brother with him, killing us both.
It's been three years since then.
I still don't think I've beaten the downhill
my brother showed me that day.
Huh?! You're joking, right?
Is your brother that good?
I guess so.
Anyway, since then,
my life's completely changed.
I can't even imagine a life without cars in it.
Wow...
So here's the thing. To go back to what
we were talking about before dinner,
this time I'll say it clearly.
I'm sorry... but I can't date anyone right now.
Please don't come see me anymore.
I... From the start, I didn't
expect that you'd date me.
I'm fine knowing you don't feel the way I do.
I've come out to watch you
on my own, because I want to.
You're so cruel, Keisuke. Why do
you suddenly have to be so cold?
You've been kind to me all day.
You let me ride in your passenger seat...
You even told me so many
personal things about yourself!
I thought we'd gotten closer than before.
I was so happy, but now...!
It's not as if I hate you.
But until Project D finishes,
I won't date anyone.
That's what I've decided.
Unless I focus all my energy,
and push myself to the very limit,
I feel I won't be worthy
to be one of D's drivers.
I understand that! I know
how important Project D is!
That's why I do my best,
trying not to interfere in any way.
That's still not good enough?
Even just watching you from afar?
You know, when you say something
like that, I just don't understand.
You're fine just watching? I don't get it.
If I like someone, I want
every last part of them.
Some wishy-washy, half-assed feeling
is painful and unacceptable.
You're the same, aren't you?
The truth is, you understand this, right?
You're like me, the type who can't
stand something that's not 100%.
Our upcoming expeditions during the summer
are going to get more and more intense.
I won't have time to spend with you.
I'm saying this because I know things would
only get harder and more painful for you.
I do think you're cute, but I
don't intend to date anyone.
Please understand.
I have a favor to ask. Now that it's over...
Now that it's over, I want to be in your
passenger seat and see you go full-throttle.
Please!
All right.
Girls call it sugar, like, so thick and rich
Guys call it tiger, a sense
of oneness never before felt
As I thought, he's incredible.
It's completely different
from how he ran before!
Girls call it sugar, that cool instant
We still imagine the circle
Incredible... You're incredible, darling!
Planet rise and march in a circle
We still imagine the circle
Is this... Is this really the end?
No, it can't be! Not that!
Planet rise and march in a circle
Before I knew it, night's curtain
had fallen, and I'd come here
There isn't another man like him. He's special!
I hesitated but I came,
it's frightening but it's nice
I... I don't think I can ever fall in love again.
With only my dreams illuminated,
I trust what my hand has touched
Because... There's no way I'd meet
anyone better than my darling!
Come, let's go to that
greatest stage together...
Here we are
We kiss and pass the red light
and drive in affection
Bless to be here
We dream right by your side in each direction
}Guys call it tiger, a sense
of oneness never before felt
Girls call it sugar
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
So? How's Takumi been since then?
Does it look like he'll find something
to pull him out of his slump?
Yeah, I dunno.
He's certainly headed in
sorta the right direction, but...
The way his eyes look
when he gets outta the car
after finishin' his delivery has changed.
Oh?
The thing about him, Yuichi...
Every mornin', he does a real
tough race on the Akina downhill.
Huh? Against who?
His other self.
His other self?
Yeah...
When he drives the Eight-Six, he races
all-out to catch up to an imaginary Impreza.
And when he drives the Impreza, he tries
his hardest to outrun a pursuin' Eight-Six.
Huh.
Knowin' the course as well as he does,
he's fully aware of how each car differs.
For example, the difference in KPH
from one corner to the next in either car.
With his degree of sensitivity...
Yeah, I could see that.
Do that enough times, and you
can sorta learn in long areas
how many seconds or how many meters
difference there'll be between 'em.
He should have a pretty precise
understandin' of those things.
In the Eight-Six, he probably has a clear
image of the Impreza in his windshield
as it takes off ahead.
It's so hot! Summer's here again, huh?
Yup. Actually, it was just about
this time last year, wasn't it?
The battle with the Red Suns...
Yeah, that's right.
That's where everything started.
The legend of Akina's Eight-Six downhiller.
That year's gone by in a flash, huh?
In just one year,
Takumi's climbed so friggin' high!
Yup, talk about a world of
difference between the two of you.
Anyway, this time of year
is just too much, huh?
It makes you wanna go out and
blow off your youthful energy!
I want a love so hot it burns!!
That's pretty incredible, huh?
Even at the pro level, you won't find
many drivers who go racing every day!
So if he practices that hard, hasn't he
closed the gap a bit between the two cars?
Is that what you think?
Yeah.
The thing is, just think about it.
Say one day Takumi's in the Eight-Six
and he makes some new discovery,
a different line than he's used up till now
that makes 'im a couple milliseconds faster.
But the next day, he's able to run
that same line in the Impreza.
Th-That's rough...
So he keeps trying to catch an opponent
that can't be caught, no matter what?
Before, the Eight-Six was
the absolute standard for him...
But havin' that one standard become two
will have a world of meanin' to him.
How can I put it?
To exaggerate a bit, his entire view
on drivin' techniques will change...
As if the line connectin'
two points will be dotted
with an endless number of other points.
Huh...
His reasonin' skills will improve.
More and more, he'll understand
things that up till now he hasn't.
You get enough knowledge and experience,
that leads to confidence and technique.
That's the route Takumi's taken to get here.
And of course, what he'll do goin' forward.
Awesome, awesome!
With this setup, I won't lose to a
Lancer Evo or a GTR or anything!
Incredible...
The car's underbody and power output should
be quite different from the previous setup...
He's instantly able to exert this level of control?
You've really gotten good at
controlling the accelerator, Keisuke.
It feels great.
There's plenty of horsepower...
And the torque really kicks in at
mid-level RPMs, making it easy to drive.
This thing's high-speed cornering
has really gotten great.
I think it's because of the wide body,
but this wing is really effective, too.
Corners I couldn't open up the
accelerator on when oversteering
are now totally stable.
With this, I don't have to fear any opponent!
I'll bet more and more races on cornering!
The timing couldn't be better, eh?
According to Ryosuke, your next
opponent will be your toughest one yet.
Huh. Even tougher than the Toudou School?
Yeah. So it seems.
I look forward to it, what kind of racer he'll be.
I was just thinking I'd like to get
into a good, solid scuffle of a race.
The Saitama area was pretty much
a string of small-time opponents.
That being said, there were
some good moments for me.
I was able to tackle some of my
assigned tasks at a leisurely pace.
Yeah. I guess we could
think of the Saitama area
as being a training stage for
you to improve your skills.
As I see it, there's no doubt
that you've gotten much better.
I guess. Even I think I've come quite a ways.
To me, the expedition wasn't too exciting,
but it was rich in content. I won't forget it.
I see. Then I'm glad.
Say, Fumihiro...
Do you think my brother calculates all
this when deciding where we go next?
Probably.
All of Ryosuke's decisions
have a reason behind them.
I wonder if, to my brother, Fujiwara
and I are still just babes-in-arms.
Don't worry about that sort of thing.
Yeah...
It can be vexing, but I've got myself
one heck of an older brother.
Our next expedition will be Ibaraki, huh?
Yes. I've already taken a look.
No matter who I face, I don't think I'll lose.
With this, I'll race so fast it'll
make my brother's head spin!
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte