"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
"Yamada Trading"
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Takumi! You awake?
Yes, I'm awake.
You all right?
Yeah.
Huh? That sound...
What the heck is this?
Quit spacin' out and get on with the deliveries.
You'll be drivin' this today. You'll use this
and the Eight-Six, switchin' each day.
Hey, you listenin'?
There's no doubt about it.
This color, this rear wing...
So that's what it was!
Dammit! I should've known!
Why didn't I notice sooner?
If I'd thought about it, on the Akina downhill,
that kind of crazy, idiotic,
no-good, shameful but fast driving
could only have been done by one person!
Sorry, kid, but you're about
to go through a bit of a slump.
Unless you can get through it,
you'll never get to what's beyond.
Incredible...
Pops, you asshole. What about this
car is "practical and easy to drive"?
More to the point, this really sucks.
What am I gonna do about this?
"Act 14: Sad Lonely Driver"
A Cappuccino? With a yellow license plate?
Yeah, it surprised us, too!
Still, D's enemies come up with some
surprising twists of their own, huh?
That was a pretty good idea.
A minicar would be
unbelievably fast on the downhill.
Be that as it may,
Takumi still ended up winning.
As good as Takumi is now,
I wonder if there are any drivers
out there who can beat him!
What are you talking about?
It's a big world out there.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop (Private Vehicle)"
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
No matter where you go,
there's always someone better.
But Boss, Takumi's getting better and better!
He's really incredible! Right?
You said it. Since entering Project D,
he's come so far so quickly!
Makes me miss the old Takumi,
who knew nothing about cars
and used to space out all the time.
Last night, standing off a bit
and watching Takumi talk like old
friends with Ryosuke Takahashi,
it made me a little sad.
Like he'd become someone
so far away from us...
That's just all in your head, don't you think?
Seems to me that right now,
he's still close at hand.
Ah, it's Takumi!
Speak of the devil, huh?
You on your way back from work?
Itsuki had the early shift, so he's already gone.
No, uh...
It's something else, sir. My dad
bought a new car. Did you know?
Yeah, I know. An Impreza, right?
Oh, so you knew?
--For real?
--An Impreza?!
Stupid old man, pissing me off as always!
Why suddenly spring this only on me?
So did you take it for a spin?
I drove it this morning, yes.
How was it?
I'll tell you how it was. For me,
it was like being in a flying saucer.
A flying saucer?
What does that even mean?!
It had such a powerful impact...
Up till now, I've driven
without even thinking about it.
But now, all of a sudden... it's like I don't
know how to drive the Eight-Six anymore.
Hold on now! What's that supposed to mean?
I think you know how to drive
the Eight-Six better than anyone!
That's right!
I... I don't really know how to put it...
I still know how to drive it,
but I've lost my self-confidence.
I feel so confused, even panicky.
"Open 24 Hours"
Sorry, Itsuki. Making you drive
all the way out here to Saitama...
Nah, it's a lot closer from
Shibukawa to here than I thought!
If you think about it,
Saitama and Gunma are neighbors!
A bit of a trip on the trains, maybe,
but close by if you're in a car.
Really? Then I'm glad.
So don't you hesitate to call me
any time! I'm always free at night.
I'll come out here lickety-split!
Itsuki, don't you have a girlfriend?
No, of course I don't...
K-Kazumi!
You have a boyfriend?
I...
Unfortunately, no.
For real?! I'm so glad!
N-No! I mean, uh, I don't mean
anything weird by that!
Sorry, gotta c-calm myself...
You haven't changed at all, Itsuki.
I get that all the time. "You aren't
makin' any progress at all."
No, that's not what I meant.
You're probably the type who
can't keep things hidden, huh?
I get that a lot, too. What I
think goes straight to my face.
I think that's a good thing. Like there
are no secret agendas or anything.
It feels comfortable to be around you.
Uh, well, I've always been like this.
I don't really get it myself!
Thank you very much!
Anyway, I still don't really understand.
For someone with Takumi's skills,
it shouldn't be that hard to get as good
at four-wheel drive as he has at rear-wheel.
Maybe he's talking on a level that's
impossible for us to understand.
There's only one thing I do know:
Bunta's curriculum of training and driving
techniques has just entered a new phase.
Say, Kazumi...
Do you mind if we swing by the pass where
Takumi and Wataru raced the other day?
I'd like to race that course in my own car.
Sure. But that one's pretty difficult.
Yup. And challenging it is what makes a man!
This takes a lot of steering work...
I can't really tell where the lines are!
Wow! Sure enough, that's turbo tuning for you!
And sudden turbo boosts. This reminds me
of how my brother's Levin used to run.
This is hard... It's so different from Akina.
I couldn't run it at all.
You say that, but you've really gotten good!
I feel safe riding next to you.
Yeah, well! I've been practicing a lot!
My turbo's got its own quirks,
so I've gotta practice.
Dammit! It's no good...
Takumi? He said that?
Huh. You don't say.
Don't give me that "You don't say."
What are you planning this time?
Yeah, well... That's a long story,
so I'll leave out the specifics.
The point is, I'm gonna have him experience
the awesome capabilities of more modern cars.
You're doing that now? Takumi's already
done plenty of racing against modern cars.
Yeah, but he doesn't know them.
As a driver, he's specialized
only in the Eight-Six.
He says he doesn't know how
to drive the Eight-Six anymore...
But the truth is, that shouldn't be the case.
Meaning?
It's not the driving of it, but the
Eight-Six itself he's lost hope in,
but he doesn't wanna acknowledge that,
so he's just comin' up with excuses.
Still, this is just as I'd planned.
Hey, don't tell me you're trying to force
him from the Eight-Six to the Impreza!
I wouldn't do that. That's my car.
I think this is gonna take a bit of time.
But he's gonna have to work through it.
Mogi...
I wonder what she's doing these days.
I bet she's not lonely at all, though.
I've been so busy and stressed out with D
that it's like I've been charging forward
with no time to think of anything else.
I wonder if I'm losing steam.
I sure am thinking about her a lot.
Why do I feel this lonely?
Up to this point, it's not all that different...
But here!
This is where it all changes.
I can't believe it! Even in the rain...
...there's such a sense of stability.
So this cousin of mine living in Higashi
Matsuyama drives this silver Altezza
and let me drive it one time,
and it's such an awesome car!
An Altezza, huh? Sure is.
Huh? Aren't you going to answer?
No, it's nothing important.
Hm! She doesn't want anyone
to butt in on our private date!
Hey, goddammit!
How long're you gonna keep us waitin'?!
Move your ass, register boy!
I'm very sorry for the wait, sir.
Um, will this be all together or...
We're payin' separate, of course, dipshit!
Those guys just now drive Lancer Evos...
Say, Itsuki.
Will you let me drive your Levin a little bit?
I have a license but no car, so if I don't
get behind the wheel once in a while,
I'm worried I'll forget how to drive.
Sure thing. Of course!
I can be your coach!
What do I do?
How can I race so that this
car won't lose to my dad's?
The more I drive, the more I don't know.
What a screwup. How many years
has it been since I've spun out?
No matter how I look at it, it's no use.
The Eight-Six can't beat that car.
I thought I'd been giving it my all up till now,
but I'll have to go one step further.
I'm going to have to squeeze every
ounce out of this car's potential.
If I can't, then I don't have what it
takes to be a driver in Project D.
You again? If you're looking
for Kazumi, she's not here.
Oh, really? Do you mind if I wait?
I have to meet with her...
speak with her one more time.
Otherwise, I think this regret
will never go away.
"Tea""Boxed Lunches"
"Sweets Fair""Original Cakes"
Huh? It's my brother.
Hello?
Do you know what kind of a position
that puts me in? Just say, "Leave."
I don't care. I'm hanging up now.
What is it? Is everything all right at home?
Oh, it's nothing.
Unbelievable. Itsuki's been
on a date since this morning...
...but I have to go out on a
Saturday drive with your ass.
Yeah, back at you.
What is it?
At that convenience store just now,
wasn't that Itsuki's Levin?
The little bugger's going on a date
around here, is he? All right!
Something seems a little off.
Yeah, kind of awkward somehow.
What do you say we head back?
I can take you most of the way there.
I...
I don't want to go home tonight.
D-Did you hear that just now, Iketani?!
It can't be! The line that
every man wants to hear!
Hey, Iketani!
She doesn't want to go home?! So that means...
Oh! Her face, so deep in thought...
It must be that!
S-So right now, you and me...
Let's go get a room!!
Shock and awe!!
H-He said it!
There's no way it could
go that smoothly, though.
There's gotta be some turn of--
Okay.
Hey! Hey, pull yourself together, Iketani!
But...
Before we do, there's
something I want to tell you.
Not here. Let's go over there.
Um, I'll be honest...
I was dating someone up
until about a month ago.
I think I still haven't gotten over him.
But going forward, you and I can get closer,
and I think I can forget about that other guy.
If you can accept that...
...then I can be with you.
Um, when you said you were "dating" him,
I guess you two got rooms in hotels and stuff.
I'd like to ask one more thing.
About how many times?
Like, more than ten? Or maybe less?
Probably... more, I think.
Suck it up, Itsuki! I know it's
a shock, but hang in there!
Itsuki, do you hate me now?
N-No, I don't, but...
I finally found you.
Wataru.
Let's go, Itsuki. There's no
reason to stick around here.
Kazumi, wait. You can't just run away.
This has got nothing to do with you!
I'm sayin' I don't like cowards.
If you've got nothing to feel guilty about,
then don't go hangin' up on people!
Kazumi, won't you listen to what I have to say?
You can't suddenly say something like
that to me. Don't bother me anymore!
I want you to hear this.
I want to get back together.
There's a reason I've been
acting so indecisive toward you.
I wasn't confident.
I'm just a normal, plain old office worker.
Plus there's the age difference...
I thought there was no way
a young girl would want to hang
out with someone like me forever.
It'd just be a matter of
time before she left me...
So I acted like this was a game.
But that's not how I really feel.
Being away from you, I learned full
well how important you are to me.
Kazumi, I need you.
What the hell's with this guy?!
He shows up out of nowhere
and starts talking shit.
Right now, she and I are in love!
Itsuki...
What are you waiting for?
There's no reason to hold back.
Just go with how you feel.
Run to the chest of the
man you really care for!
Itsuki... Yeah, you're right.
Well, that backfired.
So lame!
What should we do, Kenji?
What do you mean, "What should we do?"
We can't go out and talk to him now, can we?
This is the time to act like a true friend.
Let's sneak out of here.
You're crying, huh, Itsuki?
I, too, know your pain!
Hi...
It's no good! Nothing I try works!
What the heck should I do?!
I don't understand anything anymore!
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte