"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Blastin' off to the wicked show,
splitting the air with that sputterin' noise
Let's go, ride that thing
to the throwdown party
Determination that never
backs down, the dogfight
I wanna feel the thrill of the
screams in the phat red zone
A brief flash, like a comet
The brightness lasts a second, but I don't care
Someday, I wanna tell of that
glimpse of precious scenery
Yes, right now it's a purely instinctual dogfight
If it's a thrilling dream
you're after, it's right here
A wind that shatters the heat haze, backfire
C'mon, throw away yesterday,
right now it's a rocket dance (Dogfight!)
If the wish you can't scream aloud hurts,
then hurry and come here
You're big time gambler
Foolishness is a beautiful contour
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Tha loud sound is everywhere
Sideswipe, a 5G heavyweight
Runnin' right to the line, a hair's breadth
between offense and defense
Ba-ba-baaam!
Yo, I can step on the gas for
an easy victory, I still got it
The feeling from yesterday's race...
It's still there inside me.
Granted I won, but...
...I think Ryosuke would have had an
easier time of it if he'd raced instead.
When I think about it that way, there's no
reason for me to even be on the team.
I have to get better and better!
Someone's coming up on me.
He's fast!
"Act 7: The 85's Raging Turbo"
He's really tailing me. What should I do?
Should I make way for him
or pick up the pace?
I don't feel like making way.
Not after everything yesterday.
Also...
This is the Akina downhill!
This guy's awesome!
A dangerous new challenger has just appeared.
What?!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
He's so fast!
This could be the most talented
racer I've ever met at Akina!
If this is how it's gonna be,
I'll just have to use my ace in
the hole and shake this guy off!
No way!
It's no good. If I can't
box him in using braking...
...then there's nothing at all I can do.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Pops?
Pops! You here?
I swear. Where the heck did he go?
Oh, Takumi!
You came by, eh?
Huh? Where's Itsuki?
He left work early to go get
his Eight-Five from the shop.
And tonight, he's already going to give his
Eight-Five turbo the ol' Akina shakedown.
Well, unfortunately for Itsuki,
simply installing a turbo
is nowhere near enough
to put him in my league.
Anyway, Takumi! That's awesome stuff!
You beat a pro racer, right?
That's an incredible feat!
Yeah...
It makes us proud, too.
It's like, the racer from Akina,
making his hometown look good!
Since joining D, Takumi's been
improving at incredible speed, huh?
I beat a pro. It already seems so distant...
Because I got beaten,
of all things, on the Akina downhill.
Who was that guy?
I've completely lost all confidence.
Have I really improved since joining D?
There he is!
Da-da-daa! The star of
today's event has arrived!
Yay!
It's so thrilling!
She's gotten fast, my Eight-Five!
You better watch out, Iketani. This could
turn out to be a pretty even match.
Yeah, right. It'll be no contest.
Did you see that, Takumi?!
That was a powerslide!
What a thrill! It's so awesome!!
Yes, okay, now chill out.
Another one's coming from behind.
Whoa! He tore right past
him on the straightaway!
He's so fast! What model car is it?
It can't be... The car from this morning?!
It's an S15 Silvia!
Oh, jeez. It's not the same one.
250 horsepower sure is fast!
Not that I care anything about that, of course.
It's kinda disappointing, huh?
Like a rabbit leaping past
two tortoises playing race...
Who're you calling a tortoise?!
Ow! That's not enough to go hitting me over!
Kenji!
A normal 3A-U engine
has 80 gross horsepower,
so 150 horses is almost
twice the original output!
Up till now, I'd never imagined you
could make your rear tires slide
by going full throttle on the uphill!
I'm so, so happy that I can't stand it!
I know the feeling. It really is a thrill
after your car's just been tuned, isn't it?
How was it, Takumi? The Eight-Five
turbo as seen from the passenger seat.
"How"? It was a strange feeling.
Its power output is different
from that of my car.
The 150 horses certainly felt powerful but...
Maybe it was because of the torque.
The turbo's acceleration
has more punch than the NA, even though
they both have the same horsepower.
But...
Having so much horsepower
gives it a stiff underbody.
It feels like the damper isn't working properly.
If you're going to make a car fast,
unless you get the pistons
to stroke a bit more smoothly,
it'll feel like you can't floor
the accelerator when cornering.
You might even go into a drift,
the smallest possible...
Uh, did I say something strange?
Did you hear that just now?
I heard it. I'm stunned...
It could well be just as you said, Takumi.
Itsuki's Eight-Five is a low ride with just
a knockoff damper and spring setup.
You've always been bad with machinery,
so it sure was a surprise to hear such
precise comments coming from your mouth.
You're a completely different
person from before. What a shocker!
Well, people change with their environment.
You've really come a long way, Takumi.
No, if the staff at Project D heard
me talk like that, they'd laugh at...
It's that guy from before!
Hey, sorry about earlier. If I spot a car
like that one, I just get all happy.
You guys are locals, right?
We came from Tokyo.
There aren't as many cars
racing here as I expected.
Yeah, I thought things would be livelier.
You don't see this every day! An SOHC engine.
This is a so-called "Eight-Five," eh?
And a turbo at that.
Look how uncluttered the engine area is.
In a way, it's like new!
Look at this. The intercooler's front-mounted!
Dangerous, man. As in, kaboom.
I wouldn't wanna ride this thing! Scary...
Hey, have you guys ever raced a circuit?
No. There aren't any nearby.
If you all are racers, then you
should be goin', don't you think?
I go to lots of race meets, and I've
run almost all the circuits in Kanto.
My car's tuned a lot stricter than
for just mountain road racing.
Hate to break it to you,
but I don't think this Eight-Five would
even place in a circuit time ranking.
Wh-What?!
Now look here. What kind of cars
we drive has nothing to do with you.
Put simply, you're being rude.
I don't know how much confidence
you have in your driving techniques,
but if you're simply going to pass cars with
less horsepower on an uphill straightaway,
that doesn't require any
technique at all, does it?
What's that supposed to mean?
You're trying to say the downhill is different?
You can take it to mean anything you like.
But we've had enough, and I wonder
if you'd please hurry up and leave.
Oh, really?
This doesn't look too good, huh?
He's just waiting till we start racing, isn't he?
I'm sure he's planning some
obvious ambush to race us.
This is no joke!
If he's gonna screw with us like that,
we can't just sit back and take it!
Yeah! Talking all that stupid talk...
There's no way we'll lose on the downhill!
That's right. Let's show him the
true power of the Gunma area!
Yeah!
Huh? Huh?!
Y-You want me to do it? I can't!
I'm just not up for it today.
True, we wouldn't want to force
the ace driver of Project D
to do some boring little race...
Yeah, I guess not.
All right, I'll do it!
This isn't like you, Iketani.
Such determination!
But in return...
Please. Let me use your insurance!
Insurance?
There's no way I'm gonna forgive those guys!
And after I tried to engage
them in friendly conversation...
I've gotta teach them a lesson!
Ah! They started racing!
Okay! We're going, too!
I don't care if it's the uphill or the downhill,
I've honed my skills at race
meets and on the circuit
and there's no way I'm gonna lose!
Hey! Sure enough, he came after us!
I'm feelin' the rush!
It's been a while since I've raced!
These local racers are
better than we thought, huh?
I guess. He's got pretty good
corner entry, this S13.
But beating him is gonna be a snap.
I've got confidence in my
driving techniques again!
I sure was fast, huh?
I think I was quite cool, too!
T-T-Takumi! I'm sorry to interrupt,
but do you mind if I ask you something?
Yeah, okay. What?
Do you think what that fat guy
in the S15 said is true,
that the Eight-Five turbo is hard to drive?
I don't know...
It's really different from the car I
always drive, which threw me at first.
It's just a matter of getting used to it, isn't it?
You should drive the way
that works with the car.
Incredible! This is no kind
of car handling that I know!
I don't think Iketani will be able to get away.
He has good corner entry at the
parts of the course he's used to,
but watching them from behind,
his opponent has more stability
when exiting, and good traction, too.
But there wouldn't be that much of a
difference from just racing techniques.
The big difference is in their cars' performance.
A-Are you really Takumi?!
He's grinding the gears too much!
This isn't the same Takumi! Definitely not!
This is bad. Iketani is going to be passed.
Are you serious?!
At the straight line just before the corner.
Dammit, it's no good!
Fool! It didn't take long to finish him off.
He can't keep up with me!
I've got circuit-use full braking!
A-Awesome, huh?
A full braking corner entry
taken at maximum speed.
There's definitely no way he could keep--!
H-He's right behind us!
He's got some nerve, driving just an S13!
If he thinks he can keep up with me,
he's sadly mistaken!
I can't keep up...
Unbelievable. It's just an Eight-Five!
I thought I'd pulled away, but...
...he's right up close!
My braking, honed on the circuit,
is losing to some racer who's
only done the mountain pass?!
This is impossible... It can't be!
There's no way this can be happening!
U-Um, if you look closely, the car
behind us isn't an S13 after--
Sorry, but...
...can you not talk to me for a
little while? I can't concentrate.
You're gonna do that, huh?
I am.
I've gotta concentrate 100%!
Not yet.
Not yet... Hold it...
Now!
Here we go! Ultimate technique:
Transcendent Ultra Superlative Braking!
--Oh, no!
--We're gonna crash!
Those guys sure got what
they deserved yesterday.
It's a good thing I had him
put me on his insurance...
That's right!
Anyway, Takumi has been getting
better and better since joining D, huh?
He's gotten, how can you put it?
Like, at different points,
he'll make the car move in ways
you wouldn't have thought possible.
And that Takumi, his face won't change a bit...
He just grips the wheel all cool and collected.
He's probably confident
that he's in complete control.
Seeing that, it makes you think
there's no way you'll ever see
Takumi lose on the downhill, huh?
You said it!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Masashi?
I'll take it. I like it.
Well, that's what I said at first,
but I was surprised when I actually drove it.
It really gets me, in a good way.
I'll get all the paperwork
and take it over later. See you.
And then we talk for like
three hours every night,
so my phone bills are all expensive!
We're so in love!
Hey! Are you listening, Kyoko?
Yes, I'm listening.
I swear, you were thinking
about cars again, right?
You'll never be able to get
yourself a boyfriend like that.
Until I find someone I really like,
I don't need a boyfriend.
Racing cars is a lot more fun
than hooking up with some guy
who happens to be available.
So... What kind of person are you after?
Ideally, someone whose ride
is a rotary engine like mine...
But he definitely has to be faster than me.
And he has to be cool,
even cooler than my lovely FD.
What the heck is that? You're
using a car as your standard?
I believe that one day I'll meet
him for sure... my darling!
Sorry about this, Keisuke.
Scouting the course is
supposed to be Kenta's job.
That's fine. I've got nothing else to do.
"Steep Curve"
"Road Info.
Drive with caution"
"Sadamine Touge
Barbecue Garden"
"Customer Parking" "Restaurant"
Looks like she's looking for something.
Maybe what we saw before?
'Scuse me.
Are you looking for a cell phone? A silver one?
Y-Yes, that's right.
We found it in a corner of the
parking lot a little while ago
and turned it in to the guys at the shop there.
U-Um, I...
I'm sort of clumsy and am always doing this.
I put it in the door's side pocket, and it
can fall out when I open the door.
I-I came here to race last night, so...
Um... Uh...
You should go get it soon.
O-Okay!
What is this feeling? I've got pins and needles.
It feels like I've been stuck by lightning.
Maybe I've met him...
My darling!
Hey, the coming of a new generation
Calling now for the arrival of a new era
How long are you going to
pretend you've forgotten?
(Tension that seems like it'll
rip my heart) This heartache...
Within those eyes,
something that can't be held back...
(Yeah, this image that won't let me go)
...stares intently at the night
Yes, the two who didn't even know how
to reach out and touch someone's
heart are already, from here...
(Hey, the coming of a new generation,
Check it, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Strike the sleeping dream awake
(Skillz enough to rend the night!)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
A risky tune that rocks the times
Blast my desire
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
break what you wanna break)