"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mata sagasou
Itsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Itai hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sura wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
"Act 6: Goodbye Eight-Six"
So, you think Takumi went to Akagi, huh?
Hi, boss.
We're not sure, but it's possible.
He was acting weird all day today.
Didn't someone from our team go to Akagi?
We can make some calls.
No. If he went there to battle
it out with the Evo III...
...it's too late.
I thought he was on a
hot date with you, Mogi!
What were you doing?!
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
It's not your fault.
Besides, we don't know for sure yet
if he's actually racing in Akagi.
Takumi...
I haven't lost yet.
He passed the Eight-Six!
This race is over.
No worries now.
Kyoichi is too careful to give up the lead.
Kyoichi took the lead.
You can't relax yet.
The Eight-Six will get stickier.
This race is far from over, Kyoichi.
Hey, I see them!
--The Evo III!
--The Emperor!
--What about the Eight-Six?
--There!
He picked up the pace again.
I get it.
Since he doesn't know this course,
he couldn't attack it at
full speed when leading.
But while trailing,
he can predict what's ahead
based on my movements.
With that piece of junk... I'm amazed.
Considering our acceleration gap,
he must be turning corners
much faster than I am.
Unbelievable. His control is miraculous.
Should I speed up now,
knowing it'll strain the tires?
Or should I wait until the next
straightaway to speed up?
Silly me! I already know the answer.
I won't change the pace.
It would be the height of folly for me to do that.
Perhaps that's how Seiji lost.
A top-notch racer controls tire strain.
I'll stick to the basics... to win this!
The gap isn't widening.
It's actually shortening.
What?
The Eight-Six is going faster
than he would in Akina.
That makes sense.
What do you mean, big brother?
The mid-section consists of a series
of mid-speed S-shaped corners.
In this section, they can only accelerate
for a fraction of a second
from one corner to the next.
Yeah.
The rest of the time is spent
struggling with the constant side G-force.
With the misfiring system, Kyoichi's Evo III
has unbeatable acceleration
coming out of corners.
So, the Eight-Six has to compensate
by entering corners at a higher speed.
Utilizing its lightweight body,
which is his only advantage,
he brakes at the last possible
moment before each corner
and uses the grip of all four tires
to achieve maximum cornering speed.
If the Eight-Six weren't like a part of his body
due to all his hours of practice,
he couldn't possibly achieve a
miraculous performance like this.
He hasn't given up yet, then.
He may be unable to grasp the
concept of giving up right now.
He is becoming one with the machine.
That's all.
Even if I shorten the gap at a corner,
he easily widens it on the straightaways!
That's the power differential.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
This is Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Yuichi, it's only you.
No, Takumi's not back yet.
What's going on tonight?
Everyone seems to be looking for him.
What? To Akagi?
I see.
I applaud you... for making it this far.
This is a real feat.
Later.
This is the moment.
The end of the S-turn section.
I can go full speed after the next corner.
My serious racing starts now.
It'll end fast.
His style has changed.
For the first time tonight,
I'll use this feint followed
by an aggressive drift
to declare my intention of winning this race!
It's not a long straightaway by any means,
but it's long enough to shake him off.
He's fast! I can't keep up!
Maybe this is it.
Can I catch up?
Or not?
In the racing world,
a blown engine means defeat.
But like I said earlier,
I didn't consider this a race.
Now you can accept the reality.
Your car is dead.
The engine is completely toasted.
Why don't you put your
Eight-Six to rest for good?
No matter how fast you can turn corners,
the difference between a fast
car and a slow car is too big.
We'll race again when you have a machine
capable of competing with me.
Is something wrong?
I did what I planned to do.
It was just for fun.
For fun?
It seemed too close for just fun.
Well, it wasn't even really fun.
The Eight-Six's engine blew up
before all the fun could start.
He blew his engine?! That idiot!
I think the Eight-Six lost.
Seriously?
The Red Suns are in shock.
He blew his engine.
The Evo III was too much for him.
Too much difference in power.
He was undefeated until now.
I'm shocked.
I knew he would win!
Challenging him with an Eight-Six
was suicide to begin with.
It's what was expected, but...
...I don't get it. I'm not satisfied.
Was I expecting something else...
...from that Eight-Six?
We'll save our race until the weekend.
I'm looking forward to it.
Enjoy your confidence while it lasts.
Because I'll destroy you, Ryosuke Takahashi,
and we, the Emperors, will conquer Gunma!
My precious...
My precious Eight-Six...
What?
Hey.
Dad!
Dad, I...
We'll talk later. First things first.
We'll tow the car.
What are you doing?
Stop staring and get in.
Yeah.
How did you find out?
About what happened, I mean.
I had a feeling.
--A feeling?
--Yeah.
--Hey, Dad?
--What?
I've been saving up,
and have about two million yen now.
Maybe it's not enough,
but I'll use that money to repair the engine.
You've got more than that.
You're richer than you think.
You've been delivering tofu since junior high.
I have a savings account in your name.
I sometimes borrow from it, though.
Then use that money, too!
I can't.
Is it that expensive?
How much will it cost?
It's not a monetary problem.
The engine can't be repaired.
The pin that connected the crankshaft
and the con-rod snapped,
and the loose con-rod punched
a huge hole in the block
from the inside.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't acted so irrationally...
That engine is finished.
We'll need to put in another one.
Another one?
Yeah.
Are you bringing in an
engine from another car?
Even if it could run again,
it would feel like a different car.
Isn't that engine special?
You put so much effort into building it,
so let's try to fix it.
We'll borrow money if we have to.
I'll donate all the money I make!
We aren't that poor.
Then why use another car's engine?
If I could...
If I could, I would fix it,
but it's beyond repair.
That engine is useless.
That's that.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Takumi isn't home yet.
I wonder what happened.
Something's wrong.
Takumi, you think...
...you're responsible for this, don't you?
You're wrong.
You just happened to be the one driving it.
It's not your fault.
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga atta
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa na yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Ai wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
Ima hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
Goodbye, Eight-Six.
Now the Evo III and the FC are racing in Akagi!
Next on Initial D: Second Stage...
--"Battle at Akagi!"
--"The Black and White Flash!"
Don't miss it!