"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
I see. No wonder the left rear felt light.
I couldn't maintain grip in the left corner,
and massively over steered.
Omiya
It can't be helped.
Luck is a part of the game, and I couldn't
have been more motivated today.
I've come to realize that the root of
my driving lies in the mountain passes.
You can't experience the sensation
of your head going blank on the circuit.
I'm happy that I could fight a real battle,
because it doesn't happen very often in life.
Man, I didn't expect Omiya
to lose to that Eight-Six kid.
He's quite mysterious.
Too bad he didn't go for a time trial.
By learning his actual time, we could
have analyzed his car's fighting potential
and figured out the kid's driving skills.
Our opponent isn't stupid.
Don't underestimate Takahashi Ryosuke.
Contact the guys scattered along
the course. We're heading home.
Did you hear who won, Kogashiwa?
Of course I did.
We should be happy,
because we get our chance.
I guess you can say that.
I have to pay back
Fujiwara Takumi of Project D.
In Kanagawa, I'll get revenge for
my humiliation on the Iroha Slopes.
Act 4  [ Fated Revenge Battle ]
We've been waiting for you!
Here comes the Ace!
Well... ummm...
Well then, let me, reporter Itsuki, interview Project D's
Fujiwara Takumi, who won his first battle in Kanagawa.
Hey, I don't like that kind of thing.
Well, Mr. Fujiwara,
tell us what's on your mind.
A full tank of high octane gas for cash.
You moron! So boring!
How can you keep your
tension so low all the time?
But I just came here for gas.
It can't be helped.
Geez, are you ready for the next battle?
Takumi, when is the second match in Kanagawa?
The week after next.
We've decided to have
an interval between each race.
That means you can
relax a bit next weekend.
More or less.
It's a little far, but we've
got to see Project D
I mean Takumi race at least once.
Good idea. If we can, I want to stay overnight so
we can watch their practice the day before the race.
We can visit Hakone's tourist spots and
go to a hot spring during the day time.
Hot spring, you said, Iketani?!
Bathing in a unisex hot spring?!
Not all hot springs are unisex.
That's every man's dream. Just a dream.
Ummm...
If you're coming, the sooner the better.
If we lose, there'll be no other chance.
Hey, don't jinx yourself.
Make sure you keep winning.
Geez
Hello, this is Matsumoto.
What's the matter, Ryosuke?
Actually, I have a favor to ask of you.
I'll do anything. Do you want a
super charger in the Eight-Six?
No, that's not it.
What, the FC?
Yeah.
But why your car?
I can't tell you yet, but
something is bothering me.
I see.
This is a separate matter from Project D,
so keep this between us for now.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
He will eventually show up, so long as
Hojo Gou is with the Sidewinder team.
I'm sure of it.
It's an unavoidable fate.
I can't run away from it.
Not because I'm the leader of Project D, but
because I'm a street racer, Takahashi Ryosuke.
Maybe it's time to put an end to
Kaori
What? You're off next weekend?
Yeah, sort of.
Really? For sure?
Then let's go to the beach, the beach!
But no overnight stay,
not even coming home late.
That's fine. We just have to
leave early in the morning.
You're so right. So we can go
to the beach for real then?
The beach... I haven't been
to one for a long time.
I bet there are tons of hot gals there.
I want to see gals in bathing suits.
Nobody says "gal" any more.
I've been bothered by something for a long time.
Like there was a time when it was perfectly
okay for school girls to walk around the city
wearing a uniform with a mini skirt
that kept flashing their panties.
Yes, there was.
Actually, some still do even today.
If you think about it,
that's really abnormal.
Even if they're ugly or have thick legs,
their skirts are way too revealing.
On top of that, nobody thought it was strange.
It must be some sort of mass hysteria.
I guess you have a point.
The same thing happens at the
pool or on the beach in summer.
Personally, girls in bathing
suits are erotic and sexy.
Oh, really?
Besides that, how come these creatures called women
aren't embarrassed looking like that in broad daylight?
Well, maybe because
everyone else does the same.
They're only supposed to appear like that to
a special someone in a dark private room!
I feel the same way, Iketani!
You do understand, huh?
In short, they're just jealous.
Maybe I should become a priest.
I hate this erotic world.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I always ask you to come to Saitama.
You don't have to worry about that.
This's incredible for us. Before, we
only chatted at a family restaurant.
But we've been together since this
morning and come all the way here.
Everything is a new record.
Right. This almost feels unreal.
Takumi looks pretty sharp these days.
Yeah, you're right.
He looks more manly.
He used to wear a poker face,
or more like some emotionless kid.
I think it's because of his confidence.
He's fulfilling his duty
as an ace of Project D.
He meets Takahashi Ryosuke's
expectations and gets results.
He did grow up.
There's no way we can do the same.
It must be tough, but also very happy.
About what?
To be a member of Project D.
I'm envious because he can maintain
the tension of aiming for one goal
by acting as part of a team
and joining forces with others.
It's not something everyone can do.
He shines so brightly to those
who spend their days aimlessly.
That brat took my Imp
because the A/C works better.
Thank you, Takumi. I still have
plenty of time before my curfew.
Good thing we didn't get
caught in a traffic jam.
Well then
Be careful on the way home, Takumi.
You too, Mika-chan.
Oh, Takumi, wait.
Umm, you see
Can you just call me "Mika,"
instead of "Mika-chan"?
Go ahead.
Mika.
Nice.
Call me that from now on. Bye.
The balance is better than expected.
Takahashi Ryosuke is quite a guy.
I don't have the ability to refine the suspension
settings like this in such a short period of time.
It can really go further with this
but probably not until the final step.
It can't be helped.
I guess I have to be prepared.
That'll be the last thing I can do for Takumi.
Man, this is awesome.
So it was a roll cage when you
said something about safety stuff.
The mood is totally different.
I feel strange. It's like
sitting inside a solid box.
The pace of modification seems faster lately.
I can tell that the Project D factory is devoted to the races in Kanagawa.
Finally, the second race in Kanagawa.
So where is it going to be held, Takumi?
Oh, I heard it's going to be Hakone.
Better!
Right on. Your adjustment
perfectly matches this course.
I can't lose to amateurs.
That said, Racing Team Katagiri's main
battlefield is the circuit, not the public roads.
Don't worry. It's impossible
to find a reason for me to lose.
I'll put an end to the glory
of Fujiwara Takumi, I mean...
of Akina's Eight-Six.
Their strength lies more
or less in their immaturity.
Immaturity, huh?
Yes. If you drive on the circuit, you get used to safety, and grow fearful of mountain passes.
It's natural because there are no escape zones,
and you don't know what's beyond the blind corner.
It's not a game for rational adults to play.
That's exactly what
I want to tell you, Kogashiwa.
Even though you know that, you're
still going to fight this ridiculous battle.
That means I'm still
immature to a certain extent.
This is my graduation ceremony.
I'll probably be scared of
mountain passes in a year or so.
But I can still engage in a reckless battle because my
sense of mountain pass driving hasn't gone numb.
I want to get revenge on that guy,
and graduate from the mountain pass.
Driving skills aren't important.
What matters is how
immature you can become.
I didn't notice this in the dark
at night, but Mt. Fuji looks so huge.
Is it bigger than Akagi?
Are you stupid? Fuji is the
biggest mountain in Japan.
That's right. Anyway, it makes me
realize that we are indeed in Hakone.
Hey guys, we didn't come
here for a school trip.
Eat breakfast now.
Okay!
Hey, Fumihiro, you sound
like a teacher on a field trip.
There they are. That's Project D.
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu
It's me.
Kogashiwa
You always call me out of the blue.
I'm ready, so let's get started.
Well then, could you pick
your position for the first run?
That's how we've been doing things.
It doesn't matter to me.
How about letting a coin decide?
Heads is for the local, which is me, to be the lead, and tails is for you.
Sure. That's fine.
Good.
Tails
It's decided. I'll be the chaser.
Alright, let's begin!
A race against your son again?
Right. This time around,
he will definitely win.
He's getting better than me
as he made his own decision to leave the public
road behind and entered the world of motor sports.
It's not something anyone can do.
His efforts brought him the chance.
Sounds wonderful.
What about your son?
Can he surpass you?
I'm starting the countdown!
Five
I'll get revenge for my loss on the Iroha Slopes.
Four
Three
Two
One
Go!
Alright, they're off!
Go, Kogashiwa!
Do you remember that MR-S driver, Kogashiwa?
Of course. The guy who got pumped
up against the Emperor's Sudo, right?
He drives a mid ship car very
well, thanks to his go kart skills.
Who'd have thought he'd
show up in a place like this?
Looks like this's going to
be another tough battle.
Keisuke's opponent is also
an active racer, a real athlete.
Right. Race car drivers
have a different sense of time.
They know how to shave it off very well.
If we were on a circuit,
our chances would be very slim
but the public roads are our stage, so
there's no need to flinch at our opponent's title.
We'll be able to win if each of
us carries out our job perfectly.
I didn't come here to lose a battle.
The car's improved.
No wonder it kept winning
in the northern Kanto area.
But it's no longer mysterious to me.
The turning ability is simply a matter of tire capacity and load balance
and acceleration is a balance
between power and weight.
You may be able to fool others, but not me.
If I don't make any mistakes, I can win.
I'll watch your progress in this first run, and finish you off in the second.
You divide this course into three
sections to build an overall strategy.
The upper section is wider for faster speed.
The middle part is a super slow section with continuous tight corners.
And the lower part is a middle speed section where you can
step on the gas even though the road is somewhat narrow.
Although circuit racers would
consider the entire course very slow.
The range of speed is
too low in mountain passes.
If the average speed was faster,
I could have gained a clear advantage.
But I won't use that as an excuse.
The last section is the decisive point.
If I were Fujiwara, I'd make my move there.
Can he do that against a pro?
He has to. This is when he
has to show his true potential.
I have this eerie feeling.
We might end up seeing it on this course.
See it, you mean...
Oh no, I'm not really
good with those things.
You idiot.
I never said you'd see a ghost.
Inner wheel lift? He's good.
But I doubt such artistic control
actually contributes to his speed.
Race car drivers don't play around.
Faster or not, that's all that matters.
My brother calls it the Fujiwara Zone
but it's not exactly the same
as the ones used by top athletes.
It's a phenomenon that only occurs
between Fujiwara and his Eight-Six.
What kind of phenomenon is it?
It's difficult to explain,
except for my brother.
I'm not so sure either.
But when I drive behind Fujiwara during practice,
there are moments that catch me off guard.
He pulls away for some
reason that I can't explain.
I thought it was like a mirage.
You never know when you'll get to see it.
But there's a Fujiwara Zone for sure.
He shows it when a certain
set of conditions are met.
What's important is the
unique rhythm of the course.
What was that? My mistake?
I can't let my guard down.
Remember, I lost to him once before.
Again? He pulled away at the exit.
Was it my mistake?
My strategy was not to make any.
What bothers me most is that I'm upset.
I might have gotten carried away by his pace.
A point where his rhythm changes?
Yes. From a rhythmic repetition of stepping
on the gas, then releasing it right away
to a rhythm of delaying the release a bit.
The two cars are right at that point.
That's where something might happen.
Something? What is it?
The peak of the Fujiwara Zone.
I've always wanted to ask you.
What exactly is it?
He didn't just start showing it recently,
he did it a long time ago.
When I raced against him on
Akina, I caught a glimpse of it.
I feel like it was refined after
he raced against Purple Shadow.
Simply put, it's his level
of training in the Eight-Six.
When it comes to Fujiwara, his level
is beyond our normal imagination.
It must be the result of his
abnormal practice environment.
You said he heard the voice of the
Eight-Six during the previous battle.
In the auto industry, they often use the phrase, "The driver and the car as one"
but in reality, no one can handle
one ton of metal as if it were their limbs.
But something like that happens
between Fujiwara and his Eight-Six.
He can use the best part of the tires just
when they begin to skid whenever he wants.
He can also freely switch between the
side for turning and the slide for acceleration.
As a result, what happens is that
the Eight-Six accelerates like a 4WD.
No way, that's not possible.
Of course it's not.
The Eight-Six is still a rear wheel drive car.
What I mean is that the Eight-Six maneuvers
so sharply that it creates such an illusion.
It's a huge shock to see it from behind,
especially to those who know what I mean.
Even if you enter a corner the same way,
he points his car to the exit a moment quicker
then he steps on the gas with zero
steering angle to accelerate earlier.
There is a moment when his driving style perfectly
matches the peaky characteristics of the car.
I can't completely explain it.
There are things even you can't explain?
There are.
Especially things like the performance
of Fujiwara and his Eight-Six
can't be explained by any theory.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.