"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Blastin' off to the wicked show,
splitting the air with that sputterin' noise
Let's go, ride that thing
to the throwdown party
Determination that never
backs down, the dogfight
I wanna feel the thrill of the
screams in the phat red zone
A brief flash, like a comet
The brightness lasts a second, but I don't care
Someday, I wanna tell of that
glimpse of precious scenery
Yes, right now it's a purely instinctual dogfight
If it's a thrilling dream
you're after, it's right here
A wind that shatters the heat haze, backfire
C'mon, throw away yesterday,
right now it's a rocket dance (Dogfight!)
If the wish you can't scream aloud hurts,
then hurry and come here
You're big time gambler
Foolishness is a beautiful contour
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Tha loud sound is everywhere
Sideswipe, a 5G heavyweight
Runnin' right to the line, a hair's breadth
between offense and defense
Ba-ba-baaam!
Yo, I can step on the gas for
an easy victory, I still got it
"Back / Forward / Cancel"
This is it!
Project D!
Awesome! They won again!
--It's a course record!
--Unbelievable, huh?
They keep winning races in enemy territory!
What's "Project D"?
You know Ryosuke Takahashi, right?
Oh! That super good-looking guy!
It's a special team he made
to go outside their prefecture.
They scout out a bunch of
challengers on the Internet
then post the results online.
They even write the names of
all the challengers and streets!
"Hakuen Momiji Line
Touge Tea House"
Will they really come?
It looks like the real deal, Tohru.
Supposedly they even showed up
at the Asagiri toll road the other day.
This'll be fun. I'll do the downhill.
I'll leave the uphill to your R34.
Yeah, that's what I'd planned on.
I don't know the caliber of guys
they've got in the Gunma area...
"Souvenirs"
...but if they think they
can look down on us,
then let's give 'em a lesson in pain!
"Act 1: Project D"
Huh? Tires again?
You just bought some the other day.
Those were just cheap ones.
The grip's no good.
I've gotta have a set I can
count on for timed races.
Come on, Naho.
It's like this!
When I get my summer bonus,
I'll pay ya back in a flash.
You spend too much money on your car.
You should think about the future
a little and save some money!
It's been six years since
we started going out,
but at this rate, we'll never
be able to get married!
Not this again.
I've heard this more times than I can count.
I keep telling you because
you still don't get it, right?!
Fine. If you're going to say it
like that, I'll lend it to you.
Really? Thanks!
But...
...on one condition.
Condition?
If you lose this next race,
you have to give up racing!
Wh-What?!
I mean it this time.
If you don't keep your promise,
I'll break up with you for real.
The feeling of new tires is the best!
I'm gonna win! Naho's important to me, but...
...there's no friggin' way
I'm gonna quit racing!
Tohru! They're here!
So they came, eh? Project D!
An FD and...
What's that?
An Eight-Six?
These guys are awesome!
They might be the real deal.
Hey Ryosuke, get up. We're here.
Please get up, Ryosuke.
Ryosuke!
Ryosuke has such incredible
concentration on anything he does.
He hasn't opened his eyes once
since we left Takasaki.
Big brother knows what
works most efficiently.
Sorry Matsumoto, but please
get me a bottle of cold water.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Hello. We're Project D, and we've
come from the Gunma area.
We're called Seven Star Leaf.
Our team mainly runs this course.
You'll be going up against us.
It will be a pleasure. I believe
you've already been informed,
but do you agree to let us have
this course tonight for training,
with the actual race being tomorrow?
Yeah, I heard. That's fine.
Far as I can see, you've only got
two cars, an FD and an Eight-Six.
Are those the only two you've got?
We're an expeditionary team.
We've cut down on the number
of cars to eliminate waste.
The Eight-Six handles downhill races...
...and the FD handles uphills.
They are the twin aces of our team.
Very well, with your
permission we'll now begin.
They're more polite than I expected.
It's sort of a letdown how
friendly they are, huh?
Racing with just two cars
is unexpected enough,
but what the heck are those
three minivans? A support team?
The Eight-Six's underbody
configuration will end up like this.
These guys aren't your normal team.
In a racing team, everyone races, right?
But having a support crew
tag along for just two cars...
They may be a team, but they're
more like traveling circuit racers.
I'm not gonna be fooled
by appearances, Atsuro!
What can these guys
possibly do in a single night?!
Our team's been active for two years.
At even a moderate guess,
we've run this a thousand times!
Support team or not,
it won't make a difference!
A race is between two drivers, right?!
In a battle between 1.6-liter cars,
there's no way I'll lose!
It's local pride!
You think I'm gonna be
beaten by some Eight-Six?
Understood. This is good.
Make it so that, as much as possible,
Fujiwara will voice his opinions
and be made to think for himself.
All right.
I believe he can't say
anything of importance yet,
but what is most crucial now
is that he be made to think.
Understood.
Have you watched the video?
Yes, about 40 times.
Then you should have the course in your head.
Run the first five times at about 70% speed.
There will be a slight difference
between the course as envisioned
and how it is when actually racing it.
Your first job will be to
adjust for that discrepancy.
Okay.
Keisuke, you understand as well, yes?
We don't pick up the pace
till this stage is completed.
Yeah, not to worry.
Very well. Go!
I'm headin' out, too. Once I do
up the tires, I'm good to go!
It's probably like Tohru said.
What can they do in a single night... right?
That's how we've gotta think.
We can ponder all kinds of stuff,
but in the end,
when racin' out on the course...
...all you can believe in are your
own driving skills and your car!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I'll be back.
Thank you very much!
You're in a rather good mood, Itsuki.
That I am, Mr. Iketani!
Because it's almost payday!
Oh, that's right.
It'll be your first paycheck since
becoming a full-time employee.
Sure enough, it's a different
feeling from working part-time!
It feels like I've become an adult!
And once you get your pay,
what will you spend it on?
That should be obvious.
I'm adding a turbo to my Eight-Five!
To your Eight-Five, huh?
As it is, my Eight-Five can already...
Vroom!
...pull ahead of that S13 of yours no problem!
I've already got an estimate on a loan!
Little by little, I'm getting closer
to realizing my dream!
It won't be long now before Akina's Eight-Five
becomes known in rumor as
the car of a legendary racer!
Listen to you!
I wanna be like Takumi, tearing
up the mountain pass in style!
Speaking of, I wonder what
Takumi's doing right now...
"Shibukawa Station North
Audible Traffic Signal"
There's something I've been
thinking about since last fall...
What is my dream?
I thought about it all through
the winter, and I finally realized it.
I like to ride cars, and I want
to be faster than anyone else...
That's why I'm going to join Ryosuke's team.
Let's definitely...
...see each other again, okay?
"Shibukawa Station"
Fujiwara.
Fujiwara!
Sir?
Spacing out as always.
You're done for today now, right?
Yes. I had the early shift, so...
Going on a date or something?
No, not really.
You're not, huh? For a youngster
like you, that's just depressing!
Scary...
There are no covers on the sides!
I heard about this from Ryosuke,
but this is the first time I've seen one so deep.
The roads in the Gunma area
generally have concrete covers.
We ran it at night yesterday,
so it didn't stand out,
but if we fell into that thing at full speed,
make no mistake,
our undersides would be toast.
Actually, Ryosuke said
something about this yesterday.
That how we tackle this ditch
would decide whether we win or lose.
Even saying something like that...
Maybe he just meant,
make sure you don't fall in.
Anyway...
A lot of the time, we don't get
what Ryosuke's thinking
right up till the very end. However...
In the end, it always turns
out the way Ryosuke said.
You can believe him.
A 1600 B6 bored up to 1800...
An installed high-comp piston,
raising the compression ratio,
a lowered flywheel weight
to increase response,
and finished off with four
throttle body sports injection...
Too awesome.
Combined with your driving technique,
this is the ultimate downhill B6, I'd say.
With this, there's no way I could lose! For sure!
"Beware of Brush Fires"
"Souvenirs"
Well then, Bunta, you're still
making Takumi do the deliveries?
Yeah. Nothin's changed from before.
You say that, but he's become
an upstanding young man.
He works afternoons now, right?
He doesn't complain about it or nothin', either.
He's doin' an even better job than before.
That "Project D" team looks like
it's been good motivation for him.
Yeah. He says they're unbeatable.
Apparently they're making
new records left and right.
Yeah, for now. But before long...
...they'll lose.
It's about to start! My heart's pounding.
How awesome is Project D gonna be?!
In any case, Seven Star Leaf
is gonna take the downhill.
There's no way that Tohru Suetsugu
will lose to some out-of-towner!
"Beware of Brush Fires"
He's goin' up against an Eight-Six, right?
That FD is a powerful machine,
but an Eight-Six is just so old!
At their request, we'll be
doing the downhill first.
Rather than a simultaneous start,
one driver will go first
with the other following.
They'll go in front on the first race.
I think you realize that if we
lose the first race, it's over.
It's good!
You can start at any time.
It may be an Eight-Six, but don't
let your guard down, Tohru.
That's definitely not an ordinary Eight-Six.
I know.
I don't care what kind of car the other guy has!
Right now, I'm gonna do
the best racing that I can!
Tohru!
Shinichi, hold your hand out.
You get it, right?
I'm shaking.
It's scary! The truth is, it's so
scary that I've got the jitters
and just wanna run away from here!
But at the same time, I'm happy.
I'm so happy I can't take it!
Do you know why?
I'm grateful to Project D.
You can be a racer for a long time
and almost never get to race
with this kinda incredible tension.
To me, today's race is the chance
of a lifetime to show my stuff!
As a representative of Seven Star Leaf,
I'll make damn sure I run a
good race, with no regrets!
That's the spirit, Tohru.
All right then, whaddya say
we get this thing started?!
Tohru Suetsugu. A pleasure.
I'm Takumi Fujiwara.
Wh-What is this feeling?!
I've never felt this way before!
I'm stunned... I'm so shocked I can't stand it!
Protect me... Naho!
Tohru! I was so blown away by
Tohru's downhill corner entry
that I joined this team. He's a
do-or-die kamikaze downhiller!
There's not a person out there who
can keep up with Tohru's downhill!
There's no way he's gonna lose
to some out-of-town Eight-Six!
Going first was the right choice for me.
If your rhythm gets thrown off,
the downhill can be deadly!
Be relaxed... Rather than winning or losing,
what's most important is that
you give everything you've got.
Compared to the Eight-Six,
the Roadster is even more compact,
its small size and weight
allowing for the nimble footwork
that is its greatest weapon!
And the downhill of its
driver Tohru Suetsugu will,
as I see it, bet everything
on high-speed corner entry.
It is an unrefined style.
Each and every corner will
be taken with an inertia drift.
It is a driving style in which everything begins
when cornering speed has been
taken almost as high as it can.
It could perhaps even be said
that his driving technique
was cultivated through the Roadster,
a car that lacks power.
Meaning that he and Fujiwara...
Yes. His is much like the relationship
between Fujiwara and the Eight-Six.
With just one exception.
Whoa! Awesome!
The crux of this course is the
area that appears at the end,
a continuous stretch where
the side ditches are uncovered.
Victory will rest upon the
strategy executed in that area.
About that, is there really
any action you can take
aside from just avoiding
those booby trap-like ditches?
There is.
I've already informed Fujiwara.
Without advanced load shift techniques,
it would be dangerous to attempt...
...but Fujiwara and Keisuke can do it.
For I have chosen them. They are...
...the twin aces of Project D!
Whoa, scary! Tohru's cornering
is as dangerous as ever!
Wh-What?!
Even so, that Eight-Six is keeping up with him!
That won't last long.
There ain't a guy out there who
doesn't scare at Tohru's cornering!
I wonder how far that guy can
keep up with Tohru's crazy downhill.
He definitely won't be able
to make it to the end!
I expected as much.
Till now, no one has been able
to keep up with me this far.
That's no normal Eight-Six,
there's no mistake about that...
But more than that, the problem
is the guy behind the wheel.
He's incredible...
Still, I don't feel like he's gaining on me.
It's probably taking everything
he's got just to keep up.
I can win this race!
If you try too hard to keep up,
whatever happens is on you!
If you value your life, then pull out!
What an incredibly forceful
approach! Dangerously so!
"Beware of Brush Fires"
Ryosuke, it looks like he
still hasn't closed the gap.
I know.
It's still to come. The fastest
downhiller in the Gunma area...
...shall bare his fangs!
Hey, the coming of a new generation
Calling now for the arrival of a new era
How long are you going to
pretend you've forgotten?
(Tension that seems like it'll
rip my heart) This heartache...
Within those eyes,
something that can't be held back...
(Yeah, this image that won't let me go)
...stares intently at the night
Yes, the two who didn't even know how
to reach out and touch someone's
heart are already, from here...
(Hey, the coming of a new generation,
Check it, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Strike the sleeping dream awake
(Skillz enough to rend the night!)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
A risky tune that rocks the times
Blast my desire
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
break what you wanna break)