"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Has it begun?
I don't know why,
but I've got goose bumps.
The Supra is a grand touring car, after all.
Generally speaking, it gives
off a race oriented feel
but its design approach is different
from a hardcore sports car like the FD.
Its weakness is its weight.
What you're trying to say is
when the FD and the Supra go head to head
in a mountain pass, the Supra will be inadequate.
So if the drivers skills are very close, it's
possible for an amateur to embarrass a pro.
That's the highlight of this battle.
He isn't falling behind, but
isn't gaining on me either.
I don't like that.
It really pisses me off.
Act 6  [ Keisuke's Pride ]
Their pace is much faster than expected.
I didn't expect them to be that fast.
Since the race so far has
been a high speed match
the physical condition of the
tires will determine the outcome.
The driver of the lead
FD must feel pressured
but Minagawa is the one
who's actually hard pressed.
I don't think he expected
the pace to be this fast.
The current deadlock must be Minagawa's
psychological attack for turning the situation around.
At the same time, it's the
last card Minagawa can deal.
Dammit.
Victory hinges on whether the
lead driver can endure it or not.
It's not my imagination,
he's slowly gaining on me.
The advantage I created
is narrowing bit by bit.
The guy behind me is
pretty frightening, Brother.
I feel like he's got one
more gear left to use.
Race car drivers are so incredible
and scary, that they give me the chills.
I'm counting on you, FD.
Your remaining strength is all I've got.
The goal is so close.
Don't get in a hurry, Keisuke.
Your opponent will put
incredible pressure on you.
Emotions mess up one's driving,
which can easily reverse the situation.
Believe in your car, and
the experience you've gained.
Show the proof of your growth.
Step on the gas harder.
What's wrong? Push harder.
Try to get away... more desperately.
Harder! Try harder to pull away!
Do it!
If you don't
I'll lose this battle.
I used up all the potential of my tires.
I can't fight another round.
The FD's superbly balanced lightweight body
and front mid engine can reduce its tire wear.
That'll decide the winner and loser.
Knowing that, Minagawa still put up a fight for his
pride as a man who lives in the world of speed.
The high speed race that resulted broke
the course record by a big margin.
Brother, pros are really incredible.
You just realized something so obvious?
More or less.
I have mixed feelings of joy and frustration.
I'm satisfied with myself for racing so well.
I've done everything I can for now.
But I can't explain how I lost
my advantage right near the end.
At least, I did my best to pull away,
and I was able to manage that pace.
Both of us were struggling with worn tires, so
how did he pick up the pace in that situation?
I was scared to death.
Do you know why, Brother?
Your opponent was a pro.
Racing drivers know everything
about speed at the limit.
Each driver has his own unique
technique they've learned from experience.
They know how to raise the bar even
higher when the situation calls for it.
Every driver is different, so I
can't explain what Minagawa did
but it probably has more
to do with his spirit than skills.
That's the territory of pros.
For now, you only need to
remember that it can happen.
Alright, let's head back to Gunma.
Kenta!
You drive car #2.
Alright! Let's get going!
Sheesh, I can't drive the way I imagined.
The tires are wearing
out differently lately.
You must be trying something new.
Yeah.
I tried to copy this thing called one hand
steering that I saw in a battle the other day.
That must be it.
What's that?
You only steer with the right hand,
with your left hand on the gearshift.
I had a race called a
duct tape death match last year
and the technique seems similar.
It's easy to do that with the Imp (Suby),
because it's got power steering and 4WD
so it's stable, and the
counter steering is minimized.
Sounds impressive for coming out of
your mouth. The practice is actually useful.
You might be able to cut down the waste.
You think so? I don't know
how that'd work, though.
If you can do the same with
the Eight-Six, that'll be great.
That's hard.
I can't do that, for now.
You hit the top.
Your hands hurt, don't they?
N-not really.
Such a bad liar.
They must hurt.
You just won't admit it.
I haven't got a clean hit.
I didn't know it was so difficult.
I'll take a break, so can
you demonstrate for me?
I guess I can.
But this iron isn't mine, it's a rental, so...
Mika is incredible.
I can tell, even if I don't
know anything about golf.
I saw the aura of a top class player.
Takumi isn't answering his phone.
I have a hunch that he's with Mika.
He chose a girl over his best friend?
It's unforgivable!
I'll punish him later.
You thought he wouldn't?
In any case, Takumi and
Mika are suited to each other.
Each has outstanding skills, so they
must be mutually attracted, or sympathetic.
It must be fate between a
dedicated and honest guy and girl.
Speaking of which,
I'm also dedicated and honest.
In other words,
talent makes the difference.
Did you really have fun playing golf?
I had a great time.
Just watching your
swing made me happy.
Really?
I thought you were incredible. I can tell.
Thank you.
Although lately I've lost
my confidence at times.
Oh, don't.
Just believe in yourself.
You'll become a top notch player.
I hope so.
I want to become a pro.
A-actually, I do, too.
My goal is to become a pro.
Really?
That's awesome.
Then we should compete
to see who makes their
dream come true first.
Team Spiral
Leader - Ikeda Ryuji (Zero)
Driver - Okuyama Hiroya (01)
So our turn has come, huh?
This's almost like a joke.
246 was out of the question, but I thought
Katagiri's drivers had a solid chance.
They had too much pride, especially Minagawa.
It can drag you down sometimes.
You think you can win?
Project D's Eight-Six is fast.
I'll win. I guarantee it!
There aren't any regulations,
so we can do anything, right?
If you try to compete in skills, you
could trip over your own naivety.
I had no intention of competing in
driving technique from the get go.
I'll just try to win.
You do understand.
This summer agitation will be over soon.
Hakone will quiet down.
As Okuyama said, Minagawa must have
lost because he tried to save face as a pro.
There's no need for
conditions to be equal.
We can beat our opponents
with superior vehicle potential.
When did he get there?
I don't know what kind of idiot he is,
but he's probably not one of the locals.
The locals wouldn't pick
a fight with Spiral's Zero.
I'll show you what I've got.
It can keep up with my car's power?
Wow, what was that?
They were totally in battle mode.
The red Z in front must be
Spiral's Zero, but the rear?
It was so fast that I couldn't see.
No, I know the car type
from its distinctive tail lights.
I have a bad feeling.
You mean it's?
He isn't falling behind.
It's amazing that he can
keep up with me at this pace.
This guy's definitely no ordinary driver.
He doesn't miss the braking zone.
That means he knows this course.
If you're a local, who are you?
This is ridiculous.
What the?!
God dammit!
That was so close.
Someone else would've ended up dead.
As far as I know, there's only
one person who plays dirty like that.
No doubt, he's come.
Dark silver R32, the Grim Reaper GT-R.
Apparently, the Grim Reaper has
been sighted a few times lately.
So it seems.
He left home long ago, so
I don't know what he's been doing.
I'm not interested, either.
But I can tell you one thing for sure.
His true target is Takahashi Ryosuke.
So that's the "bitter fate"?
He lost his girlfriend two years ago,
and he's been acting weird ever since.
He withdrew to his room, quit his job,
and stopped talking to the family.
How did Takahashi Ryosuke get involved, then?
Apparently, Ryosuke had a
crush on the same chick.
Her name was...
Kaori, I think.
You had to do that in
this high speed corner?!
She was foolish. Her suicide
screwed up the lives of the others.
I don't know what
happened between them
it's been fate ever since
they met in med school.
He's not the Grim Reaper himself
he's just a pathetic guy who wanders around
because he's possessed by the Grim Reaper.
He might be ready to die for real.
Incredible speed. Your speed is lethal.
I'll have to play wildly, or I'll be finished.
It's frustrating, but I have to quit for today.
I'll pay you back later, Grim Reaper.
Project D's third round in
Kanagawa finally begins tonight.
The boss didn't give us any days off,
so we can't see the race this time.
I guess both Itsuki and I trying to get
Saturday and Sunday off is too much to ask.
Project D is the enemy,
from Kanagawa's perspective.
I wish we could send as many people
as possible to support the Gunma team.
This time around, I hear lots of guys
saying they'd go, despite the distance.
Even so, we fellow Speed Stars members can't go. I don't know what to think of this.
For today, you should
just go by yourself.
Well, actually, I'd love to
but I'm kind of broke,
so I can't pay for the gas.
What the hell?
You're pathetic.
I've decided.
I'll watch the final race no
matter what the boss says.
Itsuki.
I bet the best of Kanagawa will appear.
Whether Takumi wins or loses
as his best friend, I must
see his race of a lifetime.
I don't care if I get fired.
I feel like I have to be there.
But if he loses this time,
there won't be another one.
He won't lose.
Takumi will never lose.
Okay, I got it, so don't cry, Itsuki.
I know how you feel.
Itsuki is right.
We've got to see the final race.
We have to see the end, no matter what.
I'm the team leader, Ikeda Ryuji.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Takahashi Ryosuke of Project D.
These are our drivers.
I'mTakahashi Keisuke.
I'm Fujiwara Takumi.
So you guys are Project D.
I have a favor, or more
like a question to ask.
Just tell me what
pops into your head.
What is driving to you?
Let me hear your answer.
Takahashi Keisuke, you go first.
In short, proof of masochism.
That's interesting.
How about you, Fujiwara?
To me, it's a daily activity,
like washing my face.
That's interesting, too.
And finally, you?
I'm not a driver here,
but should I answer?
I'd love to hear it.
A dream.
Okuyama didn't show up, after all.
As he puts it, he can't find any
reason to greet his opponent.
If that's how he raises
his motivation, that's fine.
Besides, Sakamoto, did you
sense anything from Project D?
Their presence gives me chills. It must
come from the momentum of continuous wins.
And yet, they aren't desperate,
or aggressive toward their opponent.
They're so calm that they look
more pro than the real ones.
I think you're right. Those three
are top notch public street racers.
This is the perfect stage to test my
Zero theory, which I've been advocating.
The key is to free yourself from
destruction before you begin the race.
I believe that the ideal driving style can be
achieved through a mental state of zero noise.
The air is moist, so it'll rain from dawn through
the day tomorrow, like the weather forecast said.
Wet conditions will probably benefit the
locals, because they know the course.
Generally, that would be true
but Team Spiral tends to
rely on their cars potential
so they probably don't like rain.
I originally thought Project D's Eight-Six
driver would have a tough time if it was dry.
Compared to Okuyama's car, the
difference in performance is just too big.
But in rain, it will equal out.
Plus, I can think of another
condition, besides the rain.
In that case, Okuyama won't be
able to defeat Project D's lad.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.