"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
Unbelievable!
"Act 24: The Never-ending Challenge"
"Skyline"
Five... Four... Three... Two... One...
Go!
The eighth round, eh?
I'd given it up for lost, but then...
Now I'm on the edge of my seat again!
The "blind attack" paired with a
variation of the gutter-drop, eh?
Even the great God Arm got taken by surprise.
And that's how his absolute
conviction was shattered...
Still, if Fujiwara knew he was going
to use the modified gutter-drop,
didn't he have the chance to spring it sooner?
Without being dragged along
as things got so intense...
You have it wrong.
The truth is, he wanted to use
it sooner, but was not allowed to.
He was controlled, at the will of his opponent,
with no chance at all to take the initiative.
Only after his tires had lost their grip
and he'd been driven to such dire straits
was he able to turn the tables.
Or rather, he was released from his "bonds."
I get it.
Going forward is where things get intense.
His opponent is not naive enough
to be fooled by the same trick twice.
This ain't good.
A war of attrition isn't in Jo's favor.
In terms of stamina, he's got
the short end of the stick.
But there's no way Mr. Joshima could lose...
Jo's a perfectionist.
He'll try to win "smart,"
by some plan he's thought up.
I just hope he hasn't lost his concentration
from things not going his way.
I'm still so confused...
Do I open it up full-throttle,
and attempt to outrun him?
It's a rather plain approach,
but it's the only one.
I'll show you one more thing before
weariness takes my concentration...
...the so-called record-line attack!
What round is this?
The seventh? No, the eighth.
I'll stay right on him, no matter what!
If I'm feeling the hurt, then so is he.
With things getting this complicated,
I worry about the Eight-Six
having mechanical problems.
All I can think about is
that it's hardly a new car...
You don't have to worry
about that. I guarantee it.
Enough time and money
have gone into maintaining it
that it could do ten or even twenty
full-speed downhill races without a hitch.
I hope so...
My one worry is the modified gutter-drop,
which uses the curbstone.
Unlike the gutters at Akina, the ones
here will place strain on the suspension,
so repeated drops are a bit scary.
I think Fujiwara is aware
of this as well, though.
But if that's his only way to win this...
Then in a clinch, he may use it again.
Whoa...
This is awesome!
I like how much power it's got.
Even I can tell how much
stability the 4WD adds.
Going from this to the Eight-Six,
I bet it'd be a bit discouraging.
I can see how Takumi would
get into a slump over it.
Now look...
Usin' some half-assed word like "slump"
means he's still just some kid.
For Takumi, the Eight Six and the Akina
run were the absolute standard.
It was a good environment for him to get
some basic techniques under his belt.
Well, yeah. What would take your
average guy five years to accomplish,
he's done in less than one.
Yeah.
And he's reached the next step, increasin'
the number of techniques to choose from.
Nothin' clear-cut, more like an
expansion on some basic fundamentals
is what he needs.
'Cause durin' a race, any one absolute
standard is gonna go bye-bye.
For example, there could be one ideal
racin' line you can draw on a map,
but in the real world, there're any
number of lines to choose from, right?
Yeah.
Put simply, a dogfight means tryin'
to screw up the other guy's line.
So long as you tear his down and stick to
your own, there's no way he can pass you.
True enough.
Bein' able to use any line...
now that's the real deal.
Just think of what I'm havin' Takumi do now
as a menu to develop the
skills to use his techniques.
Little by little, we're seein'
some definite results.
Compared to the old Takumi,
he's a completely different guy.
Takumi's developing at a
frighteningly fast pace, is he?
I guess. But...
He's still got a long way to go.
Incredible... Something is different
about this eighth round!
I never placed much importance
on racing lines for street races.
All I think about is using my tires to
the fullest and having a good race.
Through practicing the single-handed steer,
I noticed that if you fully utilize your tires,
then no matter what line you take,
it won't make much difference in racing time.
Following that thinking,
the resulting line is that which
most effectively uses the tires!
That's precisely what the "record line"is!
To me, the ideal racing line
is not to be sought.
It is nothing more than a result!
What I'm seeing is so incredible!
Part of being fast on the mountain pass
is being able to enter
corners without hesitation.
How well you know the course
is a vital element of this.
It is also a basic principle in the
theory of high-speed public racing.
It is for this reason
that practice is emphasized
during D's expeditions.
So... local drivers who've raced
the course for a long time
have an advantage?
Correct. Especially during races
between two drivers of great skill,
knowledge of the course will
ultimately become a weapon.
Then how will this race turn out?
It will be a battle of endurance.
He who can't endure will lose.
He's pulling away.
Why? What's causing the gap?
What's different?!
We're almost to the goal. At this rate, I'll lose!
The goal is just ahead.
If I maintain this distance...
Dammit! My concentration...
Just a little farther.
I have to do something.
Anything I can do, I'll do it!
I-I've done it now...
Did he miscalculate his speed
when crossing the curbside?
The suspension isn't working!
It's no good...
I lost!
I can't believe it.
To think you'd lose this way...
I'm real sorry.
Now, I'm not trying to make excuses,
but it got hot all of a sudden, right?
I lost my appetite, and started thinking,
maybe I'm just tired inside.
But vomiting while driving...
I still can't believe it myself.
Too bad you didn't puke
while headin' to the goal line.
It was just a little farther, y'know.
That wouldn't have been smart at all.
For one thing, I couldn't
maintain concentration.
The tiredness hit me all at once,
like a hole opening up in a dam.
You'd been racing for so long...
I didn't think it would be this drawn out.
I'd expected it to be over one round earlier.
This means the man they've called
a god is now just a middle-aged guy.
This is a bit of a handful.
We'll have to run an alignment
check once we're back in Gunma.
Does it look like it can be driven back?
It'll be fine so long as it runs at a normal speed.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so down.
The car will be soon repaired.
Yeah...
I was the one who instructed you to use
the curbside, though aware of the risk.
You may feel you've lost in
terms of driving techniques,
but the end result is, you won.
That may be so, but I...
This was a good learning experience.
The key point this time was the line.
Your perception of the racing
line has changed, hasn't it?
Don't forget this experience today.
You're still learning... developing.
Both you and Project D.
Now get some rest. With the
Eight-Six in this condition,
the timed race will consist solely
of Keisuke on the hillclimb.
All right.
Please, Keisuke. Set this course a new record!
Yeah.
Still, Fujiwara's luck at winning is such
that it cannot be explained through
mathematical probability theory.
When racing professional racer
Tomoyuki Tachi, and then tonight...
...he achieved miraculous victories.
He is a mysterious fellow.
Perhaps he was born having been
bestowed with a special something.
You all right?
Yeah. Somehow or other.
You'd seem to pretty much
have this in the bag.
I guess. Unfortunately,
the young'un from Gunma
won't be makin' any records
with that car of his.
The car I used for the timed race,
I could use that as-is even on the pro circuit.
Those can't exactly be called
fair conditions, can they?
If street racing had any regulations,
that'd clearly be against the rules.
Yeah, oh, well. After all, I lost the race...
I gotta have him let me
save some face in the end!
What about that downhill kid?
What if he hadn't busted his Eight-Six
and he could've run the timed race?
In that case... Hmm...
I think I could've come through.
Hey now, that doesn't sound very confident.
You're saying the course record
that you set with your S2000
could be beaten by an Eight-Six?
I can't scoff at the idea.
When it comes to the downhill,
that Eight-Six makes the grade.
His speed and concentration were
on a level beyond what I expected.
Just for a second, he got me to
grip the wheel with both hands.
I get it. He was that good
of an opponent, was he?
Such perfection at such a young age...
Frightening, isn't it?
--How is it?!
--No good.
Dammit! Even though he set new personal
bests on the second and third tries?!
No good, huh?
Let's give Mr. Toudou a thorough
report on what happened here.
Yeah. My body feels so
achy that I can't stand it.
I want to race him again!
"National Park"
"Touge View Park"
Too bad, huh?
It couldn't be helped.
Still, you ran a good race.
You mind if I say somethin'?
You're not the kind of driver
who should be here forever.
If you like, I can introduce
you to the right contacts.
I appreciate the offer, but there are
still things that I have to do here.
I see. Well, I can't force you.
See ya.
We're not ready yet.
There's room to get better and better.
Um...
Let me warn you, though, my style
is irregular and completely my own.
I don't know that a driver of your
level will learn anything from it.
Racing in the God Arm's passenger seat...
A pretty choice arrangement, no?
He consented readily and most agreeably.
Truth be told, I'd like to be
sitting in that seat myself.
Okay, shall we go?
Yes, please.
For Fujiwara, an experience this
valuable will almost never come along.
Simply being able to see the techniques
of Toshiya Joshima up close...
Yeah.
The two of them are a
remarkably similar type of driver.
Fujiwara no doubt made a dramatic impact...
What's incredible about the single-handed
steer isn't racing with one hand.
Keep a close eye out for why that is, Fujiwara.
D shall continue with its races...
Learn well what you see for
the challenging races to come.
Now, you must simply absorb what you need.
The day will come when it shall be of use.
--Not this...
--...situation...
...friggin' again?
I swear, you guys' love lives
are dead in the water.
Come on, Boss, don't say that.
When I was young, even I always
had a woman or two around.
Maybe one of us is giving off
a "Women stay back!" aura...
Could be.
Hey, why're you looking at me?!
Takumi!
They say you won again!
No... How can I put this? I guess it was a draw.
Just say it already! A win is a win!
Well, looking at the big picture,
I can't really say that...
You're in the Impreza today?
Where's the Eight-Six?
The underbody was damaged in
yesterday's race. It's still being fixed.
--So you're free today?!
--Yeah...
Then what do you say we do
a long overdue run together?
Right, Iketani? Kenji?
Yeah, that'd be great! Maybe I'll have
Takumi show me a thing or two!
Yeah.
We're all young and girlfriend-less,
so we should add Takumi to the ranks
and bam, do it up!
Honestly, four fine young men, and yet...
--...all so sadly lacking when it comes to women.
--By the way, where's Project D going to next?
I don't know. But no matter where we
go or who we face, I'll give it my all.
So cool!
No, not at all...
I got no impression
It's for my own sake.
This town is made by imitation
There are still so many things I have left to do.
Wanting your sensation
In this silly situation
I wanna rage my dream
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Is she fixed?
Yeah.
--As of last night.
--Huh.
I got no impression,
received too many feelings
Here.
that are shades of gray,
all throughout the town are imitations
Searching for what's real, you become excited
--I'll be back.
--Yeah.
Becoming hotter the farther from it you get
Feel your frustration, your scream...
Say what you will, he sure does like it.
Racing with that thing.
Taste your vibration,
I feel it so much that I shiver
Rage your dream, race past time
Even the wind will brim forth with light
No matter how many techniques you acquire...
Rage your dream, only that which awaits
...once you think "This is good enough,"
it becomes hard to maintain that state.
Feel the wind, is what you should forget
Rage your dream, split the darkness
Unless you work hard, always aiming upward,
Like a streak to the peak
you'll never be able to advance to a higher level.
Erase the freezing darkness worldwide
I think that's what it means to master the road.
Rage your dream, and open the road
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
I'm not young anymore. It takes all
I have to maintain my current state.
A point 01 second knockdown
Reverberations left behind
disappear to the next town
The losers are left in the dust
Let's ignore the constraints of logic
But you're young! You should
be able to aim even higher.
'Cause they're a pain
A streaker runs naked across the street
Something they would know
Rage your dream, race past time
If you feel something...
Even the wind will brim forth with light
...discover even something small
while in my passenger seat...
Rage your dream, only that which awaits
...I'll be satisfied.
Feel the wind, is what you should forget
Because our meeting was one of significance.
Rage your dream,
continue on the unending road
You may feel you've lost in
terms of driving techniques,
Don't look back on your love or your past
but the end result is, you won.
Go forward and you'll shine brightly
Don't forget this experience today.
You are still learning... developing.
Rage your dream, you're living in the now
Both you and Project D.
It's like Ryosuke said...
Fujiwara, the stage that you must
aim for still lies far, far ahead.
Now, you must simply absorb what you need.
The day will come when it shall be of use.
There are still so many
things I have to overcome.
With this Eight-Six,
I'll clear them one by one...
...alongside Project D.
"The challenge of these young men
continues toward tomorrow..."
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte