"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
Look at that crowd!
More people here than at the FD run.
The race between Takumi and
Nakazato is getting a lot of attention.
What am I gonna do? I'm getting
more depressed by the minute.
We are in no position to say it was a mistake.
Takumi!
Please show up!
"Act 8: Time's Almost Up!"
Damn it! My stupid old man!
Where the hell are you?!
Could you win if it were you?
Yeah. I'd win against any
car I raced, R32 or not.
Do you think... I can win?
I know it wasn't your decision to take this race.
Trust me. Whatever you do,
don't race that R32.
You hear me?
Since your opponent's driving an R32,
no one would call you
a coward for backing out.
A coward?!
--Wow!
--Here they come.
--The Night Kids!
--It's Nakazato's R32!
It's amazing!
The black R32 is like a champion of the street.
So these are the Night Kids.
They sure came in with a big group!
K... Kenji!
We'd better start apologizing soon.
Well... but...
There's still time before 10:00.
Let's go talk him into it.
--What?
I don't think it's such a good idea
to drag Takumi into a losing battle.
We'll never know until they actually race.
Of course he'll lose.
It's obvious if you're thinking clearly!
He's going to race the R32!
He can't match its power,
and it's got 4WD ATTESA E-TS!
I thought the same at first.
But since I've been here, I've started
thinking there may be a chance.
Of course, if this was the circuit,
the Eight-Six couldn't win.
But this is a mountain pass!
This is the pass Takumi has been
running for the last five years.
Nobody knows what's going to happen.
When Takumi drives the Eight-Six,
it's no longer an ordinary Eight-Six.
It turns into a super machine
with infinite fighting power!
I know, because I have been
in the car when he's driving...
Takumi's driving is far better
than anything we've ever imagined.
You mean that time when you fainted
after three corners down the hill
with your death wails
echoing through Mt. Akina.
His downhill driving is that crazy!
There should be one other
person who feels the same way.
Wh... Who is that?
There is one other person who
got a good look at his driving.
Are... Are you trying to say...?
That's right!
Keisuke Takahashi of the Red Suns!
Here come the Takahashi Brothers!
--Now we have more stars!
--It's so exciting!
Keisuke!
My dear Ryosuke!
You look great!
They have groupies now 'cause they're cool.
Damn it! Racers should be
admired for their skills.
--I'm no match for them either way.
On top of that, they're rich.
I knew they would be here!
I'm looking forward to seeing
how this race turns out.
Watch closely!
I'll show you who the fastest man in Gunma is!
Not the Eight-Six or the Takahashi Brothers...
It's me! Takeshi Nakazato of the Night Kids!
Bastard!
Looks like the Eight-Six isn't here yet.
In that case,
we have to persuade Takumi no matter what.
All right...
Get in!
Itsuki! What's wrong?
I'll... stay, Iketani...
I can't face Takumi...
Okay.
Wait here until the last possible minute, Itsuki!
I'll bring him, no matter what!
I'm sure that Takumi is coming.
But still...
--Ryosuke! Dear Keisuke!
--What a nice place I'm in!
I might make a habit of this!
Ryosuke! Wait!
Ryosuke, honey!
What's going on? I'm so tense I could die.
I wanna go to Mt. Akina so bad.
I'm not really sure if I love
driving that much, but...
For the past five years, come rain or snow,
I've driven Mt. Akina more often than anyone.
I want to see how much I'm capable of.
Everyone says that the GT-R is really fast,
so I want to challenge it
with everything I've got.
I've never felt like this before.
I can't stop thinking about racing,
even though I don't have a car.
On the contrary, I want to
race more every second.
My stupid dad!
Where the hell did you go?
Oh!
Takumi!
Iketani!
What?!
Your father has taken the car?
Yeah...
You have no idea where he might be?
I thought he might be at some bar,
and I called every bar I know.
You couldn't find him?
Uh-uh...
What the hell...?!
If you don't have the Eight-Six,
there's no use talking about it.
This is really unexpected.
Iketani, did you come here
to talk me into racing?
Kind of, yeah.
People are making a big
deal over this at the pass!
Nakazato of the Night Kids
and the Takahashi Brothers
are stirring up the crowd.
But despite all that...
you are the star today, Takumi!
Wait a minute! Please...
...don't give me a hard time.
Still... you haven't changed your mind?
It's not that.
To tell you the truth, I wanted to go.
--What?!
But without the car, what can I do?
I was very depressed until you arrived.
Gee! Why is this happening?
How disappointing!
What can we do without the car?
I've got an idea! Hey, Takumi.
How about running in Kenji's 180?
Great idea!
It's the same FR...
...and it's got turbo for extra power...
It sure will run fast if you drive it.
--It won't work.
--Why not?
I'm not gonna race in somebody else's car.
It's gotta be my own car that I'm used to.
You have a point.
Driving somebody else's car
is not a good thing in the racing world.
Anyway, I'll wait until the last minute.
That's my only option.
He's late. What's going on?
It's already 9:45.
I guess he's not coming.
Where is he?
--What time is it?
--Almost 10:00.
Oh, no! He's not gonna make it!
Where are you, Dad?
Please come back!
I don't have any more time!
--He's back!
--What?
Turning off of the highway...
...gunning the engine twice,
that rhythm... and that roar...
He's here.
You can tell that just from the exhaust sound?
Are you sure it's your car?
Of course I am. It's absolutely my car!
The Takahashi Brothers are here.
Yeah...
They must be very anxious about this race.
They told me to my face that I'd lose.
Damn Ryosuke Takahashi!
He's not as good as his reputation suggests.
I'll beat the Eight-Six right in front of him
and embarrass him.
Let's do it.
And if you show that you're
faster than the Eight-Six
that beat Keisuke Takahashi...
...we can prove that we're
faster than the Red Suns.
This is a good opportunity to
make the crowd realize something.
The drift run can never beat the grip run.
There you go! It's like your favorite phrase.
It's a matter of course.
The drift run is just a
performance to rile up the crowd.
It's not a technique for driving fast.
It's just like you to say it firmly.
I can say this, 'cause I went
through a drift stage myself
when I was driving the S13.
A racer who has outgrown the
drift run can drive the fastest
in the grip run.
When you lost to the R32,
it was really shocking.
Oops! That was a no-no.
Well... I've changed since then.
Since that monster defeated me,
I'm driving better than ever before in the R32.
You can't call yourself a street
racer if you stop pursuing races.
I can't stand everyone making such
a fuss about the drift technique.
Come out, Eight-Six!
Showing off by drifting in your FR is over.
I'll prove it!
As usual, he doesn't show up
until the last minute.
I wonder if he'll really show up.
Didn't he tell you he had
no intention of coming?
He's coming.
I'm sure of it.
He'll definitely come.
Anyway, that's the story.
So I'm taking the car, Dad!
You'd better hurry, Takumi!
It's almost time.
We're sorry... We're taking Takumi with us.
We'll buy ten of your deep-fried
tofu in return when we get back.
Th-The ones mixed with veggies, too...
Hey! Wait!
Takumi...
His eyes looked different.
What's going on?
Never mind.
With that setting, he'll do a good job.
We're almost at the pass.
I wonder if you can catch up.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but his car is a non-turbo 1.6.
This is a 2-liter turbo.
Whatever the case may be going downhill,
it's no joke if I fall far behind him going uphill.
Who do you think I am?! One of
the top three in the Speed Stars.
Wow!
So fast!
I can do that, too.
To full power!
--Oh...!
He's gone!
The Eight-Six has disappeared!
Takumi... You were looking away
even during the entrance ceremony.
Two minutes to 10:00.
I guess they couldn't talk him into it.
I should go apologize like a real man.
Wait! Iketani told me to wait.
I should do as I was told.
But this is all my fault.
Nothing to do with the Speed Stars.
I should take my punishment like a man.
Oh, no! There are so many of them!
Looks like I have to roll with the punches.
This is no joke!
I doubt they'll be willing to forgive me
if I tell them the Eight-Six isn't coming now.
Apologizing on my knees won't help.
If worse comes to worst, I might get killed.
Dad! Mom!
Help me!
Please, God!
I haven't even done it with a girl yet.
I don't wanna die a virgin.
--It's him!
--He's here!
Oh, no! They found me!
It's too late to run.
I'm dead!
What the hell are you doing
sitting in the middle of the road, Itsuki?
Ta... Ta... Ta...
Get out of my way!
Come on! I'm gonna run you over.
Takumi!
You came!
Yeah...
Sorry, Itsuki... for being late.
Takumi...!
A street racer should race
if he's challenged, right?
Takumi...!
Don't... Your snot... Hey, stop, Itsuki!
Yeah... That's the spirit!
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu.
Oh, Yuichi!
Are you there?
I wonder what happened to my son.
He wanted to go to the pass of his own accord.
Like father, like son, huh?
Putting that aside,
today his opponent is a GT-R.
Honestly, does he have a chance?
He really did show up.
Keisuke, you were right.
So it seems...
You were gonna tell that Eight-Six's driver
about the R32's weak point, weren't you?
I was, but not anymore.
Once I saw his face, I felt nothing but disgust.
He's my enemy, after all. Besides...
...he won't lose, even if he doesn't
know the R32's weak point.
Did you give him any advice?
Nothing special, but even
the GT-R has a weak point.
The R32's weak point is...
Put simply... the body weight...
...the understeer resulting
from being super front-heavy.
Even with a tuned pedal
and driving technique,
this basic fact doesn't change.
If you keep driving tough on the downhill,
the front tires and brakes
will wear out for sure.
Even with a tuned brake,
by the time they come
to the bottom of the hill,
it'll have trouble with the
understeer going into the turn.
If there is any chance of winning,
it's in the corners towards
the end of the course.
Whether or not the Eight-Six can
keep up with the R32 until then...
That's the key to this race.
About the Eight-Six's foot settings...
I changed the settings a little bit.
The foot settings? How?
So that it will heavily understeer
when you step on the gas pedal.
That's how the foot setting is now.
What?! Understeer by
punching the accelerator?!
Takumi's driving uses drift.
What were you thinking, Bunta?
How can he race with that
foot setting against the GT-R?
You don't understand, Yuichi.
If you are good enough,
the understeer setting allows you
to accelerate faster when it's FR.
For the purpose of carrying tofu,
it's usually set lower.
With this setting,
it's possible to drive longer at full power.
But only if you're good enough...
I'm sure he can handle it.
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irete nani ka wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
Mr. Nakazato, what is your chance
of winning against the Eight-Six?
Can't you tell without asking?
You mean your R32's going to win.
But Ryosuke Takahashi said...
He's just a coward since his brother lost!
I will teach them that I, Takeshi
Nakazato, am the fastest in Gunma.
I'll show them once and for all that
grip driving is better than drifting!
--What does...
--It means action, action!
Next time on Initial D, "Battle to the Limit!"
Don't miss it!