"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
In the silver smoke amidst the frozen city
Payback for a dream I've seen so many times
My body is frozen in a
memory that I can't shake
Slam on the accelerator and deceive myself
Broken in the night
My eyes become sharper
All from someone's whim
It seems like the world will end any minute
Break into the night, it's the time
With scared eyes, I'm lost in the night
Embraced by a falling dream
Scared of being alone, missin' my heart
Even hurting myself
Love me so much,
enough that I could fall apart
If only I could throw everything away
And just love you
Then I know I could face the truth
I'm glad we came, Kenji!
Itsuki, this is paradise!
It's amazing!
Takumi!
Come over here and swim with us.
Um, I'm okay...
Okay, we're coming!
What's wrong? Come on!
We'll be right there!
--I'm so glad I came!
--Me, too!
"Act 20: The End of Summer"
You're coming wth us, right?
What's wrong? Aren't you having fun?
Yeah, sure.
Let's go down the slide, Takumi.
I think I'll just hang around here instead.
He's always hanging around.
Can we come?
Sure. You guys can come along, too.
We can come along!
Okay, let's go!
Shall we go, Takumi?
I'm not too good with slides...
It's nothing compared to your super drift.
She's always like that...
Forceful and single-minded.
I see no harm in it.
They're having fun.
Was it really okay for all
of you to take today off?
I used a sick day. My boss wasn't too happy.
She's so beautiful...
...that my heart may explode.
Seeing her in her swimsuit
is my best summer memory ever.
I'll never forget it.
After all, she is out of my reach.
Iketani.
Thank you very much for everything.
--Well...
--I'm very grateful.
I realized many things the other night.
Mako...
I'm sorry to have bothered you,
but I've decided to keep racing.
That's good!
I was hoping you wouldn't quit.
I was conceited,
because they labeled me "Usui's fastest."
We can't recover!
Spin away from him!
That race forced me to realize
the depth of driving technique.
And if I quit now,
I'll be leaving things unfinished.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's good to know what I did was useful.
Iketani?
You remember our promise
by the lake, don't you?
It came out wrong,
so you may have misunderstood me, but...
...I didn't mean it like a deal.
Would you...
...make me a woman?
I'll be waiting for you around 8:00,
under that billboard where we first met.
Can we slow down?
So cute!
Her breasts are against my back...
I have Kenji against my back...
This is so sad!
No!
Mako, can you get the ball?
Please!
Ryosuke Takahashi!
Ready, Sayuki?
Here!
Bad throw!
Sorry!
Bad throw.
Why does she carry his picture?
Anything wrong?
Oh, no...
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
You said you've never
had a relationship before.
Yes...
But you must have had a
crush on someone, right?
Sure.
I just wondered why you
didn't go out with him.
I'm sure most guys would die
for a pretty girl like you.
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
What does he do?
He's a street racer, too.
It was about three years ago,
when I was still in high school...
A few of us from school went to see a race.
I knew nothing about street racing then,
but this one car left a
lasting impression on me.
Even I could see that he had
a very special talent for racing.
I was mesmerized by the world of racing,
and got hooked on it.
I got my license and managed to buy a car.
I practiced day in and day out.
I thought I'd feel close to him if I got better.
Perhaps it wasn't the right motive.
I often went to watch him race.
But I never even talked to him...
...so I'm not sure if I really
liked him in that way.
I can't say whether I was
admiring him, or his technique.
But you liked him.
I guess so.
I guess I liked him a lot.
What a fraud!
I shouldn't have asked.
She seems far away now.
She was admiring a superstar...
The number-one racer in Gunma...
Ryosuke Takahashi.
Now I know why she likes FCs.
How can I possibly compete with him?!
He's finally ready to go
head-to-head with the Eight-Six.
Do you want to come along?
I'll show you my "fastest racer" theory.
Big brother...
That was so much fun!
I never knew that going to the pool
with girls was this much fun!
Right, Takumi?
You were mostly with Kenji, though.
Mako and Sayuki are the best, right, Kenji?
You do recover quickly.
Just a few days ago,
you were saying that racers didn't need girls.
Those two are different.
Itsuki!
All I can see is those two in their bikinis.
So blinding!
Sayuki's bouncing breasts are something,
but Mako's body is just incredible.
Right, Iketani?
I guess so.
You don't sound very convinced.
What's wrong?
Did you two have a fight or something?
No.
I'm just tired is all.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry about today, boss.
No big deal.
You should enjoy your youth while it lasts.
I'd be worried if you only cared about cars
and didn't have a girlfriend.
--Yeah.
--Good luck.
Your angel's name is Mako, right?
How's it going?
It doesn't look too good.
She is definitely too good for me.
Don't be so negative.
Listen, girls are like...
No, boss, it's okay. I have no chance.
I can't compete with Ryosuke Takahashi.
What's that supposed to mean?
What's going on? I can barely follow him.
His FC is the same, so what's going on?
My theory evolves with each new piece of data.
Be patient, Eight-Six!
When my theory is complete,
you'll be on my "defeated"list.
"Kamameshi"
I got here first.
My heart is pumping so fast that I can't breathe.
I may die when Iketani gets here.
What?
You just don't understand
women at all, do you?
Listen to me.
It's not that she was actually dating him, is it?
Every young girl has a crush on somebody.
It's no different than admiring idols on TV.
Yeah.
Just think about it for a minute.
She decided to come clean with you
because she chose you over him.
She revealed her secret to you
because she trusts you.
Can't you see that?
Forget about your stupid inferiority complex!
Being in love means that you
accept everything about the person.
Isn't that what love is all about?!
Eight o'clock?!
It's half past, you idiot!
I won't make it.
It'll take at least an hour to get to Yokokawa.
She won't wait for me.
Just go!
You won't know that until you get there!
Go, or you're fired!
If you call yourself a racer,
don't let up on the gas.
Drive as if your life depended on it.
But he probably won't make it.
That's also part of being young.
The boss is right.
I'm such an idiot!
I'll never meet anyone like her again.
Why couldn't I be more honest?!
My name is Mako Sato.
Call me!
I'll give you my virginity.
I'll be waiting for you around 8:00,
under that billboard where we first met.
She was always honest with me... but I...
I'm certifiable!
My feet hurt.
I hate high heels.
Mako, I don't need to go to a hotel with you.
Well, I want to, but...
What am I saying?
I just want to see your face.
Please, God...
I just need one more chance!
Please don't take away my angel!
Traffic? An accident? Not now!
No!
Oh, God, why?!
I'm sorry, Mako.
I'll never wear high heels again.
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
Ah! Takumi, what's with that bouquet?!
--Uh...
--Oh! It's from Natsuki, isn't it?
--No...
--I get it. It was a present to you,
the driver of the Fujiwara Tofu Shop
(Private Vehicle)
black-and-white Trueno that every
racer in Gunma knows about now,
from a gaggle of girls!
--Uh, that's not right.
--Ah! So it's from Sayuki.
Sayuki was after you in a weird way, huh?
No. I got this from Ryosuke Takahashi.
Huh?
Next on Initial D: "Challenge From a Superstar."
Don't miss it!