"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Are you Mr. Fujiwara of Project D?
That's dishonest and horrible!
What happened?
Took the day off today.
I took another shift for someone else.
Comp time off, huh?
How did it go?
You're done with Ibaraki, right?
Did you lose?
I won.
Then why do you look so gloomy?
It's about something else.
Who is this?
Hello?
Well, um... it's fine, but hold on.
What's the matter?
A girl?
Hello.
I'm sorry for calling you so suddenly.
I wanted to apologize to you earlier, but...
No, it's okay.
How did you get my number?
I looked up the number for the gas station,
and when I called, an attendant gave me your number.
I see.
I'm so sorry for saying such awful things.
You must be mad at me.
No, I'm okay as long
as you know it wasn't me.
I thought I should apologize
in person instead of calling you.
but the days flew by before
I could make time to come visit you.
I'm truly sorry.
I'll find time to visit you.
Well then.
Um, what about me coming there?
Eh?
That's if you're okay with it.
I don't mind driving
to your neighborhood.
W-what am I saying?!
Are you sure, really?
Y-yeah.
Act 2  [ New Battlefield ]
Thank you for coming all this way.
To be honest, I was sort of relieved and glad when I realized that it wasn't you, after showing your picture to Tomoko.
When I saw you for the first time,
you didn't look like a dishonest person.
But you went pretty far, didn't you?
I got carried away
because I was so furious.
I'm really sorry.
It must have hurt because
I work out in the club.
What do you do?
Golf.
I've been practicing since I was little.
I've got training camp and competitions,
so my summer break is packed with training.
So I couldn't come to Gunma.
I'm glad you came.
I took my father's suggestion
and started to play golf.
If I skip training, he gets mad.
That sounds familiar.
I was forced to learn how to
drive since I was in middle school.
I hated it before, and we butted heads a lot, but
I eventually began to drive because I wanted to.
I understand what you're saying so well.
I argued with my dad all the time.
But now golf is a part of my daily life.
We're alike.
What the hell?!
You went to Saitama to see her today?!
And what did you talk about?
Nothing really.
We just had tea in a family
restaurant for about an hour.
What's her name?
How old is she?
Her name is Uehara Mika, and she's a year
younger than us, so she's a senior in high school.
And what?
Is she taken?
Are you going to date her?
What?
We didn't talk about anything like that.
I'm not you.
Why not?
That's the most important part, isn't it?
We couldn't talk much in
such a short period of time.
It was really short.
I'm gonna say this because it's you.
I think I fell in love with
her the first time I saw her.
I wish I could say that!
I'm so envious!
I feel awkward.
I don't know what
to do about this feeling.
I don't get it.
If you like her, you have to gather
your courage and make a move.
But it could be one sided.
She doesn't necessarily feel the same way.
Sounds awfully timid for a driving genius.
That has nothing to do with this.
I'm not very confident.
We'll counter Project D with four
carefully planned defensive lines.
Sidewinder Chief Driver - Hojo Gou
As a prelude to the battles in Hakone, we'll watch how our opponents race on this mountain path.
Sidewinder Chief Mechanic - Kubo Eiji
Racing Team Katagiri Street Version -
Minagawa Hideo
Team Spiral Leader - Ikeda Ryuji (Zero)
We'll assemble a data collection team
and completely expose their strategy.
Let us take care of that.
"If you know the enemy and know yourself,
you need not fear the result of a hundred battles."
Information and data is
everything in today's racing.
Do we really have to go that far?
I don't think our opponent is good enough for the
best three in Kanagawa to sneak around like this.
In any case, I'll settle this during my turn.
Sorry, but you guys won't
have a chance to compete.
You sound quite confident.
Alright, I look forward to it, then.
Team 246 Leader - Satoshi Omiya
That's quite an indirect and
hesitant strategy, isn't it?
Team 246 Driver - Kobayakawa
I don't like that sequence.
Sounds like the first team,
which is us, shouldn't win.
So, should we deliberately lose and
let the next team take the credit?
Oh, please.
A fair and square win is the best.
I'm pissed at those Sidewinder guys, too.
We didn't ask them to manage this.
We have no reason
to hold back for them.
Show the true potential of 246.
Amazing.
She hits great distances without slicing.
What happened, Mika?
I wonder what Takumi is doing now.
Hey, Fujiwara, don't just space out.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Big news, Iketani!
Check this out!
GOLF
What?
A golf magazine?
Here, take a look inside.
That's her, right?
"A new star in women's golf"
"Uehara Mika, seventeen years old"?!
This is the girl who slapped Takumi?
I'm absolutely positive.
She looked exactly like this.
Man, if I'd known she was famous,
I would've asked for her autograph.
A golf genius who hits
a white ball in the daylight
and a driving genius who
tackles the roads at night.
Those are polar opposites, aren't they?
I wonder if this romance
will develop any further.
This is downhill checkpoint 3.
The Eight-Six just passed by.
The FD just passed
hill climb checkpoint 7.
How many years?
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, Takahashi Ryosuke?
You seem to be having a hard time
because of the power increase.
It can't be helped.
After all, hill climbing is a power game.
I have something else that worries me.
I saw some guys with stopwatches
scattered throughout the course.
Are they timing you?
Probably.
I think it's pointless to check our times.
We're still setting up our cars, and
we haven't mastered the course yet.
The speeds will be totally
different during the actual race.
But it bothers me that they're
checking our times every so often.
Okay.
It's ready to go, Keisuke.
Fujiwara seems to be in
good condition as usual.
He appears to enjoy challenging
difficult courses like this.
The car is tricky to drive in every
aspect, but he says it's easy.
It makes me wonder if he's an alien.
Is this okay, Ryosuke?
I'm sure an organized data collection
team is all over the course.
Our cars pace will pick up in the later half.
Anyone with a trained eye will be able to accurately measure our potential.
Probably so.
Shouldn't we think about using
some kind of camouflage?
No, I'd rather not use any cheap tricks.
If they want data, they can
have it, for today that is.
Don't worry, Fumihiro.
I made my decision after careful thinking.
One thing I can say is that the people
collecting data aren't our next opponents.
Is that so?
Think about it.
The battle is tomorrow.
There's no time to set up
a car based on today's data.
You're right.
They must be an opponent
we're racing against much later.
If so, we still have time.
We must focus on the opponent before us.
The first half is a series of steep uphill slopes.
The second half is a continuous mild slope.
Well, that's from the
hill-climbing perspective, so...
It's the opposite on the downhill.
Yeah.
But whether it's a hill-climb or downhill
the key to this course are the parts
where the road width suddenly changes.
There are many places where two lanes change into one throughout the course.
Those will be important overtaking points.
You're right.
I know that in my head
but the locals must know how to benefit from it, and they won't drive on the unfavorable side.
And if you aim for it,
you might fall into a trap.
Oh man, a Lan Evo again
How come my opponents always
seem to be driving 4WD cars?
I've had enough.
Why don't you claim to
be Akagi's Lan Evo killer?
That doesn't even make a good joke.
You can say that,
because you aren't driving.
Frankly speaking, it's the car I hate to compete against the most on the mountain passes now.
Because it's absurdly fast.
They gave us the choice of
being the leader or the pursuer.
Which do you want, Kobayakawa?
I can be either, but I want to take
a close look at my opponent.
I don't think I'll be outrun by a 2WD car
so the first race will be for recon,
and the second will be the real match.
Okay, we'll go with that, then.
I'm Kobayakawa.
I'm Takahashi Keisuke.
Since you're the leader, you know what to do without being told, don't you?
I know.
Half of my job was finished yesterday.
That's what you wanted
to say, right, Brother?
Correct.
I'm counting on you.
I'm going to count down!
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Go!
Give me your best prediction
on how this battle will unfold.
Best prediction?
That's tough at the moment.
He's got power.
Footwork's good, too.
But the road will soon
become steep and rough.
I'm curious as to how he'll handle it.
I know you don't have enough data.
That's why I said "prediction."
Once you have data, you're
correct 100% of the time.
The road suddenly widens here, but it'll narrow soon.
Well then, let me give you my prediction.
Just a prediction, okay?
This is my prediction.
Amazing.
It's rare to see a rear-wheel-drive
car climbing the hill so sharply.
But something's not right.
I don't like the fact that the
car's behaving as it should.
I don't feel any "plus factors."
The driver's presence is too weak.
You're a fast driver, but still,
you're boring, Takahashi Keisuke.
Omiya, what do you think
about Kobayakawa's decision?
I think his choice to be the
pursuer for the first run is correct.
Also, the road is very narrow.
I don't see any disadvantage for
Kobayakawa, even if the race drags on.
If he can figure out what makes him faster
and slower than his opponent in the first run
he can make a bold decisive
maneuver in the second run.
Are you going to use the
same strategy, Omiya?
I don't know.
I'll think about it after seeing
the results of the hill climb.
Results?
But Kobayakawa has an
absolute advantage, right?
His opponent is an FD.
I don't like it when I have
an absolute advantage.
You never know until it's over.
He's good.
He doesn't show any wasteful
wheel spin even on this rough surface.
Your perfectionism comes through loud and clear.
But your "doing your job right"
gets on my nerves.
I got it.
This's enough.
It's not like your team has
outrageously skilled drivers.
Lately, the conversations between you and Keisuke have the tendency to sound like Buddhist riddles.
I don't understand what I'm hearing from
your side, like your advice before the start.
What did Keisuke mean when he said
half of his job was finished yesterday?
Oh, it's nothing.
It doesn't have any complicated meaning.
If you live with someone under the same roof, you can communicate without saying much.
In principle, we've agreed to finish the race
quickly whenever we start in the lead position.
The first half of this course is made of steep hills, so he
must preserve his tires while the FD is at a disadvantage.
Then he can execute a super attack by making the best use
of his tires in several high-speed sections on the second half.
Halfway there.
The slope will be milder
compared to the first half.
He'll make a move somewhere.
Where will it be?
It's the kind of simple and easy strategy that Keisuke would prefer, right?
It's obvious he'll lose his edge if he
challenges the Lan Evo to a long race.
The key to victory is how much
more Keisuke can raise his top speed.
That's what he meant when he said half of his job was finished during yesterday's practice.
Where, dammit?
Where are you going
to make your move?
I know your strategy.
When it comes to rapid acceleration, the Evo won't lose to any other car.
The rest is a matter of concentration.
It's a match of concentration.
One small mistake will cost you the match.
The road's going to widen starting here.
It must be around here.
Here?
Should I try?
Evo and Imp drivers
religiously believe in an idea.
That cars developed for rallying must
be the best on the public streets.
Last spurt yet?
No, he hasn't.
Not yet.
Not here.
Maybe the next?
Where is it, dammit?
But rallies were originally
done in snow or on dirt.
4WDs aren't necessarily
unbeatable on dry asphalt.
That's why I predict
this race will be decided
uneventfully in the first run.
The road just got narrower,
and the visibility is poor.
You won't be able to keep this pace up.
Just before the goal, about 2 to 3 minutes in
terms of time, his concentration will reach its peak.
If our opponent can keep up with
Keisuke's top speed, Keisuke will lose.
The winner will be...
You won't get away!
Evo, let's do it!
He caught me off guard,
sprinting out in a place like that.
Public roads are unfair in every way.
On a complex winding road
layout with no escape zones
strictly speaking, you can
never reach the limit.
If there was a public road specialist,
that person would possess
courage, fighting spirit, experience, and
in some cases, the recklessness of youth.
I can catch up.
I must.
I must catch him once
again no matter what!
and a plus factor given only
to those chosen by God.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree-lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.