"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
This is reality.
The pace has definitely increased.
Can't I become childish enough?
Can't I push myself recklessly?
Trying not to make any mistakes
while conserving my tires.
Is that kind of calculating
making me drive like an old man?
Ridiculous.
I race with the faith that I'm the fastest out there.
He hit the guard rail!
What's happening?
A real racing driver is seriously
attacking an amateur Eight-Six driver!
What the hell? That's impossible.
Cleared the corner!
Pros are amazing, after all. That was my limit.
I couldn't have turned any faster.
So a traditional racing strategy
puts me at a disadvantage.
Fujiwara is being pushed hard.
The final stage is near.
I've got to become childish
in order to win this battle.
Act 5  [ Fujiwara Zone ]
Hey, Fujiwara, how much longer are you going
to make your son play such a meaningless game?
Look who's talking.
You used to be a wild street
racer when you were young.
Times have changed.
It's meaningless unless you drive on the circuit.
No matter how much practice he gains in mountain
passes, he won't advance past a certain level.
Your son is talented.
I'm telling you this because
I don't want you to waste it.
This is tough.
I feel like he's cornered.
No, he's grown a lot more
than you realize, Fumihiro.
Is that so?
Since he's the leader, our strategy
is to finish the race on the first run.
I already gave detailed
instructions to Fujiwara yesterday.
The actual trick lies ahead.
There's no way he's lost
his concentration yet.
I don't understand what you mean by
growing out of the mountain passes or not.
Then I can affirm to you that my
son will definitely win this time.
Let me tell you, nothing can
be that certain in a competition.
Ryosuke's prediction was dead on.
I've got to focus.
It's risky, but I've gotta try this.
His unlimited vehicle control skills
are the best part of the Fujiwara Zone.
When he drives the Eight-Six, he creates
a situation that even a pro can't surpass.
That's the idea behind our trap, but I'm
sure our opponent has already figured it out.
Does that mean our strategy will fail?
No, it doesn't.
Do you think a pro would run
away from a clash of skills?
His pride will make him
face the challenge head on.
At the very least, today's opponent is that type.
I approved this strategy because
I thought an honest and fair person
who chooses their position with a coin
toss, will knowingly fall into our trap.
On top of that, they're
racing on a mountain pass.
My son is a master of it.
The goal is close.
It's going to be an over the limit braking
match at the entrance of the next corner.
This is what mountain
pass racing is all about.
If you can clear the corner at that speed,
I should be able to, as well.
I'll take your challenge!
The combined performance
of Fujiwara and the Eight-Six
can make them clear a corner at a
speed that pros would think impossible.
Such things happen in reality.
It's all part of the Fujiwara Zone.
Same speed, same line.
Plus, my car's MR layout has
a higher limit than an FR's!
This can't be happening!
I lost.
Anything I say will sound like an excuse.
My car's got a mid engine and rear wing.
I thought I couldn't
lose during full braking.
Pros are trained to control their car a
half step before such a situation occurs.
But you kept controlling your car
until the end, while I chickened out.
The spin was caused by me backing away.
That's what I regret the most.
If I had kept going, I don't know whether
I would have cleared the corner or hit a tree.
My fighting spirit was defeated
by the fear of going off the course.
At the same time,
I was defeated by you.
I was going to invite you to
the world of circuit racing
but I've changed my mind after racing you.
Your peculiar driving sense won't
have much use in my world.
I just feel like it'd be a waste.
Be the best in your field.
You'll become one of a kind.
That's my advice to you.
Thank you.
Oh, hold on.
A victory report has come.
Hello, it's me.
What the?!
That's impossible!
So Takumi won, huh?
It couldn't have happened, dammit!
It's only a game of playing
tag in a mountain pass.
I don't need your comforting words!
You can't understand my frustration!
I'm Minagawa.
I'm Takahashi Keisuke.
I've heard that you're fast,
with consecutive wins against 4WD cars.
If you can shake me off,
you are indeed something.
Let me see your proud sprint dash.
Are you telling me to be the lead?
Alright, but do you think
you can keep up with me?
Shut the hell up.
Listen, Kenta
Yes?
This battle has a special meaning to me.
Do you understand?
I do.
Watch me.
I'll win no matter what.
I wonder how Takumi's race went.
He should give us a call.
He's dense when it
comes to things like this.
He doesn't understand our concern.
Yeah, but it's pointless to get frustrated.
Not just Takumi, Takahashi Keisuke's
going up against a pro racer too, right?
Right. Neither Takumi nor Takahashi
Keisuke can let their guard down.
Geez, I'm so pumped up!
Five seconds till start!
Three
Two
One
Go!
Why do I feel so irritated,
or is it more like vicious?
I want a complete victory over you.
I know what Keisuke means by special.
It's because his opponent today is a pro.
He's trying to test his skills against a pro.
No matter how many amateur
4WD drivers you've defeated
amateurs can't use the
full potential of their cars.
If I dash when the tires
are in their best condition,
I should be able to overtake
you even with my heavy 80 Supra.
The battle between rear wheel drive cars boils
down to the game of conserving the rear tires.
You can't attain real tire management skills
unless you take part in professional racing.
You'll wear out your rear tires
by trying too hard in the first run.
Then the proud speed brat of the
mountain passes will be finished.
Hey, do you remember
the second round of the battle
against the Todo School in Tochigi?
In that complex stage
of uphill and downhill
everyone thought you'd choose Keisuke's FD
against the racing driver, Tachi Tomoyuki.
But you chose Fujiwara's Eight-Six.
Your explanation was so
sensational that I couldn't forget.
You said you're using two approaches in your
pursuit of the fastest record in street racing.
That's why there are two drivers in Project D.
Oh, that.
I'm amazed you remember that.
Of course I did.
It sounded so meaningful.
Fujiwara is a peculiar type, who
specializes in mountain passes.
And I think he's become
exactly as you described.
On the other hand, Keisuke is a traditional type,
who adapts racing techniques to the street.
You chose Fujiwara because we wouldn't have stood
a chance against a pro in a clash of traditional skills.
I did say that.
Then what'll happen during today's battle?
Today's opponent has top level traditional skills.
The Eight-Six kid won the downhill battle,
but I wonder how the hill climb round will develop.
This time I want to
hear your prediction, Hojo.
Minagawa is a proud person, so he
doesn't think he can lose to an amateur.
But the younger Takahashi is a
better driver than Minagawa thinks.
He's well trained, especially his acceleration work.
That's why that FD's been undefeated so far.
I see.
Plus, he's backed by Ryosuke.
I don't think he'd send his brother
into a race without a strategy.
I feel the same way.
This battle will be tangled up. It's a big
mistake to think Minagawa will win easily.
Whose side are you on, Hojo?
What happened between you and
our opponent's leader in the past?
There's nothing important
between Ryosuke and I.
It's my older brother who has a
bitter connection to Ryosuke.
The driver who's nicknamed the Grim Reaper?
The FD is the lead? Minagawa
must have chosen to be the chaser.
Their positions in the first round will be the key to the outcome of this race.
As expected, he's got more horsepower.
But that doesn't mean much in this battle.
Both of us are well aware of that.
Indeed, our opponent is a
top class traditional driver.
With competition trained skills,
he won't show any weakness.
The sense of shaving time off,
mental ease at the limit, and stamina.
Those things can't be
attained by street racers.
It'd be the right strategy for us to throw
a change up, instead of a fast ball
but we don't have that kind of choice with Keisuke.
So I've sent Keisuke out with confidence
because Keisuke has grown.
Special menu? Like a boot camp?
Right.
It will be extremely difficult to continue defeating
powerful 4WD cars with your rear wheel drive FD3S.
The key is how effectively
you use the rear tires.
This training is for that.
Just five round trips
a day should be fine.
Try to match the times I've set for the
ten laps of uphill and downhill driving.
Write every time down in this notebook,
and show it to me every day.
If there's a noticeable gap between my preset time and
your actual time, try to figure out why, and report in detail.
That's all.
Fine by me, but these times are quite
a bit slower than Akagi's best record.
Don't you think this is too easy?
I didn't say you have to surpass those times.
It's not good to be faster or slower.
What?
Whether it's uphill or downhill,
in rain, or behind a slower car
you must aim for one fixed time.
If you think it's easy,
you're seriously mistaken.
You'll know how hard it is soon enough.
If you're frustrated that you weren't chosen for
the race against Tachi Tomoyuki in Tochigi
complete this menu every day until fall.
That's an absolute necessity for you to
continue winning until the Kanagawa races.
I see. I didn't know Keisuke had
to put in that kind of training.
So the second race against Todo
School must have made you do that.
But what's the meaning
behind the special training?
That training was slightly modified for Keisuke
but it's basically the same menu
I used when I was younger.
The same menu?
If you drive blindly at full throttle, you'll only put
stress on the car, and your skills won't improve.
Drive at the limit over and over, and
your times will eventually even out.
It's more difficult to get a set time while holding back,
because your times can easily be faster or slower.
Just flooring the gas pedal won't work.
You must learn the technique of
controlling the throttle precisely.
That's not all.
In rain, you have to be creative in setting the pace for
the constantly changing friction coefficient of the surface.
It's difficult to cope with the situation
when you get stuck behind a slow car.
Suppose you lost 4 seconds until the overtake
point, you must recover exactly 4 seconds.
And you do that with the internal clock in
your body, instead of relying on a stopwatch.
Is that possible?
Not right away, but you'll be able to,
depending on how you train yourself.
That's the traditional way of driving practice.
You attain an abundance of information
through repetitious simple training.
And then your internal sensor
will become sensitive to time.
I've gotta control the gas pedal
depression in a number of small steps.
It's much harder to control your desired
speed than trying to drive as fast as possible.
The great thing about Keisuke is that once he sets his
mind to it, he'll finish a task without any compromise.
He drives every day,
except for Project D's race days.
Every day?!
As the gap between the desired
and actual times narrowed
he began to understand what
made his time too fast or too slow.
The daily report made him create
a habit of analyzing things rationally
which added a logical foundation
to his intuitive driving style.
He must be aware of an unexpected
side effect of the training, as well.
Brother told me the special training
was for my accelerator work.
But that's not exactly true.
There's something else I need, in order to
continue winning in this tough Kanagawa area.
Watch me, Brother.
I've come to realize what it is.
Remember our first battle in Kanagawa, Fumihiro?
The Lan Evo of Team 246?
Keisuke accelerated in the mid section and won.
His tire management in the
second half was splendid
but I'm more interested in his
refined acceleration when needed.
Speed is what I meant by a side effect.
Tire management skills specialized for
mountain passes, and sense of time.
The real reason I made Keisuke train that way was
to make him attain those two skills at a high level.
Strangely enough, the menu
was designed to slow him down
but it helped him drive
a lot faster in the end.
And today's strategy is to make
the best use of that side effect.
In other words, Keisuke will engage in a head to
head fight against a racing driver in a sprint battle?
I won't let Fujiwara steal the show.
I'll build the legend of Project D,
the best of the Kanto area.
Not too shabby.
He's trying to catch me off guard by altering
the throttle opening at the exit of every corner.
Opening the throttle randomly between 85-90%, he's
gauging vehicle distance to decide when to accelerate.
I didn't expect him to pull off such a trick.
He's much better than I thought.
The first half of the hill climb battle is almost over.
What did you think of our
opponent this time around?
What's your actual impression?
When it comes to speed,
race car drivers are really fast.
In my race, I was able to pull away once.
I put on a spurt at 100%, believing that
I must outrun my opponent from there
but I was caught, and felt pressured.
I panic when I lose
in speed at a critical moment.
I understand that.
But Keisuke is different from me.
How do I put it?
Keisuke has an aura
which makes me glad that he's on my side,
because I don't want to race against him.
There are many fast drivers, but
I believe it'd be tough to fight Keisuke.
It's begun.
I'm counting on you, Keisuke.
Without two genius drivers on my team, it'll be
impossible to sweep all the races in Kanagawa.
And Project D won't be complete.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.