"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
"Act 13: Motivation"
Oh, is that so?
You're working at a gas station.
It doesn't pay much, but working every
day covered in grease sure is fun.
Because I always get to be near cars.
You've sort of grown up, Itsuki.
Being a full-time worker
has changed you somehow.
Uh, I don't think I've changed a bit.
I think you're the one who's
more grown-up, Kazumi.
You're sort of different from before.
I don't know... I don't think I've changed at all.
"Shibusawa Station"
"Cigarettes""Ticket Gate"
What? Is something stuck on my face?
Oh? Okay, then...
Dammit! She's gotten way too cute!
This has turned into a
drawn-out battle, just as I'd hoped.
When it comes to stamina, I'm not
gonna lose out to some little kid!
That's good thinking. A supercharger, huh?
Power ful and easy to handle.
That could give me some problems.
This is one battle that won't be settled quickly!
With this rain, there'll be no more time limit.
I should prepare myself for the worst!
By the way, I got my license.
Oh, you did? What, automatic only?
No, manual. I can even drive
my brother's Levin if I want.
I don't like it so much, though.
He'll let me drive it sometimes,
but the steering wheel's heavy
and it's a lot of work.
Won't you buy a car?
I used all my money for driving school,
so not anytime soon.
I guess I'll just work hard till I've
saved enough for a down payment.
Oh, hey! I installed a turbo in
my Eight-Five! It's so fast now!
One day soon, I'm gonna go up against Iketani!
Wow, so you're a real racer now.
Well, I guess! If you like,
I'll take you for a drive sometime!
What do you think? Seems like
a pretty even match, huh?
It's not as if you can go opening
it full throttle in this rain.
The lower the speed range,
the more the FD loses its advantage.
Ah. Thank you.
They're just before the road cut hairpins.
It looks like it's a dead heat.
He's not just gonna let us win. That FD is fast.
At any rate, keeping up with Wataru's
Levin in this rain is no easy task.
As I thought during the race with Kyoko,
this guy's accelerator handling is superb.
At this rate, he might be able to keep up...
Yes. But the longer this gets drawn out,
the more Wataru has the advantage.
About that, the other guy
had the same turbo S13 180!
Why would you use that in a race?!
What the hell's with Itsuki?
He blows us off to have a good
time over there by himself!
Do something, Takumi!
Uh, well, there's not much I can...
Just look at those leering faces!
What are those two talking about?!
I didn't know Wataru would be
here until I'd arrived, either.
What's more, Kazumi showing up
when Itsuki of all guys has to be here...
Sure is a coincidence, huh?
It's like a soap opera or something!
If only Itsuki gets a happy ending,
I won't have a leg to stand on!
Dammit! Come on Mako, show up!
No chance of that happening...
There's something I'd like to
talk to you about. You mind?
He's done a good job of keeping up.
I should know, having originally had a turbo.
Driving a high-powered turbo
on wet roads is hard!
He may be my enemy,
but that bastard's got great skill.
There's just one thing I want to ask.
Is it about what happened
just before the goal?
No, not that. See, I'm a Ferrari driver.
We're not good at playing chase, like...
The whole tactical thing,
passing and being passed...
I'm really not interested in that.
What I want to know is, simply, where does
your strong sense of motivation come from?
I felt it clearly in the middle of our race.
You've got really strong emotions.
At the very least, when it comes to car
performance, mine should have an advantage.
And I don't think there's that much
difference in our driving techniques...
It's strange.
Even though I'm saying this,
you just seem like a regular guy.
But that intense motivation of yours
even shrugs off rain like it's nothing...
Just where does it come from?
Anyone who says he's not afraid
of the rain is a rank amateur.
Driving in the rain wears away at your nerves.
Sustaining your concentration
for a long period of time
takes extraordinary willpower and stamina.
I think that's what motivation is.
That's what I meant when I said
you've got strong emotions.
Talking from my own experience,
that degree of emotional strength isn't
possible without a strong sense of purpose.
Your driving is sort of like a pro's.
Like a pro's? It is?
Beginning the second round!
Starting in five seconds!
Four... Three...
--Two... One...
--The second round, let's do this!
--Yeah!
--Go!
I'm a bit apprehensive about the second race.
After all, he's up against that FD.
You think Wataru will be all right?
He'll stick with him, no matter what.
The roads in this area are like his home course.
This guy's good. This rain can't be very
pleasant for a high-powered rotary turbo.
On wet roads, having as much power as an FD
means not being able to accelerate normally.
It takes ultra-precise half-throttle acceleration.
But there are no faults in my strategy!
If this becomes a war of attrition,
the car that's harder to control
will cause its driver to slip up.
Once your concentration is broken,
that's when you make mistakes...
That's what will decide this race!
You say that, but I still don't really understand.
I always feel that I want to get better.
I think the other members of Project D
are much more "like a pro" than me.
In any case, I just race as hard as I can
and try not to drag them down.
Is that so? Then it's probably your environment.
How old are you?
Nineteen.
Nineteen?! I'll be 26 this year.
If I'd had your technique when I was 19,
I think my life would've been a lot different.
I'm jealous of you.
If I'd just put in the extra effort,
I'd be in an environment where
I could race as fast as I like.
I've been in something of a slump recently...
I wanted to ask you in case I could
pick up any hints. Sorry to bother you.
Motivation, huh? I've come this far
without really giving it much thought.
Just being in Project D
gets me naturally motivated.
I think I've found myself in an
incredibly blessed environment.
Also, I love this car!
So... my strongest emotion is not wanting
to lose to Keisuke, my own teammate!
He's keeping up with me after all, eh?
It's to be expected.
With MUs this low, I can only
run my engine at half strength.
My FD isn't in its element
unless it's in a high-speed race.
The old me probably would've blown his top,
but that accelerator training I've been
doing recently is coming in handy.
Anyway, I have to wait it out.
My chance will definitely come!
If he could win, then I can definitely win, too!
This race has gotten deadlocked, huh?
Having to draw it out longer
works against Keisuke.
In these rainy conditions, he should have
no anxiety regarding the car's mechanics...
So all the pressure falls onto the driver, huh?
It's his nerves that get worn down.
I wonder how long Keisuke
can sustain his concentration.
You seem like you enjoy it. Tormenting Keisuke.
That's not it.
He'll never get a better chance than this
to fully master the task he's been undertaking.
I'll have him race long and leisurely.
Yeah, you've got a point...
Techniques that do not come alive during
actual, pressure-filled races are meaningless.
Meaning Keisuke's got it tough, as usual.
That bastard's still right on my tail.
A supercharger, huh? That was clever.
Even though we have the same setup that
uses air pressure to drive our turbines,
his also gets power supplied
directly from the crankshaft.
My system's greatest merit is that it gets power
directly proportional to increased RPMs.
With a turbocharger there's a differential,
or turbo lag, but not with this setup.
Even though a turbo gives you
more of an increase in power,
with this, you just step on the gas to get
regulated power, regardless of conditions!
If you're out on winding roads
with low average speed,
a supercharger will definitely give you
more fighting advantage than a turbo!
Incredible! They're going out
for a third race, huh?
Neither of them can seem to clinch it.
I guess that means their
skills are evenly matched.
It's because of the rain.
--Starting in five seconds! Four! Three! Two!
--It makes the rear car keep pace with the lead.
--One! Go!
--If they raced separately you'd
see a difference in their times,
but with these rules, sometimes the cars
just pull each other along like magnets.
I bet the two of them are tired by now, huh?
I'm sure they are,
but they're still concentrating.
Once you've realized you're tired,
you've already started to lose your
concentration, and that's dangerous.
It's why the moment that decides
the race is disappointingly short.
Dammit! I'm not gonna lose!
Now that it's come down to this,
it's a battle of motivation!
Some rich kid who doesn't worry
about money wouldn't understand,
but there's a drive and
willpower that money can't buy!
And havin' me win would make
things that much more dramatic!
This has turned into a
pretty incredible race, huh?
It sure has. They just keep racing in the
middle of this rain without any breaks.
I think Wataru is totally incredible!
Even on the hillclimb,
he doesn't lose an inch to the FD!
As someone who drives a
Levin too, I really admire him!
Admire him? My brother?
--Yeah!
--You shouldn't.
What's so great about him, anyway?
"What"? Well, everything!
He's cool, he's serious about cars...
The way he insisted on a Levin instead
of some new car is totally macho!
No, it's just that he doesn't have any money!
He's got no money, huh? Hey, neither do I!
I'm jealous... They're having a great time!
The Levin's movements have
started to become a little weird.
He must be tired, too. Maybe
it's time I try moving into action.
I'm gonna put as much
pressure on him as I can!
Dammit! He's trying to ramp up the
pressure, huh? I'm not falling for it!
I can't be the only one suffering through this.
Let's see who can last longer!
You finally showed up, huh? Hiding in
a corner somewhere doesn't suit you.
You came to support
Keisuke Takahashi, didn't you?
I'm sorry, Nobuhiko.
Don't worry about that. It's not
as if we're at war or anything.
Feel free to go ahead and
support whoever you like.
Being in the rain's got him
wobbling around that much, huh?
FRs sure are pieces of junk.
If I wanted to beat him,
I could do it any time I wanted.
Not that it would be a fair fight...
I feel like he's really on my tail.
I wonder why... If it's because I'm tired
and my pace has dropped, that's bad.
I've gotta really floor it!
This is bad. It's getting to
where I can't control it.
Does this mean I've almost
lost my ability to concentrate?
Humans can't sustain intense
concentration for long.
When pushed to the very limit,
about 30 minutes is the maximum.
Yeah, but...
Pro racers have to keep going
for two to three hours, right?
It may be a race, but it's not
as if they're going at 100%.
On the circuit, there are long
straightaways where one can relax.
So in that sense, there's no place
to relax on a winding public road.
In the rain, there is little visibility
and the road is slippery.
You can't let your guard down for a second.
What exactly happens when
your concentration is broken?
First, your concentration becomes dulled.
Your reflexes slow.
The smallest things cause stress.
You become unable to do two things at once.
When the end comes, it is disappointingly fast.
Good luck, my darling. Don't let him beat you!
I'll always be here for you, darling!
The rain's suddenly picked up.
It's really coming down now!
I can't see!
There should be a mid-speed section
up ahead that veers sharply to the left.
Dammit!
You all right?
Yeah. I stopped just short of the concrete wall.
Ah. You spun out on a good angle there.
One of my talents. This may
sound like an excuse, but...
I know where all the gutters on this course are,
and I can tell you how many there are.
But for just a second, I got distracted
by the switch for the windshield wiper
and that gutter spun me right out. All I
can say is, I just wasn't thinking straight.
Even I still can't believe it.
I guess that's what it is...
to have your concentration broken.
Wataru spun out. We lose.
It looks like Keisuke won!
We'd prepared ourselves
for an all-out victory, but...
This is very disappointing.
Indeed. If it weren't for this rain, I'm certain
you would have won the downhill.
Wataru...
Brother...
I lost.
We were utterly defeated. Project D...
And Ryosuke Takahashi! They're on
a completely different level from us.
Okay, we're moving out!
Be sure to pick up all your trash!
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie