You're wobbling a little.
I can't help it.
Yesterday's snow is frozen on the road.
I guess studless tires don't cut it.
What?!
What's up with that car?
It had studless tires, too.
Unbelievable.
Watch out! Watch it! Oh, no!
Not again! Go right, right!
Oh, no... Ouch!
- Sayuki?
- That hurt!
This snow is frozen solid.
You okay, Sayuki?
"Sentimental White"
This is so annoying.
We started snowboarding at the same time,
so why are you so good at it already?
I hate to admit it,
but other girls don't have your athletic talent.
It was the same when you
were learning how to drift.
You have great intuition
and develop so quickly.
It's Shingo!
Oh, Sayuki?
Long time no see!
What a coincidence to run into you here!
I never knew you snowboarded.
Yeah, sure!
Oh, really?
I know how to snowboard!
And Shingo always had
snot dripping from his nose
in elementary school!
Shut up!
Everyone teased him by
calling him "Drippy-Nose Shingo,"
so he turned bad and became a rebel racer!
Don't make stuff up, Sayuki!
I just had a cold that day. That's all.
Hey, Mako, don't you wanna
snowboard some more?
- What?
- Go right ahead.
I'll be talking to Shingo
about the good old days.
Hey, why don't you go with her?
Okay.
Thank you.
No problem.
What do you think of him?
He looks wimpy,
but he seems pretty normal
for a friend of yours.
How's his driving?
He's one of the faster
drivers of the Night Kids.
Of course, he's not nearly as fast
as "Impact Blue," Usui's fastest.
Anyway, she's too cute
not to have a boyfriend.
You should've set me up with her instead.
Don't be stupid!
You're not good enough for her.
By the way,
don't let them find out that
this is a blind date, okay?
She would kill me if she knew.
Don't worry.
By the way, what about you, Sayuki?
What?
Nakazato from the other night.
I think he has a crush on you.
You're good. When did
you start snowboarding?
- Last year.
- That's amazing.
Very few girls could go
that fast on this hard snow.
It's exciting and a lot of fun.
When I get into something,
I'm totally focused.
So, Mako, what do you
think of Shingo's friend?
I don't know.
He's pleasant, and seems
like the serious type.
- Is that it?
- What do you mean, is that it?
I just met him, so I don't really know.
Aha!
I sense some chemistry between them.
By the way,
I heard something interesting the other day.
Ryosuke Takahashi of the
Red Suns is recruiting racers,
including Akina's Eight-Six,
to build a new team.
I hear it'll be a special traveling team.
Is that true, Sayuki?
I admire them for thinking
of a concept like that.
They never stay in one place.
They always keep moving forward.
They're so awesome that I almost hate them.
They truly have charisma.
I wish I could see Takumi again.
I wonder how he's doing.
I bet he looks handsome.
I'm never wrong about things like that.
Yeah, sure, Sayuki.
Oh, man, I'm getting kind of fired up.
Anyway, the road on the way here
looked kind of nice.
There's no snow down at the bottom.
I was thinking the same thing.
Wanna check it out later?
God, we love racing, don't we?
Yeah.
I'm so bored.
The pass is snowy.
Keisuke...
Those who conquer winter conquer summer.
Our project won't start until this spring.
But we won't make any progress
if we just sit around all winter.
Go drive on the snowy road.
What?
Just clear your mind and drive
on the slippery, frozen road,
day in and day out.
You'll see the effect in the spring,
when you change back to high-grip tires.
Your senses will be sharper,
and your driving skills
will be dramatically refined.
Keisuke...
We'll create a new
unbeatable record at each pass
and build our legend.
Yeah.
The snow is not a handicap.
It's your best training partner.
Racers don't have an off season.
Right.
Studless tires don't grip as much.
But this is good training.
A corner is there, so you attack it.
That's the racer's instinct.
What's up with that car?!
That was a Sileighty.
Where did it come from?
Wow, the driver is very skilled!
How is it?
These are all one-pattern, mid-speed corners,
so it's boring.
I like Usui Pass the best.
Hello?
Hey, Shingo, what's up?
What?
They've been seeing each other?
Yeah, he was all excited.
I think they have a date today.
Oh, really? I had no idea.
That's good. Christmas is coming up soon.
Yeah. Talk to you later.
I wonder if Mako's many
years without a boyfriend
are finally coming to an end.
I think this SW20 is a very good car.
A two-seater is fun, but it's inconvenient.
I'm thinking of buying something
more practical next time.
Maybe a 4WD wagon.
Are you quitting racing?
I think so, yeah.
I'm not making any excuses,
but I think I've had enough fun.
When you're a beginner,
you just try your hardest,
and it's exciting to see yourself progress.
But when you get to a certain level,
you kind of see your limits.
You stop having goals and become less eager.
I guess that's how everyone grows out of it.
Well... I really don't think
one's goals disappear that easily.
Oh, yeah?
There was a time when I thought
I would quit racing by this summer.
But I had an opportunity to see
a much higher-level racer,
and I realized that there's much more to it.
I don't think I could be that stoic,
because I'm not trying to be a pro racer.
I'd like you to quit racing,
too, if that's possible.
It's very dangerous to race at a pass.
You're a girl, after all,
and what if you got into an accident?
I know no one can take away
your right to do what you want.
But if I were your boyfriend...
...I'd be too worried
to let you go to a pass every night.
There're so many other fun things to do in life.
It might suit you better to get
dressed up and go out during the day,
since you're so pretty.
I'm serious about this, Mako.
I've never liked anyone this much.
Please be my girlfriend.
I...
I'm flattered that you feel that way.
But we just met,
and this kind of feels too sudden.
I'm not asking for an answer right now.
Let's meet again in a week, on Christmas Eve.
Will you think about it until then?
Yes.
"Christmas Campaign"
You're in a good mood.
Do you have plans for Christmas?
No, no plans!
How about you, Iketani?
Of course not!
We're lonely drivers, right, Itsuki?
- I knew it.
- I don't have plans!
You guys are just too sad!
What's with the serious face?
What's on your mind?
I don't want to talk about it, even to you.
It's a bad habit of yours
to keep everything to yourself, you know?
I have a lot on my mind,
but mostly I'm wondering what I'm racing for.
I've never had a serious
conversation like this with you.
Do you think my vaguely
wanting to be a better racer
might seem strange to others?
It's not strange at all.
Did someone say something to you?
You're just too innocent and easily influenced.
We are who we are,
no matter what others say about us.
Yeah, you're right.
"Welcome to Cherry Park Lane"
Mako?
I'm sorry to have you come
out to a place like this
on Christmas Eve.
No, it's all right.
I need a favor.
Hold on a second!
I have no intention of racing you.
That's not it.
I want you to sit next to me.
What?
I usually have Sayuki sitting next to me.
This feels strange.
Okay, here we go.
She's good... no, amazing!
I had no idea.
You're way better than I thought you were.
Very few Night Kids can drive like that.
You may even be better
than Takeshi and Shingo.
I think I understand why
you had me ride with you.
This is your answer, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I thought about it long and hard.
You may think I'm a foolish girl,
but I can't shake my desire for racing.
I want to keep chasing after the people
who are running in front of me.
Even if I can't catch up with them for now,
I want to keep facing the same direction.
I'm so sorry.
I really was very flattered.
I understand.
Goodbye.
I don't know who they are,
but I'm so jealous
of the people she cares about right now.
Hey, where's Takumi?
Maybe he has a date.
Who knows what he's doing?
Let's have fun, just the three of us!
Yay! Merry Christmas to lonely drivers!
Hooray, hooray, hooray!
"Winter: Facing the Winter"
Faster and farther
More than I am today
I'll find that winding road someday
Where I can be more passionate
Where I can be brighter
The winding road is all that's real
The morning sparkles as I get dressed
And the world changes
Pushing away men for once
Shining brighter than a golden star
I can't sleep alone
My heart of glass says, "Yes, my love"
Faster and farther
Shinier than in memory
The winding road will begin here someday
Where I can be more passionate
Watching my dreams blossom
The winding road is all that's real
I can't sleep alone
My heart of glass says, "Yes, my love"
Faster and farther
Shinier than in memory
The winding road will begin here someday
Where I can be more passionate
Watching my dreams blossom
The winding road is all that's real