"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Takumi Fujiwara has been forced by his father,
Bunta, to deliver tofu every morning since
Takumi's first year of junior high school.
Though he reluctantly began driving at this
early age, without even realizing it, he gained
miraculous driving technique each day.
Then one day, while descending Mt. Akina upon completing his morning deliveries, Keisuke Takahashi of the Akagi RedSuns
appeared before him.
There's somebody.
It's not from our team.
Is it an MR2 or a 180?
Fine. You won't be in my mirror
after two more corners.
An Eight-Six?!
No fucking way!
My FD can't outrun an obsolete Eight-Six?
Am I having a bad dream or what?
I'm number two in the Akagi Redsuns!
He doesn't know
what's ahead?
After this slow right-hander,
there's a tight left corner.
If he doesn't slow down, he'll end up
at the bottom of the ravine!
As I thought.
He's going too fast.
He doesn't have enough room
to recover and slow down.
What the hell...?
Inertia drift?!
I don't believe this.
Did I just see the ghost of a
Road Racer who died here?
Aiming to be the fastest team in Gunma,
the RedSuns challenge the Akina SpeedStars.
Knowing that the 86 is driven by
Takumi Fujiwara,
a shocked gallery looks on
as the battle for revenge begins.
Go!
I won't hold back.
It's not my style to go full out on the
straightaway, but this is a time attack...
I won't see the Eight-Six
in my rear view mirror again.
What?!
He's gaining on me.
His car is getting closer.
No, it's not.
Something so absurd can't happen.
He caught me!
What's going on?
It's driving me crazy!
It's a Road Racer's worst disgrace
to be tailed by an underpowered car.
Shit!
What's happening?
It feels like my FD is slower than usual.
Did the secondary turbine stop?
He's not slowing down for the hairpin?!
What the hell is he thinking?!
What the hell was that...?
The racer who watched the battle was
Myogi Night Kids, Takeshi Nakazato.
Believing in the power of grip driving,
he challenges drifter Takumi and his 86
to a battle.
Can you keep up with my R?
He won't be able to follow me
with that overly active "crab walk."
Watching him up close,
his drift is almost an art form.
Four wheel drift at full throttle
with minimum counter steering...
I'm so impressed.
This is it.
This is the feeling.
This high tension of boiling blood...
This is a battle!
I'll push myself to the limit.
How much longer can
you keep up with me?
The Eight-Six's gonna overtake him.
Overtake him...?
But the inside is blocked.
How?
What?
From the outside?!
Don't screw around with me!
I won't let you pass from the outside!
Because I get too
close to the inside
the car misses the ideal line,
and the entry speed has to be slower!
Good, he's not gonna take the inside!
The Eight-Six disappeared!
It can't be...!
Takeshi's defeat pleases Shingo Shoji.
Aiming to be the Night Kids fastest driver,
and to defeat the 86 no matter what,
he uses an FF-favored
"Duct Tape Deathmatch" to his advantage.
You seem quite eager, but aren't you
forgetting something?
There you go.
Lucky...
I see. I've got this battle figured out.
The car can go faster
if I don't steer too much.
How can he...?
He's clearing corners with
minimum countersteering...
But I'm not as easy as Takeshi.
As long as I win, I don't care how.
Damn, it's gotta be luck.
Now I'm pissed.
He did that on purpose.
I won't lose to a lowlife
like you, no matter what!
No way.
The Eight-Six is gaining on me.
That's impossible!
I won't let you take the inside.
Is he going to hit me this time?
Dammit.
How could I be overtaken?
I don't get it!
If I lose, I'll be the
laughingstock of the team.
I'll keep my reputation by
ending this race with a tie.
The end of this battle...
...will be a double crash!
Mako and Sayuki are Usui's fastest in their Sileighty.
Since Mako has decided to retire as a racer,
to battle the 86 as her last racing memory.
So Takumi heads to Usui's pass
for his very first away battle.
They're fast.
Looks really bad.
Can I make it?
Not bad. He isn't
an ordinary Road Racer.
Otherwise we wouldn't
have any fun.
Mako, C-121 is near.
Let's settle this race.
No one has cleared the
corner at my entry speed.
No oncoming traffic.
Let's show off, Mako!
Okay.
Go!
That's impossible.
I realize now...
There's no way I can drive fast
if I watch my rear.
I won't look in the mirror again.
There are a few corners to go.
But I won't drop my guard.
I'll push harder and harder till the end.
For the pride of the best on Usui,
I won't let this be regrettable.
If you can't outrun him, there'll be
no place to settle the race.
I know.
The Eight-Six slowed down.
Why?
No, Mako!
Your entry speed's too fast!
Akagi's White Comet, Ryosuke Takahashi
sends out a challenge to Takumi.
However, Takumi can't decide what to do.
Later at Myogi Pass,
the battle of the Night Kids and Red Suns
has just begun.
Starting the countdown!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go!
He's tough.
The FD's fast in the corners.
I didn't expect anyone to keep up
with my R and I on Myogi.
He's started
steering hard.
Is he going to increase the pace
to try and outrun me?
If you do that on the downhill,
the tires will definitely lose grip.
It's started raining.
The goal is so close.
The beginning of the
rain is most dangerous.
When you skid, it happens
without any warning.
Now it's time to
settle this match!
Impossible! You won't be able
to turn at that speed!
That idiot's gonna
crash into the cliff!
The hill climb was interrupted by rain.
However, rain racing specialist
Kenta Nakamura of the Red Suns
gains the gallery's interest by
challenging Takumi to a downhill race.
I won't let you gain on me,
I'll keep pulling away.
I...is this the driving of a man who was lovesick
over a woman just a while ago?
I'm in my rhythm.
I'm in really good
condition today.
The legend of Akina's unbeatable
Eight-Six ends today.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six!
What the...?
It's impossible.
How did I get caught so easily
on the downhill in the rain?
No...
...this doesn't mean I've lost!
Having experienced many battles this summer,
Takumi has awakened to racing.
Finally, he departs to battle Ryosuke.
I'm surprised.
The Eight-Six's motion is totally
different from before.
He doesn't countersteer at the end
of his drift like before, but...
...the angle of the countersteer
right after the turn-in is smaller.
He has improved.
No good,
I can't shake him.
You're going too fast.
You've screwed up.
Dammit, turn!
How reckless.
A big power car can recover
by using its power...
...but you did it
with an Eight-Six.
I thought that he'd pull away, but surprisingly,
the gap hasn't widened much.
I still have a chance!
Well, even if the tires are a little worn,
it won't disturb my driving.
Should I try it?
Dad said there's another
way of using the gutter.
Alright, let's go!
What... did he do?!
There they are.
The FC's ahead!
Inside or outside?!
From the outside?!
The FC's drifting outward!
Incredible!
His speed's too fast for the
sharper curve at the exit!
Their lines are gonna cross!
Since Ryosuke's undefeated streak
had been broken by Takumi,
the infuriated Emperors decided to
challenge the 86 to a battle.
Though everyone said he couldn't win,
Takumi said he didn't want
to run away.
I'm gonna show you how good I am.
See that? I'll go full throttle, so that you'll
disappear from my rear view mirror.
So fast...
What a fast car.
Should I try the gutter run?
What the...?!
He's not far behind,
but right on my butt!
That's impossible!
It's so disgraceful that I can't pull
away from the Eight-Six...
I didn't expect the
Eight-Six to run this well.
This downhill race is tough.
Even if I use the gutter,
I'm slower at the exit.
I have no choice, but gutter run part two,
the exit-oriented use of the gutter.
Now!
I've won.
There's not much to go.
What the hell...?!
He's got the inside.
It's only a junker,
waiting to be scrapped!
Why is it so fast?
Takumi is unsatisfied with winning on Akina.
Since Sudo Kyoichi of team Emperor
called him out to Akagi,
and since he learned Natsuki's secret,
he was overcome with anger and sadness
and headed for Akagi.
Watch me, Ryosuke.
This battle is a challenge to you.
He's pushing me hard.
I'm like prey being chased by a hunter.
That Eight-Six is incredible!
He went by the guardrail so closely
that he touched the bushes!
Playtime is over.
It's time to overtake you.
You won't escape my counterattack.
It's gonna take the outside.
The Eight-Six is finished!
Not yet...
I'm not finished yet.
I can't shake him.
He's keeping up with me.
I'm impressed. He regained
his pace after he was passed.
You're incredible. With that
underpowered piece of junk...
...considering the acceleration difference
between the Evo and Eight-Six...
...he's turning
faster than I am.
Even if I gain in the corner...
...he pulls away so easily in
the short full throttle sections.
This is the difference in power?
It's time.
After the next corner,
I'll fully open the throttle.
I'll push myself to the limit as well.
You'll be finished in a second.
His driving changed...
It's fast, and
he's pulling away.
I can't catch him, can I?
No matter how hard I try?
Takumi's precious,
beloved 86's engine is blown.
He blames himself incessantly for it.
"There's a huge, gaping hole inside my heart..."
The next day, the long-awaited battle between
The RedSuns and team Emperor has begun.
It's over.
He's got the inside.
You're done for.
This is the end.
Shit.
Damn you!
Following this race is a heroic battle in which
a miraculous course record concludes the story.
Amidst the strangely high tension,
burning with revenge,
the Emperor's ace, Kyoichi, and the
RedSun's ace, Ryosuke, finally
begin their downhill race.
I never forgot that, Ryosuke.
And you should
also know that...
...this battle is for the sake of each of
our driving theories and beliefs.
Now, the 4WD and the misfiring system
will show off their true potential.
Ryosuke, I'll show you the result of
my past year's training.
What incredible potential it has.
I'm astonished seeing it.
Come on anytime, Ryosuke.
The tires are still fine,
and have a firm grip.
You've tuned that
car well, Kyoichi.
It pulls away if I accelerate
in a lower gear.
But I have a chance in
the high-speed corners.
It's weird that you
aren't doing anything.
Did you give up?
Not a chance.
He'll attempt to
overtake me somewhere.
Kyoichi, your fault is that you haven't
overcome the fear from your right side.
In short...
...you suck at right-handers.
What the...?
The FC took the outside!
Incredible. The Evo III is pinned
down and can't get ahead.
Damn, I can't take advantage of the
misfiring system or the 4WD's traction.
He did it!
He reversed it!
Unable to overcome the new
engine, Takumi finds Saitama's
fastest, Wataru Akiyama, before him.
Even with his race-prepped engine,
Takumi feels distant, spurring Wataru
to challenge him.
Let me observe you
thoroughly from behind...
...and see your true potential, which has
never been defeated in the Gunma area.
It's so difficult to drive here.
What's with this place?
What was that?
Was it just my imagination?
It was so hard until yesterday.
I can control it and
drive it as I like.
That's not the speed of a first timer.
I'm so thrilled.
There're many incredible
guys outside my area.
The Eight-Six is
finally accepting me.
I want to win. I've never felt
such a strong desire to win.
Anyway, I want to
win with this car.
As the conditions worsen,
he looks more skilled.
But he's human. The first to lose
his concentration will be the loser.
This is a match of how
long one can endure.
It's getting really tough,
but he must feel the same.
Even if there's a slight difference in our pace,
you can't overtake me on this course.
When you lose, it's always the chaser
who's been outrun by the leader.
What the...?
The landslide is smaller than before!
You...you can't be serious!
You're not supposed to
overtake on this course!
W...what a guy...
Ryosuke invited Takumi onto his new racing team,
but Takumi couldn't reply immediately.
So in order to test his newly reborn 86,
Takumi heads to Kyoichi's home course for a battle.
I see. It's a little faster.
Unlike a turbo, it's got the extended
acceleration of a mechanically tuned car.
But no matter how you tune the car,
it's an Eight-Six after all.
I've got 350 HP.
No matter what kind of car
I race against, I can't lose here.
Just like Ryosuke rules in Akagi,
I'm the emperor here.
I won't miss my target
once I aim at it!
He's right on my tail.
I just have to push myself
as much as possible.
The slope will level out soon,
so the Eight-Six will lose speed.
You won't be able to get away
from my counterattack.
A bridge?
The goal is near?!
The steep slope is over.
You'll need real power now.
I'll show you the winning
formula of Sudo Kyoichi.
An optical illusion makes
the road look narrower...
...and you can't approach
the outside enough.
Once I poke my nose
out just a bit...
The third bridge...!
The inside and outside positions
will be reversed on the bridge.
It's my usual finish.
I see it.
Go!
No way!
Do you want to die?!
You're going too fast!
You can't turn!
It will turn.
Please turn, my Eight-Six!
Can I?
Kyoichi had been Kai Kogashiwa's target, so Kai
decided to defeat Takumi instead.
It turns out, Kai's father and Bunta used
to be the fiercest of rivals.
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one...
Go!
It's fast.
That's not an ordinary Eight-Six.
Fine, that's what I want, too.
I'll outrun your fast Eight-Six.
There're so many
leaves tonight.
And because of the wind, there are
piles of them here and there.
If I go over them,
I'll instantly lose control.
It's so hard to drive.
I'd better let the car drift itself.
You're tough.
A cheap trick won't work.
The timing for trying that is important.
I have a bad feeling.
He's going to do something.
Now!
Once you let me get ahead,
you have no chance.
I've won this race!
At this rate, the gap
will widen more.
Go!
What a guy!
He managed to jump
on the first try!
He's got all the senses
of a mountain pass driver.
I can see the edge of asphalt
through the dried leaves.
Now, that's the last chance!
What the...?!
H...how did he accelerate like that?!
What the hell happened?!
Dammit all!
Here they come!
Who's ahead?!
They're side by side!
Shit, if one misses the line,
both'll hit the concrete wall!
With graduation in mind, Natsuki is eager to
make up with Takumi.
Around that time, her previous boyfriend Miki
takes Natsuki on a drive in his car.
Natsuki, seeking help, decides to call
Takumi, who rushes to Mount Akina.
Hello...
Takumi, help me...lake...
Hello?
Is this Mogi?
Where are we going?
Be prepared.
I won't let you go
home until I'm satisfied.
Takumi!
No way!
Takumi has come for me.
I wondered what his car is, but it's
a junker from the distant past.
Just three more curves, and
his car will be far behind.
How could he?!
Impossible!
How could a junker like
that tailgate a 4WD?
If you look away,
you'll have an accident.
How about this?
Not good...
It won't turn!
Please, stay away!
Takumi!
Takumi asks Ryosuke to battle him.
By racing Ryosuke on his home course
he hopes to find the answer
to whether or not he should join the new team...
A battle with me?
Yeah.
Please.
I feel like I can find my answer.
Okay, let's begin.
Go!
I can feel him so strongly.
You must be concentrating on
driving as fast as you can.
Show me your driving.
Awesome.
So exciting!
It's great!
The FC is incredible, but
the Eight-Six is awesome, too.
I see his aura in his driving.
Wonderful.
He's so wonderful.
He's improved drastically
since the battle on Akina.
Winning or losing is
irrelevant in this battle.
As long as they drive at their
full potential, that will be fine.
I'm envious that they
can drive so seriously.
It's strange.
When I drive
with you...
...I discover something new in my driving,
which is supposedly complete.
I've never had so much fun in a battle.
All my worries are gone.
I just have to follow him.
Takumi decides to join the ranks of Project D.
From now on, Takumi, who has shown progress
which impressed even Ryosuke, will be involved in...