Bring it back, hey, rock-n-roll!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Life goes on, I was content
With just a little hope
I waited, and someone
Decided the future for me
(Just get you get you back and bring it back on)
How small one is, bust it up!
(Here we go, 1, 2)
Move it up and break it!
Right now, let's run as far as our dreams
(Bring back, yo, it's the right time,
hey boy, rock-n-roll)
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a rumble!
"Gunma 55 O"
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop (Private Vehicle)"
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a rumble!
A close stage (Oh, yeah!)
"Narrow Curve"
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
Wavering not a single millimeter
(Check it out, come on!)
The truth is, there's really not much you
must protect (Give it up, yo! Give it up, yo!)
"Left Curve"
Let's act a little tough and
gamble it all, play the game!
"Narrow Curve"
Let's act a little tough and
gamble it all, play the game!
Let's gamble, hey jumbo
Now shake your bum and do the rumble
Get psyched and rip down that three-lined road
Arrival, move, a gathering of three
Everyone is sleeping soundly
Even if they go on and on about how
much of a pain the engine noise is...
That's all.
Say, you wanna go by a coffee shop?
Sounds good! You wanna come too, Natsuki?
Oh, sorry! I have to work.
Huh? Natsuki's got a job?!
- Who woulda thought?
- Let's go eat, man. Eat!
Huh? You're hungry already?
Hey! Takumi!
Oh, Itsuki.
How is it these days?
What're you talking about?
The car, man, the car! What else but the car?!
Ah. It's in good shape.
It's gotten to where it feels good to ride.
Huh. And after you'd said how hard it
was to drive after changing the engine...
It's changed dramatically
since installing the tachometer...
My car is really fast now.
Shoot! I wish I could say
something like that, just once!
Hey, let me ride shotgun next time
you're at the mountain pass.
Fine, but... It's scary.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Don't go passing out.
Hey! What a thing to say, you jackass! Kick!
Takumi...
Thank you very much!
Huh? What're you looking at, Takumi?
Um, do you mind if I ask you something?
What is it?
How did you get to be so good with machinery?
How can I put this?
I've fiddled around with cars
and stuff since high school.
Buying one of your own and working on that
makes it more and more interesting.
Before I knew it, I'd turned
into a bit of a machinery nut.
Takumi, you've really gotten
interested in machinery, huh?
It's just...
I finally get it, if only a little.
For example, installing a tachometer
and revving up an engine's RPMs
can suddenly change a car's whole character.
I never thought machinery could
change the way a car runs like that.
There's a limit to what a driver
can do in terms of handling,
so I'm convinced that if you want to get fast,
you'll have to pick up all
different kinds of knowledge.
Otherwise, it isn't going to happen.
Takumi's seen the light!
What a tremendous development!!
That it is. It wasn't long ago, up till summer,
that he didn't even know the term "Eight-Six."
Even so, since his dramatic
debut on the Akina downhill,
it's been one victory after another, huh?
I remember we all had to work
hard to drag him into racing...
That's right. But now, even those
have become good memories...
I... hate racing battles.
The hairpin is coming!
But he's not slowing down!
What's that?!
"Gunma 37"
Besides, being forced to accept
challenges just isn't my thing.
What?! From the outside?!
I'll do your Duct Tape Death Match!
I'll do anything!
It's faster not to steer
too much when cornering...
He passed me... That's incomprehensible!
This is my battle, right? And I...
I'm going to race it for myself.
We can't win. We chose a
monster as our opponent.
He is improving in every race.
Uh, I don't think that I'm
a faster driver or anything like that.
Takumi Fujiwara... You were very fast.
See you around.
That Takumi... Every time
he races, he gets better, huh?
Mm. He seems especially motivated recently.
He's really come a long way quickly.
Huh? A white FC?
Welcome!
For starters, I wonder if you'd
please fill it up with high octane.
Yessir!
It's him... the White Comet
of Akagi, Ryosuke Takahashi.
"High-Octane Vehicle"
Putting in a full tank of high octane!
There's something I'd like to discuss...
Can we meet up after work?
Meet... with me?
No good? I can come back
later if you don't have time.
No, I-I'm not... I'm free after work.
In that case, please call me once you're done.
This is my cell phone number.
- Okay...
- I'll be waiting.
"Gas"
Thank you very much!
Hey, Takumi!
What the heck was that all about?
A talk with Ryosuke Takahashi?!
I don't know!
What are you gettin' all red-faced about?
Huh?! I-I'm not...!
I don't really get it myself, but...
I get all revved up when
that guy comes nearby.
An expeditionary racing team?!
That's right.
We assemble a team of the
best of the best in this area
and head to mountain passes
outside our prefecture
to challenge the local drivers.
We make new records at each of
the local courses, creating a legend,
and then disband.
Unfortunately, I have been left with little time.
I believe one year from now will be my limit.
No matter what, I want to have
seen the end of this game by then.
To get straight to the point...
I desire your technique!
Won't you join our team,
and participate as a driver?
M-Me?!
You are the man who put
an end to my winning record.
Of course, because this is
my game, should you participate,
I believe I can reward you as is appropriate.
"Reward"?
You have made it this far racing
on talent and sense alone.
But soon, you should find
yourself coming up against a wall.
Clearing that wall, heading toward
the area that lies farther beyond,
will require driving supported
by precise theoretical concepts.
In order to get faster,
you will require knowledge.
Have you not begun to notice this yourself?
I can understand...
...because you are a type of
driver much like my brother.
Like Keisuke?
To couple instinctive talent
with theory is to be unstoppable.
I will teach you that which you most require.
And it is best learned while
experiencing racers' local courses.
Do this with us.
You don't have to answer now. Think it over.
O-Okay.
I await a favorable response.
You were invited into some new team
Ryosuke Takahashi's making?!
He says it'll be active for just
one year before disbanding...
Some kind of special team that'll
be going outside our prefecture.
Th-Th-That's awesome!
It's super crazy big news!
I wanna hurry up and tell lketani!!
Look, please don't turn this
into some big deal, all right?
I'm still not close to deciding.
What's there to decide?!
I mean, my first race was this past summer...
It hasn't even been six months yet.
It's only recently I've even
become interested in cars...
I'm nervous whether someone like me
could make it as a team member.
What are you talking about?
Since your first year in middle school,
you've raced the mountain pass
delivering tofu, right?!
You'll be fine!
Aargh! I'll do odd jobs or anything,
just let me in, too!
This is awesome! It's too awesome!!
Hey! All you rivals of mine!
More and more, you'll be left in the dust!
Anyway, I've been all mixed up
over this since yesterday.
I feel like before I join that team,
there are a couple of things
that I'm going to have to do...
Incredible! That's what
Ryosuke Takahashi had to say?
Right?! That's some
super-awesome big news, huh?
Yeah! Ryosuke Takahashi represents
the charisma of us street drivers...
The king of the mountain pass,
winning battle after battle!
It was Takumi who put a stop to
that record of consecutive wins,
so if the two of them paired up,
it would make a powerful team, but...
I have mixed feelings about this.
Takumi is the hero of our Akina Speed Stars.
Don't you feel like that's
being taken by the Red Suns?
I think that Takumi should spend
more and more time out there.
I want him to grow, really improve himself.
Just think of him being "on loan"
to Ryosuke Takahashi for a year.
An expedition outside our prefecture, eh?
Long ago, we considered that as well.
He should go.
Takumi isn't the type to be
content with just the Akina pass.
A blown engine means defeat.
Hello?
This is he.
Um, sorry. This doesn't have to do
with our talk yesterday, but...
Well, maybe it's not completely unrelated.
There's something I'd like you to tell me...
The leader of Team Emperor?
You mean Kyoichi Sudou?
Yes. Do you know where I could
go to meet this "Sudou" person?
Kyoichi is an old acquaintance of mine.
I could get hold of him
at any time, if I so wished...
I...
I thought that if I had the chance,
I'd like to race him again.
I see. And where do you intend to do this?
I thought I'd go over to his neck of the woods.
Kyoichi's home course is
the Iroha Slope in Nikko.
To do it there would be to face a
powerful enemy, and no small feat.
He may not look it, but he quite dislikes losing.
I like his idea of diving
straight into enemy territory...
It is a quality he will certainly
need in order to become faster.
"Tochigi Prefecture"
Hello, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hello! Um, this is Takeuchi...
Yeah. Takumi?
Nah, he's not here.
He's not?! So he went out in the car?
Um, where to?
I don't know nothin' about that.
"Steep hill roads ahead
Use engine braking
Beware of brakes overheating"
This is the Iroha Slope, huh?
Looking at the map, there were
two roads with the same name,
which was weird, but actually
coming here, I get it now.
There are separate, one-way roads
for going up and coming down...
So there are even roadways like this one, huh?
Still, this downward route is amazing!
"Danger"
- Hey, that car!
- Yeah!
Huh? What'd you say?
H-Hey, there!
- Is that?
- The Eight-Six of Akina!
"Panorama Rest House"
What was that?!
I see. Understood.
Kyoichi, we've gotten word from down below.
A car resembling "the one" will
arrive here at the top shortly!
Big brother! Are you here?
Keisuke? What's happened?
We've gotten word...
Akina's Eight-Six is at Iroha Slope!
Ah. As expected.
Huh? You knew about this?
I suppose.
Anyway, I wonder if that guy's
after a revenge race.
I imagine he is not concerned
with merely winning or losing.
He probably...
...went to Iroha Slope with
the intent of testing something.
He's here!
What's this? The Eight-Six
sounds different from before...
This was some while ago, but...
...I heard that a certain two-bit
repair shop in Shibukawa
had received a strange sort of
engine via "unofficial" routes.
A strange engine?
While it no longer exists,
long ago a touring car race
called Group A was in full swing.
Do you remember it?
No way! It's a Group A engine?!
In all likelihood, that's exactly what it is.
If it's the TRD engine that was
installed in Group A's AE101s,
it's not just an NA 1.6-Liter engine,
it's a high-performance unit
that can go over 11,100 RPMs,
squeezing out 240 horsepower.
It was probably de-tuned for street use
and placed under the hood
of the Akina Eight-Six.
But even if it is a racing engine,
there's going to be a limit
to how much power you can
squeeze out of an NA 1.6-Liter unit.
Correct.
You repaired the Eight-Six, eh?
Yes.
Do you remember what I told you at Akagi?
"We'll race again when you have a
machine capable of competing with me."
I believe those were my words.
This isn't the same car it was before.
And it's a good car for me.
Will you not race against it?
Fine. For me, this battle
has been left unresolved...
Here I shall finish it!
What I'm concentrating on isn't horsepower...
It's turning!
Installing that engine will result
in dramatically improved handling.
His cornering, which already
boasted exceptional turns...
...will now be even more polished!
It may allow for an equal fight
against Kyoichi's misfiring system.
The race will be a single downhill stretch.
We descend to the bottom,
where the road crosses three bridges.
The goal is on the other side of the last bridge.
You go first, and I'll follow.
If you can make it all the way to the
goal without letting me pass, you win.
But if I pass you, I win. Sound good?
But that!
If you want to say it's unfair,
that would be an insult toward me.
Don't forget, the Iroha Slope
is my home course.
Without a handicap like that,
this would be no contest.
If there's anything you want to say,
I'll hear it once we're done.
Let's begin!
The downward route of the Iroha Slope
is just like a Gymkhana course,
but with steep slopes added.
No one can get the better of Kyoichi here!
He has techniques honed in Gymkhana,
and he's a genius at low-speed cornering!
I see. He has gotten a little faster, eh?
An increase in acceleration
particular to mechanical tuning
and different from that of a turbo.
However, no matter what
tuning was performed...
...it's still an Eight-Six.
I have 350 horsepower!
"Curve"
That is a super high-rotation engine...
Wiseass! Does he think a modification like that
can compete with my misfiring system?!
No matter what car challenges me,
I cannot lose here!
As with Ryosuke in Akagi,
here I am the emperor!
I won't let my prey escape!
He's staying right on me...
Anyway, all I can do is go all-out!
This slope will soon level out...
The Eight-Six will slow down there, too.
There will be absolutely no
escape from my counterattack!
"Danger"
The greatest pitfall of this course
is not being able to suddenly switch from
the incredibly long slow section
to the high-speed side!
Even the most skilled racers fall into this trap!
This isn't about technique;
it's about instinctual sensitivity!
No one can suddenly switch
and adapt to the high-speed side!
Save for one exception...
The White Comet of Akagi, Ryosuke Takahashi!
Only he...
A bridge?!
Is the goal coming up soon?
The first bridge! This is the end
of the steep-gradient section.
From here, this will require all-out power.
I will show you...
the Kyoichi Sudou-style winning equation!
The second bridge...
And a high-speed right corner,
as if one had been
shot from the top of the
bridge from a catapult.
For senses accustomed to
the slow-velocity section,
it's frightening enough
to make your heart leap out!
An optical illusion, the road seems to close in,
leaving no room on the outside.
If I just slightly nudge my way in there...
This race is mine!
The third bridge.
On that bridge, the outside
becomes the inside.
For me it's the same finish as always!
The moment I pulled
alongside him, it was all over!
I see it! Do I go?
Go!
What?! Idiot! Does he want to die?!
He's going too fast! He can't turn!
Turn! Come on, turn! My Eight-Six!
Can he make it?!
In today's race,
the quick left turn going into
the third bridge was everything.
A normal Eight-Six couldn't
make that turn there...
Or rather, a person with normal
nerves wouldn't plow in like that.
Were you sure of what you were doing?
I... I start to "see" the road.
Earlier, too, I could clearly see the line
that my car's outer tires would be following.
I thought I could just barely make it,
so I eased up on the brakes
and went as-is.
I can't really explain it,
but I've always been this way.
Once I've "seen" a road, I can just drive it.
I see...
It's a strange car, that one.
It's not a car that just anyone
can drive, I'll give you that.
It's a good car.
It is?
I lost. Let's meet again if we have the chance.
I'm really happy, but... I don't feel like I won.
Maybe it was a draw, if you look at it fairly...
Hey, Takumi! Get up!
You were out pretty late
last night. Where'd you go?
Iroha Slope.
Say, Pops, going forward,
there's probably going to be more of this.
Getting back just in time and
going straight out to deliver...
I think there are going to be times like that.
If ya make it back in time to deliver,
I've got no complaints.
More to the point... Here.
I don't want ya dozin' off
and wreckin' the tofu.
Drive careful so you don't spill the water.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
All right, I'm off.
Keisuke...
I heard. You went up against
an Evo III at Iroha Slope.
You already know about that?
Those sorts of stories get spread around fast.
It'll be winter soon.
Our expeditionary plan will start in earnest
in spring of next year, once the
icy road season has finished.
You're coming, right? With our new team?
My big brother's time limit is one more year.
So I want to give everything
I've got during that year
and race for my big brother's dream.
In this grand game he's so passionate about...
...what sort of catharsis will be at the ending?
I want to know that! If you let
my big brother teach you,
after one year, I'm sure you'll be crazy good.
But I'm gonna get to a level
far above even that.
Our race will wait until then...
But in one year's time,
I'll beat you and attempt to go pro!
I'm going to be a big, major-league name.
Come with us.
Let's do this, together.
Incredible...
What incredible people!
What? Is that for real?
It's for real! He totally took on
Sudou of Team Emperor
for a downhill battle on Iroha Slope!
And what was the outcome?
Takumi says it was a draw.
A draw?
Yes. But friggin' Takumi,
he looked content with that.
I don't doubt it. Sudou's speed is renowned...
...and what's more, this was
on the enemy's home course.
That being said, the Eight-Six's new engine
may be an absolute devil of a thing.
Takumi may well have awesome technique,
but having enough power to
go up against a Lancer Evo...
I think that makes this a serious matter.
A serious matter?
Yes. For the first time,
Takumi has acquired a machine
at which he can throw
everything he's capable of.
Perhaps the true legend of
Akina's unbeatable Eight-Six...
...is only about to begin.
Welcome!
High octane. Uh... 20.
Putting in 20 liters of high octane!
Hey, hang on a minute.
Make that 15.
Are you the Eight-Six of Akina?
No, I'm not. And you are?
I came 'cuz I heard you can
meet Akina's Eight-Six here.
I'm Kogashiwa.
"Tochigi"
Kogashiwa, he said? It can't be!
Here it comes!
Hyaa!
Aww, jeez!
- Hyaa!
- Okay!
Don't go there, it's dangerous!
Order in! Fast Burger, small fries,
and iced tea, no sugar...
One of each!
Okay!
He's not here yet, but he should be by 5:00.
He said he had somewhere to go...
Okay. I'll come by again.
Sir!
You said "Kogashiwa" just now, didn't you?
I apologize if I'm mistaken, but...
Could that be as in Ken Kogashiwa?
Ken Kogashiwa... is my father.
Thank you very much!
"Gas"
Come on manager, please tell me
about that customer just now!
What was that about?
You mean about Ken Kogashiwa?
Yeah! Just who is he?
It'd been a long time since
I'd thought of that name.
How many years, I wonder...
Twenty years? No, easily more than that.
Back then, Bunta and I were
running various mountain passes...
...and Ken Kogashiwa was a
rally racer working the Iroha Slope.
At the time, he was Bunta's greatest rival.
Anyway, he had a crazy racing style.
He went up against Bunta several times,
and in the last big race, Bunta won.
We didn't hear a single
thing from him after that.
Bunta Fujiwara, legendary
racer and Takumi's father.
And this is his rival...
His son grew up so fast, and
now he's come to meet Takumi...
That was some pretty good driving.
What was that just now?! What happened?
I felt a jolt just by going past him!
I still don't get it... But it was awesome!
A challenge to a race?
That's the sort of feel it had to it.
Yeah! And I think it was an SW20
with a Tochigi license plate.
That car's a mid-engine, so it
has formidable racing power.
"Mid-engine"?
"Now accepting card applications!"
It means the engine is
located behind the driver.
In normal cars it's in front of the driver's seat,
but in a mid-engine, it's opposite.
In a rear-axle drive,
having the engine to the rear
makes the tires less likely to slide
when your foot's on the gas.
That gives it the acceleration
advantage when coming out of corners.
Having that heavy engine
centrally located in the car frame
has the benefit of increased maneuverability.
F-1 machines are all mid-engines, too.
H-He's here!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Yes, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Kogashiwa? Ken Kogashiwa?
This is unexpected!
How many years has it been
since I've heard your voice?
So you're the Akina Eight-Six?
It seems you beat Sudou of
Team Emperor at Iroha Slope.
Sudou was my target!
The locals said that loud,
sputtering Evo III was unbeatable...
But I was confident I would defeat it!
I was so close, and you swooped
in and stole all my thunder!
That's why my target has shifted
automatically over to you.
I want to challenge you!
Well? What's your answer?
I don't feel I beat the Evo III,
but after a story like that,
I don't intend to run away!
I can't say when, but before snow falls,
I will definitely go to Iroha Slope again!
Fine, understood. I look
forward to it with pleasure.
My name is Kai Kogashiwa. And you are?
Takumi Fujiwara. Sorry,
but I'm working right now, so...
Ah, my apologies. Oh, and one more thing.
Were you out racing on Akina earlier?
No...
I see. Then, no matter.
Huh?
What're you doing, Pops?
Takumi...
Someone came to meet you today, didn't he?
Driving a squat-looking car called an SW20...
How did you know that?
Do you plan to race him?
Yeah.
I hate running away from a challenge.
You... would lose.
Dad, I went to where
Akina's Eight-Six is yesterday.
Is that so? You're finally going
to challenge Fujiwara's son?
You know about that, Dad?
Yeah, there's a bit of a backstory there...
Kai, there is a good strategy
for beating the Eight-Six!
- See ya!
- Okay, see you tomorrow.
Takumi!
Come on Takumi, don't ignore me.
I want to talk to you about
something. Meet me later.
Why tell me?
We're friends, aren't we?
"Friends"?
Takumi, you told me before that
it's not as if we're dating, right?
S-So that makes us friends, right?
And if we're friends, then you can
help me with some advice, right?
Takumi, wait! Meet with me, please!
I... I'm busy.
Takumi!
Hey, when are you thinking
about going to Iroha Slope?
Once you decide to do something,
sooner is better, right?
It's not as if delaying it will change anything...
That's why I'm going tonight.
You're joking, right? Are you serious?!
I mean it.
Tomorrow's Saturday, so it's
only a half day at school...
I'll probably be all right even if
I don't sleep too much tonight.
When you make up your mind,
you don't mess around, do you?
Anyway, what are you gonna do?
About the new team.
Yeah...
You're joining, right?
Have you already told them?
Not yet.
Not yet?!
It looks like the team's not going
to really get moving till spring.
I've got a bit of time till then.
There's a lot for me to think about.
Think about?
My heart's in it, but it's just so intimidating.
Ryosuke and Keisuke are incredible people.
They have such firm senses of purpose...
Me, I just sort of want to go fast, that's it.
A sense of purpose, huh?
You going?
Yeah.
Aah. It's pretty tough over there.
I'll give you one piece of advice.
Huh? This is unexpected!
Just shut up and listen.
I'm only gonna say this once.
You can trap him at the area
of the last bridge. By then...
...he's sure to be in front of you.
You can't know that, can you?!
Good!
Listen here, Kai.
You're up against Fujiwara's son.
He's bound to be incredibly skilled.
Winning this race will require
both strategy and technique.
I will tell you the strategy
for beating Fujiwara's son.
First, let him get ahead of you.
Are you nuts?! That idiot
"strategy" can go screw itself!
If you let someone who may
be faster go in front of you,
then of course you're gonna lose!
Think clearly, and you'll see that
overtaking him is just impossible!
To be sure, a standard
approach would be of no use...
That is exactly what makes this a strategy!
At the Iroha Slope, sometimes a line appears
that is even farther in than the corner line.
You're telling me I should follow it?!
You're okay with that, Dad? Whatever
happens to the car ain't my fault!
Just do it. Then, overtaking him
will be, to use a boxing metaphor,
a win by knockout!
This time, make sure anyone who
sees will know it's a clear win!
Listen Kai, set him up after the midway point.
Till then, whatever else, just keep up with him.
"Tochigi Prefecture"
Under his dad's gifted tutelage,
he started doing karts as a kid,
winning who knows how many races.
What's a legit racer like
that doing on the streets?
Who knows? Before that,
he'd apparently been the fastest
to do the Iroha Slope on a motorcycle.
Oh, that's right. There's an
Emperor named Seiji lwaki, right?
He rode a white Evo IV...
Oh, that bastard who had his
hair done up in back, right?
When Team Emperor invaded the Gunma area,
he beat everyone single-handed, right?
It seems that same lwaki was
recently rather soundly beaten
by that SW.
You again?!
I have no intention of going up
against you all tonight, lwaki.
I just thought I'd give you a brief heads-up.
A heads-up?
Tonight, I'll be racing the
Eight-Six of Akina here.
What?!
It won't do for you to
keep losing to outsiders...
So I'll put a stop to him, Sudou.
- Bastard!
- It's an interesting match, don't you think?
Akina's Eight-Six vs. Kogashiwa,
graduate of kart racing.
What shall be the result?
I'm quite eager to know.
Thanks for coming. Do you not
need to take a look at the course?
I already have. I got here early, so I did a lap.
Then I will explain the rules.
We start at the same time.
When you've completely crossed the
third bridge, you've crossed the goal line.
Whoever gets there first wins.
You good with that?
Then let's begin.
There's no mistake...
This Eight-Six is the Panda Trueno
I passed in Akina before.
Meaning that the person
behind the wheel then...
...was the guy who beat my dad,
Bunta Fujiwara. And this is his son.
I didn't really "get" it when I
met him at the gas station...
...but now I feel it.
This guy is fast!
What a thrill this has become... I have to do it!
Okay. Understood.
It looks like it'll start soon.
Understood.
Ryosuke...
I heard there's an interesting
race to be seen here, so I came.
Do as you like.
The wind is strong tonight...
It may be dangerous.
Great piles of dried leaves
are sure to be on the streets.
At the critical moment,
what decides this competition...
...may, of all things, be these leaves.
The whimsy of a fallen leaf, eh?
Takumi! What do you think?
Please don't get your hopes up too high.
You don't have a plan?
Didn't your father say anything?
Yeah, he did, but... It was just nonsense.
Hey, give me a break!
The only thing to do is go all-out!
Do your best, Takumi!
You can whup him, I'm sure of it!
Okay, here goes!
Five... Four... Three...
Two... One...
Go!
Whoa, awesome! The Eight-Six really took off!
Takumi's so fast!
Incredible! The mid-engine should have
the advantage at the starting dash...
The Eight-Six's new engine
is incredible after all!
He's so fast! This is no ordinary Eight-Six.
It has more power than a 2-liter 3S!
My dad said that letting him go ahead
and then overtaking him
would be a knockout victory.
Good! That's fine by me, too.
I'll overtake that "fast" Eight-Six
from behind and show them all!
"Reduce Speed"
I'll overtake that "fast" Eight-Six
from behind and show them all!
Okay, understood.
The Eight-Six has been in front since the start.
That Kogashiwa dude is nothing but talk, huh?
Even you couldn't capture the Eight-Six.
If he let it go first,
his non-turbo SW has no chance!
I don't know about that.
I had absolute faith in my counter
strategy just before the goal...
In that respect, I can't say
that I didn't let my guard down.
So?
I avoided unseemly tactics,
and tried to run a clean
race with no funny business.
That pride is what dug my grave.
If Kogashiwa runs an all-out dirty race,
he has a chance at victory.
What are you talking about?
Put simply, a line. There is a special line
for overtaking a car that's ahead of you,
right here on the Iroha Slope!
Kogashiwa used to race karts,
so he'll use a left-footed brake.
With his right foot still on the gas,
putting his left on the brake
will shift load to the front,
eliminating understeer.
This way, he can go forward at full throttle!
On a unique pass like this,
there's bound to be things only
a local would know about, huh?
I think Kogashiwa has been
considering various strategies...
Takumi has the disadvantage.
But long ago, Takumi's dad raced
Kogashiwa's here and won, right?
Yeah. I thought he'd give some
advice based on the experience...
...but Takumi just showed up half-cocked.
That Takumi... He's in trouble.
There are a lot of leaves out tonight...
What's more, the wind
has blown them into piles.
Going over one of those
would send you flying...
This will be difficult.
Still, these conditions should be
harder for the Eight-Six up ahead.
He doesn't know where
or when he's going to slide.
This is hard to race!
Instead of just sliding,
maybe I should make it slide.
I should hurry and spin the rear
tires out, and drift all four of them!
What's he doing?!
He plowed right into the pile!
Drifting on a road surface
made easy to slide on, eh?
You're something else, Takumi Fujiwara.
Half-assed tricks won't work on you.
During the hairpins at the Iroha Slope,
sometimes a line appears
that is even farther in than the corner line.
Where should I spring that trap?
Timing will be critical!
Yes, this is the 33rd corner.
The sound of their exhaust
is getting very loud!
They will be at this hairpin soon!
"Curve"
Is getting very loud!
They will be at this hairpin soon!
Okay. Give me the blow-by-blow
once they're there.
- It will soon begin.
- Huh?
I have a bad feeling. I don't really know what,
but some trap is about to spring!
I can't wait anymore! Dad, I can go now, right?!
This sensation, it's all tingly...
Something is coming!
The trap will be at the 33rd corner ahead!
They're here!
They're here, sir! The Eight-Six is in the lead!
Here!
What is it? What's happened?
What? The SW went even
farther in than the in line?
What was that?! It overtook the Eight-Six?
The Eight-Six was overtaken?
A special local move, eh?
Well played, Kogashiwa.
What, the SW pulled ahead of
the Eight-Six? At the 33rd corner?!
Hey, this has turned into one incredible race!
How did he pull it off at a hairpin like that?
- Did you hear?
- This will be a tight race.
Takumi!
Don't think badly of me.
The line farther in than the
corner line is drawn in mid-air!
It's a hairpin curve particular to Iroha Slope,
which has great height differential.
That's what makes it possible!
This is a local race that breaks all the rules!
This race is mine!
I'll lose! At this rate, I'm going to lose!
What do you think, big brother?
There are 11 hairpins remaining.
The outcome is not yet certain.
What do you mean, Ryosuke?
Kyoichi, this has unfolded
just as you said it would.
However, don't you think
the trap came too soon?
A trap sprung too early
gives the opponent a chance
to recover from the
psychological damage inflicted.
I see them! They're now at the 37th corner!
At this rate, he'll just get
farther and farther ahead!
Shoot! This guy just won't quit.
Fine. Guess I'll do another corner!
He took off!
Go!!
Unbelievable! He cleared the jump in one go!
It's like he's got his finger
on the pulse of the road!
But once I've been let out in front,
you've got no chance!
I'm gonna race like this right toward the goal!
"Hokkai Ramen"
"Takahashi"
A racing line against
which there's no defense?!
One draft beer, please.
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell Takumi about that?
Coming down Iroha Slope, there's a
bridge and a tunnel at the end, right?
- Yeah...
- I told Takumi,
"If you challenge him, that last spot will
be the only place to get the drop on him."
And I said when he gets there,
he's sure to be behind.
His face told me he wasn't gettin' it...
I wonder if he understands by now.
You gave him some advice
on how to pull ahead?
In a sense.
If he can understand what I told him...
...he's got about a 50%
chance of getting ahead.
What the heck, just 50%?!
That's low!
Of course it is. His opponent
will be racing at full speed.
Bunta, this time it will be
your turn to taste defeat!
He's really good! Being overtaken
and looking at him from behind...
...I can see that clearly.
We're about the same speed
on the straight-aways,
but his corners are incredibly fast!
It's taking everything just to keep up...
Fat chance of overtaking him!
At this rate, I'm gonna lose,
just like my dad said.
Come to think of it, what was it my dad said?
You can trap him at the area of the last bridge.
By then, he's sure to be in front of you.
You can't know that, can you?!
Yes, I can know that.
All right, this is the important part,
so shut up and listen.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
At this time of year, the brush
along the roads of Iroha Slope
starts to dry out. That's your chance.
Starts to dry out. That's your chance.
If ya start creepin' up
on him at the first bridge,
the entrance at the second one
will be tight but barely doable.
With your skills, you'll be
able to stay alongside him.
If ya go divin' into the third one together...
Then it's all up to luck.
Give it your best.
So Dad knew that Kogashiwa
would pull those jumps?
But what really matters is what
comes next, and I don't get it!
The time when the brush starts to dry out...?
What's he telling me to do?!
One more left! Coming up
is the last hairpin curve!
Once we get into the mid-to
high-speed section past that,
he won't have a prayer!
I'm feelin' good, Dad!
Everything is going accordin' to plan!
The brush along the road is drying out...
I can see the grade level of the asphalt!
I've got it! He's telling me to do that!
This is the only spot! It's my last chance!
What?! Such speed!
What the hell just happened?!
You son of a bitch!
- Here they come!
- Which one's in front?
They came in side-by-side!
If either of them strays
even slightly from the line,
they'll both smash into the concrete wall!
I lost.
Me, a local... done in by fallen leaves!
Still, he's really great, that Takumi Fujiwara!
The Eight-Six won.
Looks like Kogashiwa spun
out right before the goal.
Ah...
Big brother!
Shall we go, Keisuke?
Yeah.
Takumi Fujiwara... He's going to be big.
The Gunma area alone won't
be enough to contain him.
I understand full well why
Ryosuke has his eye on him. But...
At some point, he will overtake
even Ryosuke as a driver.
I see. Understood. We'll pack up here, too.
It's over! The Eight-Six won!
Yeah! Takumi won!
He did it! Incredible!
This will be the start of a
new legend of the Eight-Six!
Incredible isn't he, Akina's Eight-Six?!
Hey now, no crying, lketani!
I'm just so happy...
I'm going to cry, too!
I appreciate your skillful handling.
Thanks to that, we didn't
have to get into a wreck.
This is my dad's car, so I wanted
to give it back without any dents.
Same here.
I passed by this car once before in Akina.
In that moment, I thought to myself
that this might be one
opponent I couldn't beat.
I never planned on going
up against your dad, but...
...that's how intense of an impression I got.
And I ended up losing, so I guess
my impression was on the mark.
It was a shock to lose on my home turf,
but that was a good experience you gave me.
You and your dad are both incredible.
Let's do this again somewhere.
I'll sharpen my skills first...
See you.
It sure is cold today! Takumi,
you got any pocket warmers?!
Hell no, I don't!
The cold sure sucks, huh?
That harsh wind blowing...
Takumi, what do you think
you'll do after graduation?
Graduation, huh?
Yeah! You don't plan on
going to college, right?
- I guess not...
- So you goin' to vocational school?
Uh...
If you haven't made any plans yet,
why not work here with me?
Here?
I'm thinking of asking the manager
to make me a full-time
employee here come April.
You should do that, too.
While you're spacin' out,
more and more time will slip on by!
See you!
Isn't it a little different from before? Your car.
Your seat's different, and how
it runs feels different, too.
Say, Takumi, what are you doing for Christmas?
Nothing really.
Don't you have a party or
something at your house and stuff?
Since I was a kid, we've never
done anything special for Christmas.
It's not like we've got a mom at home, so...
Anyway, enough about that.
What did you want to talk to me about?
I... I broke up with the guy in the Benz.
H-Hey, I don't care about that!
You're lying.
If you really didn't care,
you wouldn't be ignoring me!
You're ignoring me because
you've got me on your mind, right?!
In the summer, you and I went
to the beach... We even kissed.
You're mad because you feel
like you've been betrayed, right?
I'm sorry.
It's cold... It's already winter, huh?
I... I want us to be close, like we were before.
I don't!
I can't just switch my way of thinking like that!
I can't accept that!
I won't give up! I'll make up with you for sure!
There's one thing I want to ask you.
You're pretty popular. You could
find plenty of guys to go with, right?
This isn't like you. Why choose me?!
"Why?" There's no reason...
Because I like you of course, why else?!
Thank you very much!
Iketani!
This weather feels like it's gonna
start snowing or something, huh?
It certainly is cold today.
More importantly, Itsuki,
what are you doing for Christmas?
What am I doing? It's obvious, isn't it?!
As I thought, a party with your friends?
After all, this is your last
Christmas in high school...
Incorrect! I am working, sir, working!
I have to trade out the
Levin tires on my beloved car
with winter-use studless ones!
Just like me at your age.
And what about Takumi?
Uh, Takumi...
Man, he can really space out, huh?
Especially so today...
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Hey Pops, I...
Um, I'm gonna be graduating soon, right? So...
Just do what you wanna do.
"Tofu"
"Fried Tofu"
Whether that's being a tofu man or whatever...
There are guys with time on their
hands even on Christmas Eve, huh?
Don't you have somewhere else you can go?
Man, when you say it like that...
Anyway, who cares?
No matter where you go today,
it'll still be rough being alone.
Look to your right, swing over to
your left, it's nothing but couples!
On a day like this, we should
go out and eat some great food.
That sounds good! What about you guys?
I'm going, of course! I've got nothing to do!
What about you, Takumi?
I don't have any money, so I'm not going.
What the heck?!
You're as unsociable as always!
"Cake Shop"
Tofu shop... Tofu... There it is! I finally found it!
Okay, here goes!
Sure has gotten cold...
At this rate, there'll be
snow up on the mountain...
U-U-Um, tofu... No, not tofu!
I-I'm a friend of Takumi's.
Ah. He ain't come back from work yet.
Oh. Um...
Ah! No, nothing. Sorry to have bothered you.
Actin' like some middle-aged peddler...
Hey, you there. That looks heavy and all,
so if you came to see
my son about something,
I think he'll be back soon,
so come in and have a cup of tea.
Is that all right?
What a pain. Stupid Christmas...
Tea's all I've got, but...
Oh! So that's what that big thing was!
It's cute, isn't it? Look, the tree even has this...
That's pretty.
An Eight-Six?
It's handmade. I made it.
Takumi seems to really like that car, so...
Friggin' Takumi sure is late.
Where's he wanderin' around at?
What time were you supposed to meet?
No, uh, we didn't make any arrangements.
This is an unannounced,
"gatecrash" Christmas party.
- This, please.
- Yes, sir.
This hit me a minute ago...
You're the girl who used to call
now and then last summer, right?
Yes...
When those calls suddenly stopped,
I wondered what was up...
A lot happened... It looked
like Takumi started hating me.
I didn't want us to graduate
with things like this.
I've been trying hard,
but Takumi just won't forgive me...
I don't know the particulars,
but Takumi ain't one to strut around
choosin' who or who not to forgive.
I think he probably doesn't really hate ya.
He may be just a kid, but he's as stubborn
as an old man about some things.
Once his mind is set, he totally
refuses to compromise about it.
What's more, at times like that,
his attitude can be exactly the
opposite of what he really thinks.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I'm home.
Huh? Is someone here?
Merry Christmas!
What the heck is this?
Merry Christmas...
Pops, you too? What are you doing?!
"Karaoke Club"
Merry Christmas!!
This sure is fun, huh?!
What're we doin' next?
It's not as if he's got any alcohol in him...
Sure is lonely, huh?
Sure is pathetic!
- Mako...
- Huh?
Racers don't need women after all, do we?!
Takumi, put the tree over there.
O-Okay.
I've loved Christmas
ever since I was a little kid.
That's why I wanted to spend
Christmas with you, Takumi.
You said before, right?
You'd never had a Christmas before...
Okay, let's eat some cake! Cake! Ta-daa!
- Light the candles!
- Pops, a lighter.
Yeah...
- I'm turning off the lights!
- Okay.
What? Did Dad fall asleep?
Huh?
Say, Takumi, what are you
doing after you graduate?
I haven't decided yet. What about you?
Me? Well, I...
I've sort of gone along
with the flow up till now,
but I thought if I keep doing that,
nothing good will come of it.
I want to find something that I want to do.
That's why I decided to go to school in Tokyo.
Happy New Year! Many happy returns!
Yeah, Happy New Year.
Here's to another good one.
We get a lot of customers during
New Year's, so everyone do your best.
You can count on us, Boss!
You're all fired up, Itsuki.
You better believe it! Come April,
I'll be a full-time employee here!
Ah! It hasn't been cleaned over there yet!
Starting April, we'll be seeing
Itsuki here every day, eh?
I don't know whether to be happy or sad.
Hey, Takumi! Don't stand there
spacing out! Wipe the windows!
You gotta find ways to be productive!
Wow, listen to you.
Well, as a contributing member of society,
I have a different mindset
from Mr. Takumi here!
Thank you very much!
Say, Natsuki, thanks for working
so hard even during New Year's.
You must've had lots of plans, right?
No, that's fine. Right now, working is more fun!
Is that so?
Once I started working,
I realized for the first time...
Working to save money is really hard!
I suppose so.
- Welcome!
What will your order be today?
Once you've decided...
Natsuki?
What gives? Talk about cold!
You already forgot my face, have ya?
Miki...
For starters, lemme get a
cheeseburger and a shake.
O-Okay. Cheeseburger
and a shake, one of each.
Why don't we go for a drive when
you're off work? I'll give ya a ride.
No, that's all right.
What's with you? Got your guard up, huh?
I ain't gonna bite you or nothing!
Okay, fine!
I'll be done soon, so...
I came back here for New Year's vacation.
I sure was surprised to see ya workin' a job!
Something feels different about you...
Oh, yeah? It's normal, baby, normal.
You've changed, too. Like, more adult...
You're sexier than before!
Hey, you got a man?
That's really none of your business, is it?
Well, when you say it like that,
it means ya don't!
In that case, hook up with me!
Let's have all kinds of fun, like in the old days.
I bet you can't get me
out of your head, can ya?
I'll get out here. Stop!
What the hell, you're mad?
I'm sorry, but I don't want to go out with you.
I'm not dating anyone,
but there is someone I really like.
He's very important to me, so...
Goodbye.
Stop! Miki!
What's the big deal? Just hang out a bit longer.
Lemme hear about this
important person of yours!
He... He's scary!
- Good night!
- We'll be leaving now.
Whoa, it's really coming down now.
Oh, yeah. Say, Takumi...
You wanna come by my house?
Well... Whatever, I guess.
It's not like you got anything
to do if you go home, right?
"Gas"
Yeah...
Where are we going?
We got a lot to talk about, right?
Somewhere with no one around to distract us.
The night's just gettin' started.
Takumi!
And that's when lketani...
Huh? What is it, Takumi?
I'm gonna pass on today after all.
What the heck for?
I'm just sorta not in the mood.
Plus, my dad's out at a party.
He's bound to get drunk and
call me to pick him up in the car.
Come on, just forget about that!
See ya.
Shoot. He should hurry up
and leave that old man.
Natsuki! You and me used to
have fun in the old days, huh?
You'd do anything I told you, wouldn't ya?
C'mon, let's do it like old times.
You can do that, right?
- No!
- Why the hell not?
Because now is different!
Don't screw with me! When did
you get to be such a friggin' bore?
You used to be more easygoing,
a girl who could get in the mood!
People change when they
find someone they really like!
D-D-Don't go actin' all high and mighty! Shit!
"Takumi Fujiwara"
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Bitch!
Hey, wait!
Dammit! Natsuki!
Takumi, please! Pick up!
Son of a... Ow!
Shit!
It ain't like you can run away from me!
Takumi!
Please! Hurry and pick up!
Yes, hello?
Help me! Takumi! The lake...!
Hello? Natsuki?
Hello? What's happened?
Hello? Hello?
This doesn't feel like
she was messing around...
The lake?
Lake Akina!
You said "Takumi" or somethin' just now, huh?
Don't tell me the guy you like
is that friggin' Fujiwara!
Your face tells me that it is!
Shit!
You gotta be kidding me, Natsuki.
Of all people, you had to go
and get chummy with him?
I think it's time you shut
the hell up, before I make you!
Just who do you think you are?!
That ain't no way to talk to your seniors...!
I don't wanna friggin' remember that!
Takumi...
...will hit you again.
Why, you!
If you're gonna call for help,
then think about who you're callin'
Fujiwara can't make it out here.
He doesn't even have a car!
He'll come. Takumi can race
mountain roads very fast.
He's... got a car?!
- Shit! Come on!
- That hurts! Let go!
- Shut up! Get in the car!
- No! Don't pull me!
Hurry up and do it!
That hurts! Stop!
Strike on, ride on, ride on my own
Hurry up and move into the streaming
Screaming to the mountain high
Where are we going?
If we stay here, people can
come by and bother us.
We'll go down the mountain, change locations.
You better get ready, 'cuz until I'm satisfied...
...there's no way I'm lettin' ya go home.
He's really crazy! What do I do?
Takumi...
Loud desire, a roaring backfire
Sput-sput-bang!
You've stepped so hard on the gas
But you still can't shake him
Why were we born in this era?
Why are we alive at this moment?
Why do we stand to climb this steep road?
To search for the fundamental reason
for existence and action
That itself is surely a reason to live
Now strike you on
Everyone searches all alone
For their own futures
Please come, Takumi!
Even if they make great sacrifices
(Bang it down)
Strike on, in order to be
the you that you really are
Strike on, how many more
wounds will your breast bear?
Strike on, go chasing after
your dreams, love, no matter how far
Straight shot, how many screams
and tears do you hide as you run?
(Hey, make a noize!)
(Somebody make a noize!)
(Somebody shake your body,
now you make a scream!)
To be strike on
Well, it's already the fierce battle stage
Onlookers will get all riled up
Comin' at ya, straight shot!
Takumi!
No way!
That was too fast!
Takumi came... He came for me!
I wondered what kinda car he had,
and it's some beat-up old jalopy!
Don't go yelping over a little drift like that!
Natsuki! Sorry, but there's no way
that car can catch up to mine!
Takumi can catch up. He's a great driver!
Ain't gonna happen. It's not about
whether his driving's good or bad.
I've got four-wheel drive!
Everyone in the world knows...
...four-wheel drive rocks on snowy roads!
Mad speed like this, even on snowy roads!
Once we take these three curves,
Fujiwara's car will be far away and outta sight!
Wha?!
That's impossible!
Dammit!
I-it can't be! My four-wheel drive,
beaten by a rear-wheel drive piece of junk!
It's not your car's fault.
It's probably just because you drive slow.
What?! Bitch, you got some nerve,
makin' fun of me like that!
Keep your eyes on the road or we'll crash!
Shit! This guy just won't quit!
How about this?!
No good.
It won't turn!
Please! Don't hit us!
Takumi!
Natsuki.
Takumi, you came...
What the heck happened?
I didn't know what was going on,
so I came racing down here.
Whose car is that?
It's someone you know, right?
We'll talk in the car. Let's go, Takumi.
Are you angry?
I'm sorry. Is it because I got in Miki's car?
Whatever.
Takumi...
I'll take you, so just go straight home.
No. I can't go home with things like this.
If I don't say this now, I feel like
I won't be able to say it again.
So I want you to listen.
The person I was dating before...
...the guy you knew about,
the one with the Benz...
I got money from him.
I really regret doing that now.
Back then, in exchange for money,
I felt like more and more,
I was losing something important.
The real reason I started my job
is I thought that if I worked,
I could get back whatever it was I'd lost.
And I wanted you to see how hard I was...
I wanted you to look,
and know how hard I was working.
Oh, oh no! Crying in front
of a guy is so uncool!
I definitely didn't want to do it, yet I...
This is terrible!
When did I turn into such a crybaby?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Takumi.
I have something I want to say, too.
It's how I really feel.
I... I like you!
You want to race me?
Yes. Please!
You still haven't answered
whether you'll join my new team.
I'd like to decide that based on this race.
Please!
Fine. Any conditions?
You start and I'll come behind.
The place will be Akagi.
I have no illusions of winning.
It's just, last time was at Akina, so...
This time, I wanted to race on your home turf.
I feel like if we do that, I'll find the answer.
Very well. This Saturday. I look forward to it.
"Chilled tofu soup"
Teach you about tuning up?
Yes. Just a bit of advice will be okay.
I want to try doing it myself.
Who are you up against this time?
An FC... I mean, me.
You yourself, eh?
Guess it's about graduation time, huh?
Okay, get ready!
Go!
"Welcome to Akagi Prefectural Park"
A-Awesome!
In the blink of an eye...
That's a twin drift?!
Perfectly executed, eh?
Fujiwara's feelings come
through all too clearly.
Right now, you are doing naught else
but concentrating on racing to your very limits!
I will have you show me... your racing!
- Wow!
- I'm stunned! That was incredible!
The FC is great, but the Eight-Six is great, too!
I can feel an aura comin' off of his racing!
Hey Takeshi, don't get too close!
If some stranger saw us, we'd look
like we were buddies, right?!
Oh...
What do you think, Keisuke?
Kenta, there's no way that Ryosuke
would lose on his home course!
I'm just saying, what if?
Either way would be fine.
This race isn't about winning or losing.
So long as they put their all into
their driving, that's what counts.
I'm jealous of those two, being
able to race all-out like that...
Incredible! Just as I thought, he's incredible!
He has progressed far
beyond that time in Akina!
It's strange. When I race you,
though my racing should be
perfected, I see something new.
I never thought I could find such joy in racing.
All my misgivings are gone.
I should stick with this guy!
"12th Graduation Ceremony"
Takumi!
We've graduated, huh?
Yeah.
I'm getting together with
some friends after this.
I'm just going to pop in to
say hi and then leave, so...
Okay?
- Natsuki!
- We're going!
Okay! I'm coming right now!
See you!
Hey, Takumi! So this is where you've been.
Graduation... It's enough
to make you cry, huh?
Hey, what are you doing after this?
You wanna come to my place and trade
memories of the bloom of our youth?
Uh, I... That is...
Could it be, you and Mogi are,
just the two of you...?!
Well, it's just...
No worries, no worries! You go on.
After all, I am a lonely driver!!
I'm gonna trade stories with
lketani at the gas station!
I'm not lonely!
The lake's ice... It's completely melted, huh?
It'll get warmer and warmer...
...won't it?
Takumi, you got that job at the
local delivery company, right?
Yeah. I can't even think of
a life separated from cars...
Being separated is terrible, isn't it?
I knew about this, but I hate it!
Come on, Takumi, come to Tokyo with me!
Come on!
I'm staying.
There's something I've been
thinking about since last fall...
What is my dream?
I thought about it all through
the winter, and I finally realized it.
I like to ride cars, and I want
to be faster than anyone else...
...so I want to become a pro racer!
That's why I'm going to stay behind here.
"That's why..."?
A new team will be forming,
and I want to join it
and learn all kinds of things.
I don't want to lose to anyone...
I want to stand at the top as the best racer!
Awesome! That's awesome, Takumi!
It's awesome...
I'll be lonely, but I'll endure it.
Without you, I'm sure my
memories of high school
would have all been terrible.
It's because you were there
that I was able to make so many great memories.
I'm not a good match for you, am I?
But I'll never forget you,
no matter how much time goes by.
Our memories together are precious to me.
So work hard and make your dreams come true.
Takumi!
Takumi... I'm going to work
hard so that I won't lose, too!
"Shibukawa Station"
Dilemma will always linger
I am distressed by this
The news is nothing but
self-centered hypocrites
I'm sick of it and can no longer watch
Becoming separated
is an emotion that closely resembles despair
But having been able to meet you
will lead to my rebirth
And so much of that same sort of love
"Initial D"
"Rental Counter"
will, under that same sky,
be born today, too
Spin, spin, planet Earth
An energy stronger than
anything else will pour outward
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
There's no such thing as scary things
Because the feeling is always at my side
I've been spending all my
lifetime driving on my car
Now I can see the way to
fly high, that I can go far
One day I'm leaving my past behind
Dancing in the fire of another life that I can try
The race is over!
Time to discover brand new spaces
Now and forever you can live it your way
The race is over!
Time to discover dreams and places
Now and forever, you can live it your way
I've been searching for tomorrow,
waiting for the sun
Now I believe I made there
never and it's time to run
One day I'm leaving my past behind
Dancing in the fire of another life that I can try
The race is over!
Time to discover brand new spaces
Now and forever, you can live it your way
I've been spending all my
lifetime driving on my car
Now I can see the way to
fly high, that I can go far
One day I'm leaving my past behind
Dancing in the fire of another life that I can try
The race is over!
Time to discover brand new spaces
Now and forever, you can live it your way