"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
It's so hard to maintain control
because the two cars are misaligned.
It's an unrecoverable mistake.
I can't get the maximum braking ability.
It's no good, we aren't slowing down.
I can't stop!
I'm not going to let you
do all of it by yourself.
I'm so impressed! Let me help!
Act 11  [ Full Stop, And Beyond... ]
You guys... what are you?
This
isn't my imagination.
She's here.
Kaori is here.
Kaori is...
Kaori was here.
Did you sense it, Ryosuke?
I did.
It was the scent of the
perfume she always wore.
I shouldn't be able to
smell it in a place like this
but it suddenly entered
my car before the toll booth.
I intuitively realized Kaori was there.
Senpai, we must have
encountered some kind of miracle.
Today's her anniversary.
It must be Kaori who saved you.
Ryosuke, are you stupid?
I had solid hostile intent
as I drove behind you.
You would've been a murder
victim if the worst happened.
How can you sound so nonchalant, as if it happened to someone else?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We just had a "battle."
It would've been easy to
kill me if you were serious
but it didn't turn out that way
because you followed your own rules.
That's why I accepted your challenge.
We threw everything we had into it,
and now both of us are standing here.
The fact that you were the opponent for my last
street battle means more than anything else to me.
It was you who taught me the
joy of driving the mountain pass.
I was able to drive so well with you watching,
so I'm satisfied from the bottom of my heart.
That's more than enough for me.
Let's put an end to this.
I couldn't figure out why, no matter
how hard I tried. It was just painful.
I blamed myself every day, and spent a
countless number of sleepless nights.
Only the negative images filled my mind.
But tonight, after racing with you, I feel like
something inside me was finally able to let go.
It was probably because I was able
to express my feelings to the fullest.
And you responded.
Your message was loud and clear,
and stronger than any words.
I realized so well that you've
been suffering from the same pain.
I'm sorry, Ryosuke. Thank you for this.
You could have ignored me, but you came.
I'm satisfied having raced with you.
I can say that from the bottom of my heart.
Your precious car is scratched up so badly.
Sorry, but it was unavoidable.
I can imagine how difficult the situation
was just by examining those scratches.
I'm not going to say much.
I'm just glad you made it back safely.
That's the Takahashi Ryosuke I know.
Well done.
I feel like I was able to get
over a lot of things by racing him.
It was a battle for my own sake, too.
Something's changed.
Ryosuke's facial expression is different.
He looks better, as if he feels refreshed.
As a team leader who sends
two drivers into battle
I must always know the reality of
what it's like to fight on the frontline.
What's most frightening is
becoming less sensitive to it.
But I was able to reassure myself
about my insight before the final battle.
I've done everything I could for
the riskiest stage in Kanagawa.
Our double aces have already surpassed me.
They should be fine.
One more battle to go.
Let's do our best to win.
One week until Project D's
final battle in Kanagawa.
I wonder what sort of driver
Sidewinder's downhiller is.
I'm also curious about what
kind of car he's going to drive.
Well, whoever he is,
he'll be no match for Takumi.
That's what I think, too.
But remember Kenji mumbling about something
just when the Kanagawa battles started?
I'm afraid of a driver who's
specialized in a particular course.
The kind of driver like Takumi
who won race after race on Akina.
That's impossible.
Takumi's one of a kind, because he didn't
grow up in an ordinary family.
Parents have to be
eccentric for that to happen.
Well that's...
He's a natural racer with a
special environment and talent.
You honestly think there's another
strange family like them in Kanagawa?
Probably not.
Here comes that "slightly loud" car.
You're still wearing your uniform, Mika?
Yep. I didn't have time
to go home and change.
It's not that uncommon, right?
I mean, up until last year
you were wearing one, too.
Do I look good in the sailor style uniform?
You came to realize your girlfriend
is a high school girl, didn't you?
Well yeah, but you won't be
able to play golf that way.
No worries, because I'm your coach today.
To the right again.
It goes to the right no matter what I do.
It does curve, but you've improved, Takumi.
You're totally different from the first time.
Even a skinny guy has some muscle, after all.
Maybe. I think my arms are strong
because of the Eight-Six's steering.
It's so heavy.
It curves like that because you put
too much strength in your right arm.
Let me use your club for a sec.
When the club is in this position,
the face should look like this.
I don't really understand.
Can you show me how?
Well then, watch me from behind.
Like this
and just lift the club naturally.
Mika
I'll do it.
You shouldn't.
Iketani, Itsuki!
What's the matter, Kenji? You look upset.
Did your grandma go missing again?
Don't go and jinx us like that.
I've got the latest info on
this weekend's race in Hakone.
They're so secretive, that I don't know
much in detail, except for one thing.
We didn't know anything about
Sidewinder's downhill driver, right?
What do you know about him?
Actually, I don't know anything
about the driver himself
but apparently, his car is an Eight-Six.
An Eight-Six?
Is it a Trueno or Levin?
I don't know that much yet.
Besides, that's not important, is it?
You're absolutely correct.
Eight-Six versus Eight-Six, huh?
It's fortunate because Takumi won't
lose, if both cars are Eight-Sixes.
There shouldn't be any other Eight-Six
drivers who are better than Takumi.
I was nervous, not knowing what the
opponent's car was, but now I feel relieved.
Once Takumi engages in a fight of
driving technique, he'll win for sure.
It's too naive to simplify
the matter like that, Itsuki.
I feel the same way.
I've a bad feeling because it's so ominous
for Sidewinder, which is the best
in Kanagawa, to use an Eight-Six.
It's a matter of confidence.
They appear to have a very good strategist.
I don't think he staged a battle between two
Eight-Sixes just to make the show more interesting.
They must be doing
everything to counter Project D.
Their choice of an Eight-Six as their final weapon to stop
Takumi's consecutive wins may be a sign of confidence.
He drives so smoothly that he doesn't
leave any strong impression at all.
But if you time him, he drives this downhill
faster than any of the Sidewinder members.
Plus, he doesn't drive any other course.
This world is full of strange talents.
I wonder how a kid like
him acquired such skill.
It's perplexing.
It's something beyond the common notion
of what driving technique should be.
Even Project D will be caught off guard.
He got rid of his R32.
Do you mean Rin?
Yes.
I don't know what made him change.
The Grim Reaper GT-R will
never appear in Hakone again.
I don't know what happened to him
but I've heard that he's requested
to return his former position at work.
It's good for the Hojo family, isn't it?
Probably so, but it
doesn't mean anything to me.
Little kids maybe, but we're not at the age where we can
just up and go back to being friendly siblings just like that.
It's creepy for brothers
our age to be so clingy.
Project D, my ass.
I'll defeat you, Takahashi Keisuke.
How is the new setup?
It feels good on Akagi's roads
but I can't say much until
we get some data in Hakone.
I want to tackle the final stage real soon.
I'm tired of image training.
I'll circle the dates of my Hakone
expeditionary race on the calendar
so don't forget your
delivery dates, okay?
Got it.
His tire management is impressive.
But something bothers me.
The control is too perfect.
Keisuke, Fujiwara, come over here.
As you know, this course is long, so it's physically
impossible to practice on everything in one day.
So cut it to the bare minimum.
Find what will become the key to victory as
you drive, then expand your scope from there.
If you try to do everything,
it'll only be half finished.
Imagine tomorrow's dogfight, and take a practical
strategy of knowing what to focus on and what not to.
I'm sure both of you can do that.
Then go.
The course is so long that it'll take longer
than usual to complete their routine.
I'm going to let them practice
thoroughly until dawn, so be prepared.
Got it.
I'll get more food
than usual for tonight.
They say you can't fight
on an empty stomach.
Thanks, Fumihiro.
I'm counting on you.
Hey, Matsumoto, you
know something, don't you?
About what?
About Ryosuke, of course.
He's acting differently.
Well, it must be because
this is the final battle.
I'm sure he's focused.
No, that's not what I mean.
It's like he's relaxed,
like he's smiling more often.
Matsumoto, if you know something, tell me.
Well
I don't know anything, really.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
What do you think, Kubo?
That FD is giving off a different feeling
from the last battle against Spiral.
It might have been
modified a lot for this battle.
I don't know.
The outer appearance is different
because of the carbon fiber hood,
but the insides shouldn't have changed much.
I'm worried. Forget about the Eight-Six.
Instruct everyone to focus
their data collection on the FD.
If you say so, I'll do it
but are you sure about the Eight-Six?
Data is meaningless for Shinji's driving.
He won't be able to make use of the data.
Even if he doesn't have it, he'll still win.
Shinji is that kind of driver.
Don't you think so too, Kubo?
You're right.
Focus on the FD.
Obtain as much information on its section times
to determine how its fighting potential varies.
Alright, I'll arrange that.
Oh man, our boss is nervous.
He fell for our opponent's diversion strategy.
They shouldn't have changed the
specs very drastically at this point.
That FD is a completely balanced machine.
I won't be tricked, Takahashi Ryosuke.
This is our match of intelligence.
You're worthy of being my opponent.
Hey, Mister Zero.
Well, if it isn't the hot blooded 246 guy.
It has finally come to the
moment of truth, hasn't it?
I was expecting you to stop them.
Sorry that we weren't good enough.
Takahashi Keisuke
How do you rate him?
His accelerator technique on
a half wet road was exceptional.
He managed to control the traction of the
rear tires, as if they were a part of his body.
Besides his concentration right at the moment of attack,
his ability to switch mindsets quickly is also impressive.
He reaches beyond the scope of Zero Theory,
like a fighter jet boosted by an afterburner.
In other words, he's like you.
Like me?
The type of driver who shows his eagerness for
victory, who has skills and understands the theory.
But in the end, what
matters most is the spirit.
You and Takahashi Keisuke
are alike on that account.
I don't feel bad hearing that.
What kind of driver is Fujiwara Takumi?
I want to hear your opinion since
you witnessed his true potential.
It's difficult to describe him.
It's like a black hole.
Black hole?
He has a wide margin to be able to absorb a lot.
He appears to have his own concrete policy, but in
reality, he has no color. He's transparent and flexible.
He improves race after race, so he's probably
different from when he raced against me.
So you think highly of him,
almost raving about him.
Then what's your prediction for this
battle between Project D and Sidewinder?
You want to cut to
the point, don't you?
It's unfortunate
but Sidewinder will win.
I've come to the same answer.
I really admire Takahashi Ryosuke.
As a member of a Kanagawa area team, I can't openly say
this, but my emotional side wants Project D to win.
But that's impossible.
Sidewinder had plenty of time to prepare.
As long as they have Kubo Eiji as their
strategist, they don't have any weaknesses.
But you can't really tell
until they start racing.
It's not like Project D
has no chance of winning.
They have a slight chance due
to their drivers improvements.
I say their chance of winning
is one fifth, which is 20%.
This is getting ridiculous.
I've never seen so many
guys with stopwatches before.
Don't they have anything else to do?
Speaking of which, we aren't that different, coming
all the way from Gunma only to race in Hakone.
Well, that's true.
They're measuring my
section times pretty closely.
I don't like them trying
to figure out our strategy.
Should I add another camouflage pattern?
No, don't.
Just do as normal.
I'm afraid that you won't finish
practice if you try to do it differently.
At this point, we don't
have to modify our style.
I got it.
I'll let them watch and learn the style of
Project D, the best of the northern Kanto area.
Yup, that's exactly what I meant.
What should I do then?
Set the suspension to pattern C,
and add 10 liters of gas.
Did you notice a huge number
of scouts throughout the course?
Keisuke told me about them,
and tons of stopwatches, too.
Here you go.
There're quite a lot of people out there,
but they aren't pushing the buttons.
I noticed those who were keeping
time and taking notes from the first round.
I'm sure they're the same people.
I remember some of their faces.
But today none of them pressed
the button on their stopwatches.
Are you sure, Fujiwara?
Yes.
He noticed such small
details while he was driving.
That's what makes him so great.
But what's the meaning of this, Ryosuke?
It contradicts what Keisuke said.
That's fine. Both of
them are telling the truth.
It's going as planned.
And so, the day of the final battle in Kanagawa has arrived...
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.