"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
I will catch up to you! Until I have the
chance to launch my counterattack...
...there's no way I'm letting you go!
Do you think Fujiwara is planning
a counterattack after all?
Perhaps. However, launching a
counterattack will not result in victory.
As for whether he will realize that...
"Act 12: Straightaway of Struggles"
Dammit! In this night rain and with
the spray of water I'm sending up,
he should be completely unable
to see from that side ditch,
so how can he keep up with me so precisely?!
Relax! First things first.
I have to be calm here.
If I lose my cool and my rhythm
gets thrown off, it could be deadly!
Okay, he's on my tail and I can't shake him.
I just need to switch strategies
to one that can't lose!
This spray has reduced my
visibility to almost nil. Still...
It's strange, but I don't feel scared.
Do you remember the
blind attack Fujiwara used
in the second race against the Toudou School?
Yeah. There's no way to
forget something like that.
Turning off the headlights and racing
a mountain pass in the dark...
Fujiwara is currently being supported by
the same manner of technique and ability.
Such as?
Even when there is inadequate
visual information,
he can supplement it with the
image that appears in his mind.
When it comes to this ability,
Fujiwara is quite outstanding.
He can instantly gauge top speed
and can unerringly race road
surfaces devoid of markers...
All because of his mental image.
That could be the source of what supports
Fujiwara's genius-like technique.
What? The Eight-Six is right on him?!
Really?
Where are they now?
The stretch of winding roads by the steel tower.
At this rate, it's too tough
to call just by the first race.
I can't comment until I hear
what Sakamoto has to say.
In any case, we'll have to come up
with a strategy for the second race.
A simulation with the Cappuccino
coming from behind, huh?
What a setback.
I didn't think there would
even be a second race...
All because of the rain, eh?
Unlike Sakamoto, who has only raced
in the Capuccino for a few days,
our opponent knows his
Eight-Six inside and out
and can control it like an
extension of his own body!
If only the course were dry. But this rain...
The Eight-Six is using it to its advantage!
I've had a bad feeling since earlier.
A sensation like he's planning
something is coming to me in waves.
But on this narrow course, and in the rain...
What the hell is he thinking?!
Quit screwing around!
Don't go planning something reckless.
Just stay there and behave!
Here!
What?!
I told you to quit screwing around!
No good!
Looks like countering an opponent who
can corner faster than you is impossible.
No. One more time.
Somewhere at these consecutive
corners coming up, I'll try again.
This next time will be my last chance.
If Ryosuke says I can do it,
then I can definitely do it!
Just a little longer...
Yes.
Even now, I can't forget...
...the shock and impact at being
passed by Fujiwara in the rain at Myogi.
I don't know how much of an
advantage having a light car is...
...but I just can't imagine
Fujiwara losing in the rain!
Go!
I diot! He's cutting in too close!
That bastard's dug our graves!
I'm gonna fall in!
I did it.
I don't know how I pulled that off,
but it was really lucky.
Still, that mistake just now
pulled me a little farther back.
I guess a counterattack is
no good. It just won't work!
But if that's the case...
For example, the methods of
Kyoichi Sudou of Team Emperor.
Something like that would be effective.
Don't forget, having a
completely different mindset
will be the key to winning this battle.
So if it's not a counterattack,
then Ryosuke...
I see. Understood.
My advice may have been
difficult to understand...
But the fact that Fujiwara is currently
able to keep pace with the Cappuccino
probably means that,
while not fully comprehending,
he has brought the gist of it into play.
Yes. But will he be all right?
If he could keep up during the opening and
middle sections of the race, he'll be fine.
I think those were the most difficult.
--And he springs the trap...
--Yes, at the very end.
He'll pull ahead at the place where
the enemy's greatest weapon,
being lightweight, ceases to be a weapon.
That's where Kyoichi would
take precise control.
Because it's the safest,
most certain way to pull ahead.
But will the enemy simply fall for
that safest, most certain way?
That is the greatest problem he will face.
He'll come! This flat straightaway
just ahead is my greatest weakness.
No matter what, I can't let
myself be passed here!
Whatever tactic I have to use, I'll show
you I can make it to the second race!
Is this the straightaway just before the goal?
If I want to go, this would be my chance.
But something's bothering me.
If I fail twice at cornering but
pull ahead right before the end...
Can I really call that winning?
Would Ryosuke praise me
for something like that?
I don't know... But I'm out of time.
I can't afford to hesitate!
What do I do? Do I go?
Or do I just do nothing and
let it go into the second race?
What's the right answer?!
Will he come from the right?
Or maybe from the left?
Here, I can't utilize this
thing's small frame anymore.
Even if I run in the middle of the road, it
still opens up space on the right and left.
I don't really care for doing it like this,
but I can't give up any road!
What do I do?! Which way of winning
is the one that Ryosuke wants?
The left, huh?!
There's no way I'm lettin' you in front of me!
I have to save face in front of my peers, too!
He'll go that far, will he?
If that's how he wants to play it...!
There they are! They're coming, Iketani!
What?!
Takumi's Eight-Six is gone!
If you're thinking about riding it out into
the next race, that is a mistake, Fujiwara.
Don't insist on a "pretty" victory.
Having such self-centered
fixations will only limit oneself...
And being limited leads to the end of growth.
If you feel resistance to pulling
ahead on the straightaway,
that is hubris and dependency!
How one wins does not require style!
Go, Fujiwara!
It's gone!
The Eight-Six is gone from my mirrors!
That's impossible. It can't be!
His headlights were right on me a second ago.
I don't get it!
What?!
Sakamoto got passed... The Eight-Six won!
Impossible...
He finished it in the first race?!
I said it from the first, did I not?
A completely different mindset.
The driver's job is to draw out a
car's latent potential to its very limits.
If one were to describe the essence
of it, that's what it boils down to.
Beyond racing fast, if there is one
key to beating an opponent's car,
it is simply to turn this sentiment
into a weapon and to attack.
This way of thought is what I wanted
you to experience in today's race.
Telling you to recall Kyoichi's
methods meant not just his technique,
but also included the
meaning of this psychology.
Today's race was for the most part
decided until the halfway point.
Good work sticking close to him, and not
being thrown off during that section.
You did well. Just relax and enjoy yourself.
The time trial has been cancelled.
That turned out well, huh?
I... Did I just get praised?
To be honest, I only sort of accept it.
Did I really do well in passing him like that?
Right up till the end, I really felt lost.
I thought about doing nothing
and riding it out till the second race.
It's a good thing you didn't.
Ryosuke would definitely
have gotten angry at you.
Really?
Of course!
There's no guarantee conditions would've
stayed the same for the second race.
Don't forget, half the help
you got was from the rain.
If it had stopped raining, it would've been
impossible to keep up with the Cappuccino.
Oh... I guess you're right.
If you'd been racing on your own, you'd
be free to choose whichever you like,
but right now you're racing
as a representative of D.
Don't forget that.
I can't believe it. How could you lose?!
And under these conditions!
I just can't believe it!
What the hell happened?!
I don't know. I don't get any of it.
On the straightaway right in front of
the goal, he just suddenly disappeared.
He cleverly went into
the mirrors' blind spot, eh?
If that were the case, I would've
noticed before he'd pulled alongside.
I barely had time to go "Huh?"
before he was right there beside me.
Hey, get a hold of yourself.
What are you on about?
You're not some amateur!
Say what you like, but if I
don't get it, I don't get it!
This has shocked me the most!
Yeah, you've got a point.
You guys couldn't beat
that Eight-Six either, right?
Man, I've had enough of this.
I've completely lost confidence in myself.
It doesn't look like I'll be
recovering from this for a while.
There's something fundamentally
different about that guy.
He's an incredible driver.
Still, that blind attack in the middle
of the rain was really effective.
The rain already made it hard to see,
so to your opponent, I think it
really felt like you'd disappeared.
Ryosuke already said this, but that
tactic is a powerful weapon in a fight.
You may be right...
But personally, I don't think I
want to use it too frequently.
I'd enjoy it too much.
Enjoy it? You would?
But it would come out spontaneously...
If an opponent wouldn't open up
any road, I'd do it reflexively.
Or if I got angry...
Ah, there he is!
Hey, Takumi!
Wow, you really gave me a shock earlier!
Somehow, I completely lost sight
of what your Eight-Six was doing!
Uh, us too.
Sorry 'bout that!
I almost got hit by the Eight-Six, too!
I'll forgive ya this time, though.
At least I'm not causing a scene...
That Levin! It can't be!
That's Wataru's Levin!
Yeah. You just now noticed that?
Wataru's representing the
other team on the hillclimb.
What?! What does that mean?
Don't tell me! Don't tell me!
K-Kazumi?
Kazumi!
It's me! Me!
Itsuki?
The compressor!
You changed it to a supercharger?
Yeah. After losing to that guy's Trueno last fall,
I started feeling dissatisfied
with how my turbo was set up.
I'd just finished putting the engine together
and after thinking through a couple
of options, this is what I came up with.
The supercharger's direct response is,
if anything, close to NA.
It hasn't got the quirks of a turbo, and it
feels like I've put in a large-volume engine.
This thing will be just the trick
for a tight course like today's.
Keep that in mind as you bring your A-game.
I see. I'll have to do that.
I'll friggin' show you what
having a turbo is all about.
Line up your cars! The Levin
goes first, followed by the FD!
Keisuke, your task has
been set since last week.
You understand, yes? Road surface conditions
are perfect for measuring its effectiveness.
Yeah, I know! Just watch
me out there, big brother.
Very well.
Here we go!
Starting in five seconds!
Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
Awesome! For it to be a match
for the FD in the start dash,
Wataru's Levin must really be awesome!
I installed a turbo in my Levin as well,
but this is completely different!
My brother's Levin is rebuilt now,
and installed with a supercharger.
A supercharger?
He ended up blowing out his old engine.
It looked like he really
hated losing to your friend.
He put everything into his racing,
and really pushed himself.
Huh. He did?
Still, a supercharger is a bit unexpected.
But he said it suits a car like the Eight-Six.
My brother's very satisfied.
He said that his racing power
has improved over his old turbo.
Once we enter the low- to
mid-speed section coming up,
it doesn't matter how much power you
have, you won't be able to use it all.
It will be a battle of driver vs. driver!
It's a street fight, where the winner is
the one with the strongest conviction!
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte