"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Kikanaku natteta
ano CD wo mata sagasou
Itsushika nervous-gachi no futari no tame ni
Speed tozashita kako ga
mezamete iku melody
Chikyuu ga furueru hodo ni
kakushinhan no neraiuchi
Blazin' beat
Itai hodo tsuyoi ai wo abisete
Sakebu kaze hibiku oto de daite
Naked mind, desire
Motomeru koto ni tsumi wa naku
Utagau koto sura wasurete mi wo makasete
Blazin' beat! Yo! Binbin de ikou,
moral wa hashotte ii darou
Shoudo no mama ni tobidasou
Weekend da yo zenin shugo!
M.O.V.E., move, buchigiri hajikeru
Torihada mon no wakuwaku
wo sagasou, it's the time!
"Act 10: The Eight-Six Turbo!"
That was a surprise.
Man, it was just getting interesting.
We'll try it again very soon.
Don't act so cool.
There are all kinds of racers.
I have one more thing to look forward to.
"One week later"
They didn't need you on a Sunday afternoon?
Maybe you aren't that useful.
How rude!
It was super busy in the morning.
I've worked two weeks straight,
so they gave me an afternoon off.
That's okay, then.
Why did you come here, anyway?
Well, I wanted to see how you were doing.
Mom and Dad worry about you.
I'm fine. I'm working very hard.
I hope so.
I'm low on gas. I should fill up.
My friend works at a gas station.
Welcome!
Hey!
Big brother, that's Itsuki.
Welcome!
Twenty liters of high octane.
Right away!
Her brother is really good-looking!
I've seen that Eight-Six Turbo.
I hear you and my sister are friends.
Isn't she too strong-willed?
No, I don't think so.
Hey, big brother!
Don't ask him stupid things like that!
She's a good girl, so be nice.
Yes.
This is a complete change of topic,
but I hear that Gunma
has a really fast Eight-Six.
What?
They say he's undefeated.
I know Gunma is pretty big,
but I thought you might
know something about him.
Of course I do! He's my friend.
--Seriously?
--Yes.
Itsuki, wasn't it?
I know we've only just met,
but do you think you could
arrange a meeting with him?
I want to talk to him.
I'm curious about his Eight-Six.
Piece of cake!
He's a bit slow, but he's a nice guy.
How about tonight?
--You sure?
--No problem!
I was planning to go see
him after work anyway.
That'd be great.
Thank you very much!
I can't believe he's your friend's friend.
I'm thankful that you guys became friends.
I don't like this.
You seem to only care about Itsuki's friend,
and not about Itsuki.
That's not true. He seems okay.
Why are you meeting his friend?
No reason.
I just want to meet him.
He must be skilled to have won
all his races in competitive Gunma.
I hope that's it.
You tend to lose your cool
when it comes to street racing.
Come on, Takumi!
I just want Kazumi's brother to like me.
This is a good opportunity
for me to score some points.
Okay, I'll be there.
But I'm not interested in racing him at all.
The new engine isn't that good.
Don't worry about that!
I learned my lesson after the thing
with the Night Kids' Nakazato.
Kazumi's brother seems very nice.
You'll see when you meet him.
It's cool to see three Eight-Sixes!
But mine is an Eight-Five.
He's young.
You know that Eight-Six Turbo
that came in this afternoon?
I saw it once...
...when I went to see the
Red Suns race the Emperors.
Yeah?
It had amazing uphill acceleration.
Since her brother drives a car like that,
Kazumi may not be that impressed with Itsuki.
There you go again, Iketani.
Your way of thinking
won't help your social life.
Itsuki doesn't look like he
worries about things like that.
Clumsy but positive guys have an upper hand
over guys who worry too much.
You're still young.
You just got a new engine?
Yeah, but it's a lot slower than the old one.
--Right, Takumi?
--Yeah.
That's why he won't be able to race for a while.
--Right?
--Yeah, that's right.
Is it a normal 4AG?
I don't know much about engines.
It has okay power,
but it's hard to control.
It's a weird engine.
Do you mind if I take a look?
Uh, no, I don't mind.
What is this?!
It's not a 4AG, even though it is a 4AG.
Is this a joke?
Are you teasing me?
I don't know where you got this engine...
...but don't insult me by saying that it's slow.
Well, but, um...
--Why is he mad?
--Who knows?
I thought we were fellow Eight-Six racers.
Is my cheap turbo not good enough for you?
You owe me an explanation.
Stop it, big brother!
What are you talking about?
Stay out of this, Kazumi.
I've never met anyone who has
an engine like this for street racing.
This engine is for professional racing.
What?
I could never afford it...
...no matter how much I wanted it.
Picturing this engine in my
Eight-Six makes my mouth water.
So what?
I don't care what kind of engine you have.
But why lie about it?
Why can't you say you're fast?
Both of you disgust me
with your deliberate lies.
We weren't, really...
Don't be ridiculous.
It's not a lie.
Let's go, Itsuki. I'm done talking to him.
--Takumi!
--Running away?
I'm not done with you.
Oh, no! Takumi is losing it!
This is not good!
Kazumi!
I...
What's the matter with you, big brother?!
Itsuki introduced his friend
to you out of kindness.
Apologize to them!
If you don't want to, then go
and never come back here!
Kazumi...
Don't be rude to my friend!
I'm doing my best to live on my own here.
Don't show up randomly and mess up my life!
Okay.
I'll go, then.
--Itsuki?
--Yeah?
I'm going, too.
Hey, wait! Don't leave me here alone!
--Later.
--Hey!
Hey, wait, Takumi! Takumi!
Hey, Takumi!
I didn't expect her...
...to react like that at all.
I guess coming to Gunma was
a good thing for her after all.
But for me...
I'm sorry.
He gets so intense when it comes to cars.
There's no need to apologize.
When I saw your confused face,
I got so angry with Wataru.
My hand moved before I could stop it.
Please don't think that I have a short temper.
Don't worry!
Actually, I was sort of glad.
I know that you got upset because
you wanted to defend us.
Why did you stop?
You know I wouldn't have chased after you.
Now that you're here,
I may want to pick up where we left off.
I don't care what you want,
but there is one thing I need to know.
I need to know for sure if this engine...
...is that great.
I can tell it's not a normal engine,
but if you're right and this is a great engine,
I want to know why it lacks power.
I know absolutely nothing about engines.
Are you serious about that?
How can the owner not know about his car?
Where did you get this treasure, then?
My dad got this engine somewhere.
I don't know, because he
didn't tell me anything.
Your dad? He must work
in the racing industry, then.
No, he runs a tofu shop.
How can a tofu guy get this kind of engine?
This isn't something you
can simply buy with money.
Never mind. I, too, am curious
about this engine's full potential.
Can you drive me around?
I want to feel the engine for myself.
What's your plan now, Bunta?
Well, I imagined it would take about a month.
He's had more than enough practice with it.
The thing you ordered is here already.
Isn't it about time?
I don't know.
I haven't gotten enough of
a reaction from Takumi yet.
It's good that he's trying to
compensate with his technique,
but he should've noticed by now.
Well, I'll just wait and see.
It feels weird. The shifting
stalls the acceleration.
It has tons of power at the rev limit,
but up-shifting causes a power loss.
This engine is defective.
No need to compare it to a turbo. It's dull.
Why? This can't be its full potential.
What the...?
Again! Why?
Now I get it! I know why.
I can tell you why you don't get much power.
It's very simple and basic.
That thing.
It's your tachometer.
My tachometer?
That tachometer is no good.
It doesn't go high enough.
This is a "high-rev" engine that
generates its power at a very high rpm.
Professional "normally aspirated"
engines are all like this.
The fact that you get a surge of power
right before shifting is proof of that.
You need to rev it higher.
You haven't been able to
use it to its full capacity.
I would say that this engine is capable of...
...at least 10,000 rpm.
A tachometer that only shows
7,000 rpm or so won't cut it.
The treasure is left unused.
This isn't an original Eight-Six engine.
It's called a "4AG,"
but it's a five-valve-head engine
that was adapted from the newer "101."
There's supposed to be a "VVT" device
that switches valve timing
at lower and higher rpms.
Its absence means that
this is a super high-rev engine.
I noticed something while sitting next to you.
The interior panel looks too cheap
for the engine you have.
At least, you need water temperature
and oil pressure gauges.
The person who installed this engine
has terrific knowledge of auto mechanics.
The tires and the brakes are well balanced.
So is the body.
So, why aren't the essential gauges there?
There's only one answer to that question.
For whatever reason,
the engine's true power has
been sealed off on purpose.
Sealed off?
It's a simple but reliable way to do it.
A good racer won't over-rev.
So, without a new tachometer,
he won't rev beyond the red zone.
I've often felt camaraderie
toward fellow Eight-Six racers...
...but never hostility.
This is a first for me.
I have a strong desire to defeat you now.
No matter how well you can race,
you're lacking an essential element as a racer.
Huh?
I absolutely can't lose to you.
We'll settle this shortly.
I'm lacking...
...an essential element?
I'm in shock.
I got scared.
The way he entered corners was beyond belief.
He can go way beyond the limit
that my body is used to.
He's ignorant about cars,
but his technique is unreal!
It makes no sense!
If I lose to him,
everything that I am will shatter into pieces.
My very existence depends on this!
Furikaereba itsudatte
Kawaranu kimi no egao ga atta
Arukitsukare tachidomaru hi mo
Chiisa na yorokobi no hi mo
Kono ryoute ni kakaekirenai
Ai wo oshiete kureta
Atatakaku
Sotto yasashiku yomigaeru kaze wa
Ima hitori sora wo
Mitsumeteru boku ni hohoendeiru
Mada ano hi no mama no
Mabushisa de te wo futteiru
Kimi wa everlasting memory
Wataru challenges Takumi!
The race is about to start!
Next on Initial D: Second Stage...
"The Seal Is Broken."
Don't miss it!