"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Blastin' off to the wicked show,
splitting the air with that sputterin' noise
Let's go, ride that thing
to the throwdown party
Determination that never
backs down, the dogfight
I wanna feel the thrill of the
screams in the phat red zone
A brief flash, like a comet
The brightness lasts a second, but I don't care
Someday, I wanna tell of that
glimpse of precious scenery
Yes, right now it's a purely instinctual dogfight
If it's a thrilling dream
you're after, it's right here
A wind that shatters the heat haze, backfire
C'mon, throw away yesterday,
right now it's a rocket dance (Dogfight!)
If the wish you can't scream aloud hurts,
then hurry and come here
You're big time gambler
Foolishness is a beautiful contour
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Tha loud sound is everywhere
Sideswipe, a 5G heavyweight
Runnin' right to the line, a hair's breadth
between offense and defense
Ba-ba-baaam!
Yo, I can step on the gas for
an easy victory, I still got it
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I finished the deliveries.
Ah. Good job.
Listen, I'm gonna do the deliveries
tomorrow and the day after.
How come? We said we'd
switch every other day, right?
I know, but... I think the team's going
out on another expedition next week,
so I'm taking what I'd miss.
Well, that's admirable of ya.
It's a long way from the old days
when you'd go out complainin'
about it. Is delivery that much fun?
It's not really fun at all. It's just, if I
don't do the Akina run, I get anxious.
When the team goes on the road,
we race unfamiliar courses, right?
Coming up with strategies for the
new course takes everything I've got
and I can't think of anything else.
This is the first time I've
thought of it like this, but...
...when I do the Akina run, I feel really
relaxed and notice all sorts of things.
It's not like I've completely
mastered driving the car yet.
But even if I try out new things, it's gotta
be at Akina at first or it's no good.
That's why... I'm not gonna say every day,
but as much as possible, I'd like to
go out on the morning deliveries.
Outta nowhere, ya friggin' realized
the importance of a home course...
"Act 3: The Most Powerful
Man of the Toudou School"
Welcome!
--Huh?
--Hey!
Takumi?
This is unusual, seeing you out so early.
I've got the day off today.
With nothing to do, I sort of ended up here.
A fine youngster like yourself having nothing
to do on a day off? Now that's a problem!
What about your girl?
Haven't you heard anything
from Natsuki? Since last time.
Since April, I've gotten a letter from her once.
From what she wrote, she sounds
like she's enjoying herself.
Knowing her, I think she got used to
Tokyo quickly and is getting along fine.
You should go see her once in a while.
No, not good!
Iketani, if you say something like that,
Takumi will fly off right now!
I'm not going. I'm busy, and don't
have time for that sort of thing.
Wh-What?
Between work and the team,
I've got all I can handle.
I can't think of anything else.
Is that so? Still, when you say it like that...
If you turn into...
...a carbon copy of Kenji,
don't come crying to me!
That's right! He's a good age,
but he doesn't have a girlfriend...
A lonely existence where you
end up here in your free time!
Are you okay with that?
I don't wanna hear that
from the likes of you two!
Kenji!
You'll pardon me for my lonely,
girlfriendless existence!
Uh...
I swear. Hey, I've been hearing things,
Takumi. Project D sure is incredible!
I saw the new expeditionary file.
It gave me the shivers, for real!
Right now, Takumi and Keisuke Takahashi
are the two poster boys for the Gunma area!
You guys are just too talented.
No matter where you go,
no one can stop you, huh?
That's not true. It's not as if winning is easy.
It's always a battle right to the end.
And there's no way of knowing what kind
of tough opponent will show up next.
I'm really under a lot of pressure.
And who will your next opponent be?
Is it already decided?
Yes. I think it was Toudou... The Toudou School.
What? The Toudou School?!
Do you know it, sir?
Yeah. I've heard rumors. An ex-rally racer
turned shop president who started up
an advanced driving technique school
that's attracted young car enthusiasts.
An advanced driving technique school?
They actually have something like that?
Yeah. And with drifting as popular as
it is these days, it looks like these guys
are a bunch of balls-to-the-wall racers
whose only concern is mad speed!
There are guys who've graduated
the Toudou School and gone pro,
and apparently several semi-pro-level
grads still prowl around the street scene.
Y-You're gonna go up
against guys like that? Takumi...
Mr. Toudou. What is it you
wished to speak about?
Daiki. They're coming tomorrow.
That expeditionary team.
Project D?
Yes. About that...
Mr. Toudou, this car...
It's a demo car we're using.
You wanna give it a try?
Thank you for the opportunity,
but I'll use my own car.
The demo cars of Toudou & Co.
are quite astounding,
so much so that the race
would be over all too quickly.
I wouldn't feel as if I'd
won by my own abilities.
You goddamn fool! Quit talkin' that crap!
...is what I'd like to say, but I already
thought that would be your answer.
Whatever. Do what you want.
It's all a game anyway.
Well, do your best.
I'll go and watch for myself,
if I get to feelin' like it.
What the hell, Daiki? You're gonna
turn him down? What a waste!
If it was me, I would've gladly
taken the boss up on his offer.
This car is awesome. It's so awesome,
you start giggling once you're inside!
I know, but...
...I thought that using your own
car was a rule or something.
And my EK is tricked out to where
it's unbeatable on the downhill.
Look, don't put too much stock into this, Daiki.
I've heard of Project D,
and compared to the intense training
we've gone through at the Toudou School,
the level of those guys is disappointingly low.
Yeah, I know that. But...
Somehow... Somehow, doesn't it
piss you off? This Project D thing.
I don't know about the Internet
and homepages and stuff,
but this whole thing of showing off
what they're doing to a large audience
makes it clear that
they've gotten far too uppity.
I guess.
This showoff manner of theirs is inexcusable!
I want to show them that there
are a lot of fast racers out there!
Yeah, you're right. Really drive the
point home to 'em... with your EK9.
Yeah.
Say, Ryosuke...
I've been thinking about this for a while,
and don't you think the D homepage
is a little too confrontational?
No, it's fine.
It's just fine the way it is.
When we arrive at our destinations,
we must play the part of the hated villain.
But if that's the case...
Yes. Our opponents will
become emotional, agitated.
The more so, the better.
If it is not an urgent, frenzied race,
then it has no meaning.
Winning races and setting new
records is one of D's objectives,
but this project has another, separate purpose.
And therein lies the true
meaning behind the initial "D"!
Hold on a second. This is all news to me.
Yes, it would be.
I have yet to inform anyone of it.
That's pretty shifty, Ryosuke.
Okay, so tell me. What does the "D" stand for?
You'll know soon enough, Fumihiro.
And just when is "soon"?
When this project is complete.
It looks like they'll clear out
all the local cars for us.
The course will be reserved just for us.
Reserved or not, there'll be a
route for general cars, right?
No, this road is still under construction,
so it's not open for traffic.
It looks like there won't be any
general cars at all going through.
Under construction...
So that's why. Even just watching the video,
it seemed like an incredible course.
There's some serious height
differential and winding roads...
It's newly paved and the
roads have plenty of width,
but there are lots of falling rocks, and the
road surface can't exactly be called pretty.
Keisuke!
Huh? You're here? What are you doing?
What do you mean, "You're here?"
I came as the driver for the second van.
Keisuke! Once the settings are ready,
please let me sit in the
passenger's seat for one race!
I want to see your driving
up close, learn from it!
I don't know. I'm not sure
it'll be possible to do that.
This time will be especially intense.
It will?
Don't you feel anything at all, Kenta?
All right. Preparations are okay!
You can go now, Keisuke.
Okay.
We're going, too.
All right.
They're so confident, it's eerie.
For them to open up the
entire course, let us borrow it...
Even I can taste how much pressure there is.
Just what kind of race are they
going to run? The Toudou School.
Kyoichi Sudou of Team Emperor
is a graduate of the Toudou School,
which should give us a general idea, yes?
Underhanded beasts like him abound.
Guys on Sudou's level abound?!
Hey Ryosuke, D's only just gotten started.
Shouldn't we have put this off till a little later?
No.
If the project is such that
it could be crushed here,
then it could not have won later anyway.
In this one night, we shall
put ourselves to the test.
We shall unify our efforts
and crush the Toudou School!
Project D, eh? They seemed more
respectable than I'd imagined.
To be honest, I was impressed.
As a team, they looked quite efficient.
Yeah, I feel the same.
Those three minivans were stuffed
with tires and parts for the undersides.
The FD and the Eight-Six each had
their own mechanics, all working busily.
They were a pretty capable bunch.
Some really smart guy's probably
giving out the orders, huh?
Judging by appearances, they may
be more skilled than we thought.
Up till yesterday, I wasn't
looking forward to this at all, but...
A race by outside rules sure looks fun!
Races between Toudou students are
way too strict and are no fun at all.
They get you for the tiniest mistake
and you'll get chewed out by
Mr. Toudou if you slip up even a little.
Compared to that, a race by outside
rules is only half-serious, right?
I'd like to try. Let me do it!
I wanna try, too!
Come on, be reasonable.
Defer to the graduates, your seniors,
and let the active racers take the lead here.
Daiki's EK will take the downhill...
...and my Integra Turbo will take the uphill.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
In exchange, on the off chance that you lose,
we're not gonna cut y'all any slack.
'Cause you'll be muddying
the name of the Toudou School.
Yeah! Whoever loses has to pay
a penalty of one million yen!
A million yen?!
That's pretty steep...
This isn't funny, sir!
Water temperature is stable.
How is the traction?
It feels great. I can really open the throttle.
Once you've put in the oil, I'm gonna try
another two or three runs with this setup.
All right.
The twists in this road are incredible...
This course's downhill is dangerous!
I changed out your brake pads
with some really durable ones.
That will cause a corresponding drop in
your absolute braking. Be careful about that.
Got it. I'm going now, Matsumoto.
I'd like to check your pads after five laps,
so come back here once you're done.
Okay.
The faces of Ryosuke and
the others are different.
What is this feeling?
It's a sense of anxiousness they didn't
have when on expeditions as the Red Suns.
I think something incredible is happening.
I'm scared. So scared I wanna run away!
So acting as a driver for Project D...
...begins by learning to endure this?
Iketani! Itsuki!
It's coming up tonight, huh?
Project D vs. the Toudou School!
You really have a lot of free time, don't you?
Hey, aren't you looking forward to it?
Seeing what kind of race Takumi will run.
Yes, but it's not like we can head to
Tochigi and watch for ourselves, is it?
Why don't you go, Kenji?
After all, you're free, right?
Shut up! Quit saying I'm free
because I don't have a girlfriend!
It's not like I'm coming right out and saying
anything about not having a girlfriend...
--You are saying that, aren't you?!
--Nah, nah.
Tonight, eh? But this time, even Takumi...
The sun's finally going down, huh?
I couldn't sleep very well last night.
This day sure has felt long.
Why are things so tense?
Maybe because yesterday we couldn't
see the local guys in their cars at all.
It's nerve-wracking not being able
to see your opponents' racing.
We can't get any data on them either.
But the flip side of that is, they
didn't get to see our racing either.
I've got a bad feeling.
Or maybe I'm over-thinking things.
Sure, there's such a thing as having
a level of absolute confidence,
but we haven't been blown off like that
once since our days with the Red Suns.
Fumihiro, that stuff doesn't
bother me in the slightest.
I've raced different people before joining
this team, and it's always been like this.
I can concentrate more if I don't
know anything about my opponent.
It's about racing down the road in front of you,
not thinking about needless things, right?
Right now, I'm enjoying this
so much that I can't take it.
Fujiwara...
I don't know how to put it, but...
...this is a whole lot of fun.
Oh.
When I hear it like that,
Fujiwara's actually right.
He is, isn't he?
That's incredible, being able
to enjoy a situation like this.
He's "big," but on a strange scale.
He's a different type of driver
from Ryosuke and Keisuke.
Akina's Eight-Six, Takumi Fujiwara.
It's no wonder we're all worked up,
you having made it this far.
We've got not choice but to believe in
the downhill ace that Ryosuke chose...
Daiki?
I'd like to check the brake area, so I'm going
to borrow a jack and some tools, Sakai.
Sure.
A final check for tonight's race?
Nothing so dramatic...
To be honest, my heart's not in this.
I can't get myself motivated.
I sort of picked up on that. You haven't
been acting too excited since last night.
It's because of the other guys' cars, right?
Yeah! You get it, right?
Most of all, that Eight-Six.
Even if you went running circles around it,
it would just be like bullying the weak, right?
What I saw yesterday has
really gotten me bummed out.
No matter how good the driver is, I can't
find a single thing to get fired up about!
Even that FD would've
made a better opponent.
This is just like you, this hang-up
of yours. What's the big deal?
Everyone knows it doesn't
matter what car it is,
when it comes to the downhill,
there's no way you're gonna lose!
Change your mood around
and show him just how big a gap
in skill there is between you two.
These guys were the ones who challenged us.
There's no reason to hold back, right?
Even if your opponent is
some inferior Eight-Six.
I'm Takumi Fujiwara.
Daiki Ninomiya.
He's a young one. This is
Project D's downhill racer, eh?
We'd like to run these as lead/follow races.
Choose whichever position
you like for the first race.
Are you for real? We're local racers,
and we've got the advantage.
This is our racing style.
That's awfully confident of you.
Fine. In that case...
For the first race, I'll follow.
Okay, then shall we begin?
You're okay coming from behind?
Wouldn't going first have
gotten this over with easier?
Probably... But there's been a little snag.
You get it, don't you? This guy isn't
the walk in the park we thought he'd be.
Ah. He chose to come behind for the first race?
Put Fujiwara on.
Fujiwara. It's Ryosuke.
Hello?
Fujiwara, listen closely.
I have two basic instructions.
Okay... Okay.
Understood.
We're counting on you, Fujiwara.
Fumihiro.
Today's opponent is really amazing.
I can feel it. He's incredibly fast.
Awesome...
Start out slow, then open the throttle
when you come out of the first right.
The Eight-Six will start first,
with you following.
Understood.
The driver of that Eight-Six seems
a lot more legit than I'd imagined.
I chose to come from behind
because I'd gotten a little curious.
Why an Eight-Six? What can
you do with a car like that?
I'll have you show me!
Okay, go! Let's get started!
--They're starting!
--The downhill's gonna start!
Can you hear that, Ryosuke?
It'll be starting soon...
The critical night for Project D
to ask itself what it's capable of!
Hey, the coming of a new generation
Calling now for the arrival of a new era
How long are you going to
pretend you've forgotten?
(Tension that seems like it'll
rip my heart) This heartache...
Within those eyes,
something that can't be held back...
(Yeah, this image that won't let me go)
...stares intently at the night
Yes, the two who didn't even know how
to reach out and touch someone's
heart are already, from here...
(Hey, the coming of a new generation,
Check it, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Strike the sleeping dream awake
(Skillz enough to rend the night!)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
A risky tune that rocks the times
Blast my desire
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
break what you wanna break)