"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
I've come all the way to Kanagawa!
One and a half months behind
his arch rival, Fujiwara Takumi
Takeuchi Itsuki finally steps
into the land of Hakone!
You got it completely wrong.
You're just a sightseer.
The woman at the kiosk told me that it's rare
to see Mt. Fuji so clearly at this time of year.
Does this mean something good will happen?
It should! Today is Project D's
final battle in Kanagawa!
Takumi's victory is guaranteed!
I hope it's that simple.
Oh, I thought I recognized that voice.
Nakazato and Shoji
of the Myogi Night Kids?!
I knew you guys would be here
because this is the final race.
It's great that you came
all the way to support us.
You know, that sounds really disturbing.
Don't think of Fujiwara Takumi as
the representative of your team only.
Project D carries the hopes
of everyone in the Gunma area.
So today is the last day we
get to see Mt. Fuji from this deck.
I still can't believe the situation I'm in.
It still feels weird that
I'm a member of Project D.
You might as well thank me.
I went all the way to Akina to invite you.
Yeah, you did.
Wipe that look off.
Don't lose.
I haven't seen your opponent yet,
but I sense something really bad.
My intuition as a street racer is usually correct.
Your opponent must be like a ghost, and you'll have a tough time.
Seriously?!
But I don't think you'll lose.
I'm saying it because you were like a
ghost before, but now I can see you.
So you won't lose.
We've gotta win.
If they're focused on the data, we just
have to be better than we are now.
Act 12  [ Brothers ]
Great day, isn't it?
Look, the surface of
Ashino Lake shines like a mirror.
I haven't seen you for a while.
I want to enjoy the hot spring
and drink tonight. It'll be fun.
What are you talking about, Sayuki? We don't have time for that tonight.
I know. I was joking.
I've come all the way from Karuizawa
to root for the cute Takumi.
I'm looking forward to seeing
how handsome he has become.
That aside, how are you
doing in the races?
It's tough.
I hate to admit it, but I'm always blown
away by the level of those around me.
After I started racing, I realized
how great professional drivers are.
Project D's achievement
is incredible, almost divine.
A lot of pros have been defeated.
It might be different this time around.
Sidewinder has a professional manager.
You might not know this, but this event has
caught the attention of people from all sides.
If they win, it will cause a stir.
This might not end as a mere carnival among a small group of street racers.
Is this battle going to be tough?
Probably so.
Kubo Eiji's bio is very interesting.
He used to work at the racing
division of a large manufacturer
but he left the company a few years ago, and now he manages his own shop.
He develops aftermarket parts while he builds
demo cars to compete for times in the circuits.
His parts are known for
their high performance.
He's a real pro.
What's unique is that he used to compete in rallying,
and even won some big prizes in provincial races.
He sounds tough, the circuit part really creates an almighty air about him.
You're right.
By the way, Fumihiro...
What's today's pasta?
I beg you, please.
Can you call and cancel the event?
You can't do that any more.
If you really don't want to do it,
you should call Hojo yourself.
That's impossible. He's scary.
Stop talking like a little child.
You said you'd do it, so be
responsible for what you said.
I don't feel like it.
And there's a show I want to watch, too.
Are you scared?
I've never felt fear, but
this is too much of a bother.
I don't understand the
meaning of racing cars.
What's the point?
You should ask Hojo yourself.
Whether you drive or not,
you're obligated to see Hojo on time.
It's like they're glued together.
From where I stand
you're just plain creepy
No matter how close you are, that won't
bring you victory. I'll let you know that.
Hojo
I've finished my data
collection and analysis.
I think I know the combat potential of the FD,
based on the data from the first three races
in Kanagawa and last night's practice.
Your NSX's settings have
been completed accordingly.
Let's take advantage of the
NA engine and mid ship layout.
Traction is everything in hill climbing.
The key is how efficiently the car can transfer
its power to the ground at the exit of each corner.
If you can gain a 0.1 second advantage in one section,
you can gain a 1 second advantage in ten sections.
Motorsports are plain and simple.
It's all about physics, although
I don't have to explain it to you now.
Let me get to the point.
Based on the assumption of using the
same driver in the same environment
your car should have a 15 second advantage.
15 seconds is not a big advantage
for the entire distance of the course.
Their FD is far more refined than expected, which is my miscalculation, but
I did my best under the given circumstances.
Do you have any qualms with
only a 15 second advantage?
It's enough.
Who do you think I am, Kubo?
Do you think I'll lose to some punk
from Gunma in driving technique?
You can't make light
of the punk from Gunma.
If you fail to use that 15 second
advantage properly, you might get screwed.
Cool!
Even though it's only free practice,
it still gave me goose bumps.
Takahashi Keisuke is going
to race against that monster?
How is it, Hojo?
Pretty good. Well done.
Mr. Kubo!
What? Inui hasn't come yet?
I called his mother, and found out
that he left home a while ago.
It's like he's playing hooky,
not from school, but from racing?
What should we do? Should we
arrange a substitute for the downhill?
Do that, but only as insurance.
We'll wait for Inui until the last moment.
Chickening out right when it counts.
What a brat.
I think he's out there
somewhere wondering what to do.
I'm sure he'll make up his mind and
show up before the downhill race starts.
I hope so.
I thought you'd never
show up in Hakone again.
The Grim Reaper GT-R is
no more, but I'm still alive.
I'll go wherever I want to.
We haven't talked like this in a while.
I'm sorry, Gou.
I've caused a lot of problems
for you and our father.
Brother, why did you come here?
To watch your driving.
You got a problem with that?
I'm not going to give you
any advice like I did before.
You have a great strategist anyway.
There's just one thing.
Ryosuke is big.
You're fortunate.
As a man who loves cars and mountain
passes, you can't be happier than this.
Do your very best.
Use everything you've learned.
And enjoy yourself.
This time, I'll watch you until the end.
It's about to start.
This hill climb is going to be good.
You were talking to your
little brother a while ago.
What kind of advice did you give him?
I didn't give him anything of the sort.
I just removed a heavy burden from his back.
You can't perform well by using
negative emotions as motivation.
I just figured he wouldn't be able to defeat
Ryosuke's little brother in that condition.
I see.
My Zero Theory has a similar rule,
which is to get rid of all negative emotions.
Anger, jealousy, grudge, self glory, and sadness.
Those negative emotions will not
guide a driver in the right direction.
Do you know why Project D is so strong?
They always look like they're having fun.
They love cars and mountain passes.
That's what drove them until now.
No matter how difficult the situation becomes,
they somehow find a reason to enjoy it.
On the other hand, Kanagawa
drivers aren't enjoying this at all
because their sensibility
and pride get in the way.
You corner yourself the moment you think there's no way you can lose.
You've got to have fun.
Rather than winning or losing, it's a matter of whether you can enjoy this or not
especially because today is
the final day of the carnival.
Five seconds to the start.
Four
Three
Two
One
Go!
Here they come.
Incredible.
The NSX looks much more
aggressive than during practice.
It hugs the road like a real supercar
Watching it gives me chills.
Plus, it's in the front position, which means the
FD has no chance of winning if the race drags on.
I don't like his lack of focus.
What's on your mind?
I see your hesitation from behind.
Brother, you can't show up
and spout such nonsense.
You know what my responsibilities are.
I did everything in
preparation to win this race.
My motivation was high enough.
But you still think it's not enough?
I don't want to lose no matter what
so what were you trying to say, Brother?
You could have jinxed him.
I wonder if Gou will
understand your true intentions.
Regardless of his motivation,
I still don't think Sidewider will lose.
They spent enough time on
preparations in order to win.
They have a strategist named Kubo Eiji.
Kubo, huh?
That old fart stinks.
He's just sneaky, nothing like Ryosuke, who has aesthetic quality.
I see. That sounds more
like the Hojo Rin I know.
Gou might be confused for a
short period of time, but he'll get it.
First, he has to empty his mind
so that he can recall what's truly important.
Omiya, what kind of driver is Hojo of Sidewinder?
I know Rin, the older brother
but I've never competed in the circuit
against Gou, because he's much younger.
The Hojo Brothers are pretty
well known on the circuit.
I remember the older Rin always guided his
younger brother by showing him the ideal lines.
They seemed to like each other,
and were exceptionally fast to boot.
They're very similar in some aspects to the Takahashi Brothers of Project D.
The cool headed and logical older brother and the emotional younger brother.
You can say they are alike,
especially the younger brothers.
They both drive a peaky car with a narrow margin
of control, and they compete in cornering speed.
Concentration and mad dash
speed are their strengths.
This will undoubtedly become a sprint race.
The car in the lead will
make a dash at some point.
They just passed the second hairpin.
The second hairpin, huh?
From there, section 2 is a mid speed stage where the cornering speed is slow.
Section 4, which is between
two hairpin curves, is similar
so section 2 and 4 are where
the NSX will perform better.
It has a clear advantage in terms of section time.
That's because of better braking due to the mid ship
layout, and the NA engine's immediate response.
The first key point is section 2.
If we can surprise the FD driver
by picking up the pace there
he'll wear down his tires
just trying to catch up.
NA cars are easier on tires,
compared to turbo charged cars.
If we hold on until section 4
and launch a full attack
the rear wheel drive, turbo charged FD won't be able to keep up.
Given the fact that Hojo chose the front position, that must be his scenario.
The battle will take a new turn from there.
I don't understand.
We used to drive just for fun,
but that was a long time ago.
There's something strange
about my brother now.
I'd better stop thinking so hard.
I just have to show
how fast I normally drive
with this car.
He's started to show sharper movements.
I don't like this.
He suddenly pulls away even
if I don't make any mistakes
which is exactly what my brother predicted.
He gives off the same
feeling as a certain someone.
I'd be panicked if I hadn't anticipated this.
But this isn't where the real battle takes place.
He might be shocked by
the NSX's speed more or less.
The hill climb of this vehicle class was
always fought between turbo charged cars.
The NSX is the only exception, as far as domestic sports cars are concerned.
The expensive and large engine is
mounted in the middle of the chassis
which gives the car superb
handling on a twisty course.
The high cornering speed
of the mid ship layout
and the fast cornering exit speed
of the NA engine's linear response.
The butt kicking acceleration of the NA engine will become even handier on public roads
with so many more short
corners than circuits have.
But I don't think he's upset,
because he's familiar with the type of driver who
has a unique style of using the NA engine's advantage.
You mean Fujiwara?
I think Hojo Gou's NSX driving
style is similar to Fujiwara's.
If you adapt that type
of driving to the hill climb.
That's a difficult opponent to deal with.
That's true.
But I knew early on that our
opponent would be using an NSX.
It's not like Keisuke and I just
sat back and waited for today.
We have our own trump card.
Keisuke, use all the skills you've
learned up until today in this race.
I don't get it.
What did they come here for?
Even women like them.
It's odd to see someone like
them in a place like this.
What should I do?
I can't just show up like nothing's happened.
The meeting time is long past.
But I can't go home either.
Mom would be angrier than Hojo.
Why am I always like this, running away at the
most critical moment and disappointing Mom?
But the person who's most disappointed is...
Hey, young man!
What's the matter?
You look so gloomy.
Well, um... nothing really.
Really?
You've been looking down and
sighing for quite some time.
You look like you're a high school
student. Do you love cars?
Did you come here to see the battle?
It's not that I love them,
but I feel like I do more or less...
More or less, huh? Oh, whatever.
I'm Sayuki.
This sexy lady is Mako.
What's your name?
Shinji... Inui Shinji.
They just passed the third hairpin.
I have their section time.
Looks like their pace has increased.
So far, it's going as planned.
Good enough.
Shinji, do you live around here?
Yes.
We came all the way from Gunma.
Amazing, huh?
Yeah.
Why did you come all the
way here just to see a race?
Well, that's because we
used to be street racers.
Besides, it's fun.
Right, Mako?
Yes, it is.
It's thrilling just to watch, and it's even more
fun if you sit behind the steering wheel.
Fun?
Here they come!
Why? What made them so excited?
What's your take, Mako?
Hard to say, but at least
the NSX's traction is impressive.
The exit of this corner is really steep, but it
accelerated quickly without losing balance.
The FD is at a disadvantage after all,
because its response was one step behind.
Hojo's red car wasn't having fun.
But the yellow car was smiling.
They passed the hairpin at the observatory,
and have entered section 4.
This is where it begins.
It's begun.
I can't conserve the tires from here
on, but I'm counting on you, my FD.
Please hold on.
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.