This is fun.
It's not about logic.
You can't just allow your
opponent to pull away.
If I see a car trying to
outrun me, I must chase it.
It's only natural.
It makes my blood boil.
The view is different from usual.
I'm going at an extraordinary pace.
I can't stop. How can
I quit having this much fun?
He's fast.
Not only is my car under-steering,
but it's over-steering as well?!
I've never worn the front tires
so much in a hill-climb before.
He must have the same problem.
Dammit!
I can gain on him a bit if I can
go flat-out for at least 3 seconds.
I have to shed every tenth of a
second I can in order to keep up.
After that curve there's a
4 second flat-out segment.
I must take every opportunity one by one.
Is my entry speed too fast?
No, I've gotta go for it.
Swing the tail a bit,
and use four-wheel drift
I have to keep on pushing, or I'll fall behind.
I have to push it.
Mako, Sayuki, I have to go.
Go? Where?
The best part of the
show is about to begin.
Why don't we watch the
downhill race from here together?
No, I.
I must go.
Mako, please watch me from here.
I might defeat Fujiwara Takumi.
What is that supposed to mean?
Could Shinji be?
Just like Takumi,
he's driving an Eight-Six
and it's a Trueno to boot.
No way.
Takumi's opponent today is
Shinji?!
Hey, the goal is all on the satnav.
Space out and go on, no problem.
100% safety, 0% risky?
Don't stress over minor things,
just toss that out the window.
Who decides what's right?
Don't bother about stuff like that.
You just have to stay focused on
All the things you love, and beyond the raging storm.
(So now it goes above and beyond)
To infinity!
Outsoar the Rainbow.
Don't just stand and watch.
Amp up your senses and fly high.
Let go and fly free even farther.
(Ain't no satisfied, so never stop to fly)
Infinity.
(You can reach the goal on your own)
Initial D
Crawling desperately several thousand times.
Only they are the ones that deserve to look back and talk.
History will prove that someday.
The race was at such a miraculous high pace it
exceeded the limits Kubo Eiji had set for the car.
It tells us something about human potential.
The margin of victory between the
winner and the loser is very thin.
The goddess of the mountain pass
cast her smile on Keisuke tonight.
Keisuke's honest passion and love for mountain passes must have surpassed Hojo Gou's by a small margin.
Act 1  [ Natural ]
Brother
Did you have a chance to
talk to Takahashi Keisuke?
No, but I felt like we had an elaborate communication while we were driving.
There's no need for a conversation.
He must feel the same way.
I lost.
I feel frustrated, but also refreshed.
I saw views I had never seen before.
I see.
If that's the case, you'll grow from here.
You must have done your best.
Good job.
Ouch
It's all yours.
I'm counting on northern
Kanto's fastest downhiller.
You're just too awesome,
like I always think, Keisuke.
It's in my bones.
I'm glad you came, Shinji.
I was worried.
What changed your mind?
I was moved while I was
watching you drive, Hojo.
I want to be a hero.
I want to race. Let me do it.
I like your expression. Go for it.
There's no one else.
Only you can stop
Project D's consecutive victories.
Oh, right.
You don't need to hear stuff like that.
Just express yourself as you like.
Drive freely and have fun.
Tonight's stage is so thrilling.
You're the star, Shinji.
Okay.
In my opinion, we should
take the lead position regardless.
Shinji has overwhelming speed, but his
opponent has more experience with battles.
Eliminating all uncertain factors is
what a strategic plan is all about.
He can make the best use of
his talent if he drives as the lead.
This match must be
settled on the first run.
I have no objections, Kubo.
Shinji has a good look on his face.
When he's concentrating,
his skills are unmatched.
He's Sidewinder's Eight-Six driver?
He looks so young.
He's probably younger than Fujiwara.
This is like a joke.
Has Fujiwara ever raced
anyone younger than he is?
And why an Eight-Six?
Let's completely crush Project D.
This is the first street race for our miracle boy,
who grew up on the mountain pass of Kanagawa.
Brother
Yeah, this final battle could
be his toughest challenge.
I'm Fujiwara Takumi.
I'm Inui Shinji.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
As expected, they chose to lead.
The first run is the hardest part.
Think of him as your strongest opponent ever.
Keep up with him, even if you
have to use the tires to the fullest.
He's tough.
I understand. I'll do my best.
Let's begin.
Five seconds
Finally
It's finally time for Project D's downhill ace,
Fujiwara Takumi, to take off!
Four
Calm down, Itsuki.
That being said, I'm getting excited.
To be honest, so am I.
Of course we are!
Takumi represents our home region of Gunma!
He's more like our pride.
Right, Takumi is our pride.
Please win.
Three
Two
One
Go!
Hey, those two Eight-Sixes
have different body shapes
especially the chasing one.
Yeah, the Eight-Six has two kinds,
the Levin and the Trueno
and each has a two-door
and three-door type.
Project D's Eight-Six, with the rear hatch, is called a three-door hatchback
and the other is called a two-door sedan.
Oh, I see.
The Eight-Six was very
successful in motor sports
but the two and three door types
were used in different fields.
The three-door was mainly used in circuit
racing because of its aerodynamic advantage.
The two-door was the mainstream in rally
and gymkhana because of the stiffer body.
If that's the case
does Sidewinder's two-door have
the advantage in a street race like this?
Well, in this case
I guess it does.
What the?
It broke.
I've been using this since I bought my Eight-Six.
Man, this'll bring bad luck.
I'd better toss it.
Wow, he's fast.
I'd better call it a day.
For some reason, I can't concentrate.
On a day like this, it's no use,
no matter how many balls I hit.
Mika
I'm just not feeling it.
I'll study at home, so can we stop?
Because today
Is something bothering you today?
No, it's nothing.
Just let me stop for today.
Takumi, I'm waiting for your text.
At one point, I was getting worried,
but at least he reached the starting line.
He still acts like a child when he shouldn't.
I don't know how to apologize.
You don't have to apologize.
He came to the starting line,
holding his head high.
Once he grabs the steering wheel,
Shinji has a different personality.
Do you really think so?
I hope that's the case.
I just have a bad feeling.
I feel like he's going to do something stupid.
There's no need to worry.
He may be Sidewinder's youngest member
but he's a seasoned driver
with the most experience.
You used to say that, didn't you?
Um, yes.
I wonder how many years
we've driven this road.
It's been twelve years since
he moved up to elementary school.
My job is located at a spa resort
on the other side of the mountain.
I drove up and down the mountain pass
every day with Shinji in the passenger seat.
It's only natural that Shinji
knows this road very well.
I see.
He has a good memory, but since he
doesn't study his grades aren't good.
But he has a high IQ,
which shocked his teacher.
He may have exceptional spatial cognition.
When did he start driving?
Well, umm, I can't say this too loud
but probably sometime during
upper elementary school.
Wow
That's not even funny.
It all started out of his kindness.
I was raising him all by myself,
and I had a lot of worries.
He probably couldn't stand watching me drive while I was fighting to stay awake.
I remember very well that I was
surprised by his excellent steering work.
I drove in the morning because traffic was heavy, so he only drove at night.
I see. That's why he's
unusually fast on the downhill.
Now I know the reason behind Shinji's speed.
He learned mountain pass driving
as if he was playing a game.
His steering work is the product
of constant repetitive training.
It's like a refined art.
Why is he so fast?
I think you have a point when
it comes to him playing a game.
He looked happy every time he drove.
That car is a treasure of my late husband.
Because he was a rally driver, I have some knowledge about technique
I didn't teach him anything.
I didn't even give him any advice.
His driving is completely self taught,
without any theoretical background.
He's a natural born talent.
I've been watching him drive
for so long, so I know that
the center of his technique is no-brake driving.
No braking?
Using the brakes as little as
possible must be his game.
It's nonsense from a
driving technique standpoint
but his goal was never speed.
He doesn't use the accelerator very often.
Because it's the downhill, he can use inertia.
While focusing on steering, he tries to
find the lines that he can drive smoothly.
When he's at the wheel, you can sleep comfortably in the passenger seat.
We're home, Mom.
We're home.
Did you sleep well?
I want to drive in a way that'll let you
sleep because you always look tired.
Another success today.
He's a kind boy.
Since he caught Mr. Hojo's
attention a year ago
he's been developing the basics
behind technique and theory
but his intuitive no-braking
feeling hasn't changed.
He must be an ordinary
driver on other courses.
This road is the only one
he knows so completely.
His body knows the limit of how
fast he can enter each corner
literally, each and every single corner.
The limit he knows is totally
different from that of other drivers.
If that's the case, you really
don't have to worry so much.
Shinji finishes his job so
smoothly that I almost hate him.
He looks like he wants to tell me he doesn't have to do anything special.
Horsepower isn't very important
to fast driving on the downhill.
The downslope will help a 100-hp
car accelerate like a 150-hp car.
If you're up against a 200-hp car,
you'd feel like you're fighting a 300-hp car
but that's completely useless on
the downhill of a mountain pass.
The balance between weight
and agility is more important.
Fujiwara won every race on Akina because he had everything necessary to make up for the Eight-Six's lower power.
My EG6, your R32
and the Takahashi brothers, who were considered the
fastest in the Gunma area back then, lost because of that.
But this time, something's different.
The trump card Fujiwara had back then seems to be in the hands of his opponent this time around.
It's an ironic twist of fate that the last battle of the
final round happens to be a race against an Eight-Six.
I don't know about that.
Sure, the Sidewinder kid has a dangerous aura
but Fujiwara has gained experience
and developed his skills over the past year.
He's got something beyond logic.
Even when he's pressured, he can find a way to
break through with his miraculously swift reactions.
He has something that can make it happen.
The legend of Fujiwara Takumi will never end.
Why?
I fell behind a little through a
series of a few tight corners.
Both are Eight-Sixes, so why?
I can't keep up with him in the corners.
I've never had this happen before.
Bring it back, hey, rock'n roll!
Life goes on, I was content with a little bit of hope.
Someone decided my future so I only had to wait.
(Just got to get you back and bring it back on)
How small I was, bust it up!
(Here we go, 1, 2)
Move it up and break it!
I've gotta run for my dream now.
(Bring back, yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll!)
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
It's a stage on the edge.
(Oh, Yeah)
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
Not even a millimeter of hesitation.
(Check it out, come on!)
Truth is, there aren't many things worth holding on to.
(Give it up yo! Give it up yo!)
Act a bit tough and gamble away all I've got.
Play the game!
Let's gamble, hey jumbo.
Now shake your bum and do the rumble.
Three sharp lines and maxed out tension.
Here comes the M.O.V.E trio while everyone's asleep.
Even if they call us annoying for all the noise
I like to move it, move it.
I'll make you move into it.
Let's play the sensual noise of the domestic cars.
Show a dazzling desire.
Warp all the way from the start to the goal.
Let's overtake at Mach 55, to your next stage.