"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri
Misugita yume no daishou
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
Akuseru funde gomakasu
Yoru ni kowareta mama
Shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Dare no kimagure kara
Sekai sae mo owarisou de
Break into the night, it's the time
Obieta me o shite lost in the night
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Jibun sae mo kizutsukete
Taoreru kurai ni Love me so much
Subete o sutete anata o
Aisuru koto sae dekitara
Kitto sunao ni naresou
Morning, Takumi!
What's with the sleepy face?
I was born with it.
Hey, it's getting closer.
The race against Ryosuke Takahashi!
I'm so excited that I can't focus on classes.
We're talking about Ryosuke Takahashi,
the fastest and most popular racer in Gunma.
Do you have any special strategy, Takumi?
No.
I'm not versatile enough to change
my race based on my opponents.
It makes no difference.
I just race the fastest way I know how.
If the opponent is faster, I'll lose.
Otherwise, I'll win.
That makes sense.
I'm counting on you, you know?
What if you ended up beating him?!
That'd be so cool and awesome and...!
How embarrassing!
"Act 24: Akagi's White Comet!"
Welcome!
Oh, it's just you.
I got something very interesting.
You mean you got an adult movie, Kenji?
Sorry, Itsuki.
This is better than that!
Better than that?
They're racing.
It doesn't look like Akina.
Just watch the tape.
Can we watch that last part in slow motion?
It's Ryosuke Takahashi!
He looks so much younger!
This was three years ago.
How did you find this?
Some diehard fan videotaped his races.
What a drift!
Angling into a corner like that is miraculous.
So cool!
Hey, I was actually there for that race!
I still remember it.
Back then, he was a lone wolf
and didn't belong to any team.
They called him "Akagi's White Comet."
Akagi's White Comet...
That sounds so cool that I'm shivering.
What about the Red Suns?
Ryosuke personally handpicked
a few premium street racers
to form the Red Suns.
That's why the quality of
his team is much higher
than that of our "friendly" team.
Now, he and his brother Keisuke
are known as "The Rotary Brothers."
But to me, he will always be
"Akagi's White Comet."
What are you guys watching?
I'm sorry!
--Turn it off.
--It's okay.
Keep watching.
That's good stuff!
--Takumi's really racing him, huh?
--Yes.
I bet it'll draw the biggest crowd ever.
Ryosuke Takahashi is a superstar,
and now Takumi has become
famous as "Akina's Eight-Six."
That's right. A mysterious downhill specialist
has suddenly appeared in Akina this summer!
I'm so excited!
Honestly, who do you think will win?
I hate to say this,
but I don't think Takumi
stands a chance against him.
This opponent is unreal.
I have to agree.
Ryosuke Takahashi is fast... ridiculously fast.
That fast, huh?
He was already the fastest then,
but he's gotten even faster.
On top of all the street races,
he's repeatedly won the Gymkhana
and various circuit competitions.
He holds many course records
and has never lost a race.
His undefeated streak is unbroken.
And they say that he's never had
to give his all in any of his races.
He only uses half his ability
and still defeats any opponent.
So no one has ever really
seen his absolute best yet.
Well, if Takumi can keep up
with him, it's a job well done.
But...
There you go with your negativity again.
Can't you be more optimistic?
Then who do you think will win, boss?
Well...
Takumi has beaten Keisuke
and Night Kids' Nakazato!
And there was Usui's Sileighty
and the duct tape death match!
And a race in the rain!
I think...
I think he'll do just fine.
Ryosuke is by far the best racer
among the elite Red Suns.
Keisuke and Nakazato don't even come close.
To use a boxing analogy, the odds are 10 to 1.
I want Takumi to win.
He's my best friend,
and I want our proud Eight-Six...
...to defeat the FC!
Stop crying.
Boys like cars, don't they?
Sure.
Are cars that exciting?
Sure they are.
They can take you anywhere.
If you had to choose between
your girlfriend and your car,
which would you pick?
I can't compare them.
My girlfriend is one thing
and my car is another.
Racing is very deep.
I've been thinking about
how to get better at it.
Thinking about that makes me feel good.
You're...
--...sexual.
--Huh?!
Where did that come from?!
Why do you say that?
Sorry, I just felt it.
It's women's intuition.
I'm pretty sure that I just got a peek...
...at your hidden sexuality!
What are you saying?
You're not making any sense.
Don't worry. You wouldn't understand.
When is the big race?
Two nights from tonight.
Isn't it against a fast racer?
Yeah.
I want to watch you race.
But maybe I shouldn't.
Don't crash.
You can lose, but don't get hurt.
You have to promise me that.
Ryosuke, you got another invite
from a professional team.
They called me today.
Again? Wow.
Which team?
It's the "Hoshiya"Team.
They're looking for a young, premium racer.
They want you to call them
right away to set up an interview.
I know for sure that you'll make a great pro!
It's very exciting.
What are you gonna do?
Turn it down for me.
Like I said before,
I have no desire to go pro.
What a waste!
Can't you at least talk to them?
He's right, Ryosuke.
I'm not interested in the
professional racing world.
I'm only attracted to street racing,
where anyone can freely express himself.
The Gymkhana and circuit competitions
are the path I took to master street racing.
Right now, there's only one thing on my mind.
The Eight-Six on Saturday.
Done working?
Wanna go for a spin?
--With you?
--Yeah.
I've readjusted the car, so I
thought I'd go for an easy drive.
An easy drive?
I hate it when you talk like that.
"Akina Skate Center"
--Hey, Bunta?
--Yeah?
Did you readjust the car for the big battle?
That's right.
I think I'll speed up a little, Yuichi.
Hold on!
I'm ready. Just a little bit, okay?
Here comes the corner!
What entry speed!
I feel the G-force diagonally behind me.
What the heck are you doing?!
I feel like having a smoke.
Stop that!
Keep your eyes on the road!
Oh, no!
Not too bad.
I'm serious this time!
Let me out!
The tires and engine are adjusted for the race.
How much horsepower does it have now?
Well, I'd say its max is about 260 horsepower.
260 horsepower?!
You downgraded it!
It had at least 350 before.
It did.
Less horsepower?
Why did you have to make it slower?
You should remember that, at times,
you need less horsepower to run faster.
That's how deep street racing is.
The key to downhill success
isn't power... it's balance.
I thought I had adjusted my FC
to make it as fast as possible
both uphill and downhill.
I knew I could handle
even more power downhill,
so I upgraded the turbine
and raised the firing speed.
But in the end, I had to lose all that power.
Regardless of the reason,
this downgrade was humiliating to me.
I had to throw away my pride for this race.
The Eight-Six is that tough of an opponent?
I'm lucky that I've met
such an extraordinary racer.
My racer blood is boiling up.
Let's go.
Less power, but fast!
He clears the corners faster.
There's no way my brother will lose to him now!
Right now, I'm not Ryosuke
Takahashi of the Red Suns.
I'm the lone wolf known as...
...Akagi's White Comet.
I'll win this battle, no matter what!
Takumi!
Hey!
--Race day is finally here!
--Yeah.
It makes me angry, Takumi.
Everyone thinks Ryosuke Takahashi will win.
They say it's like a novice
fighting a heavyweight.
Aren't you offended?
Any plan for a big upset?
Let me see...
No.
Those racers are headed to the pass.
It's finally here.
--Boss?
--Yeah?
I've cleaned up outside.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good job.
--You're going to the race, right?
--Yes.
You still don't think Takumi can win?
No. I know he's exceptional,
but he's still in high school.
He still has very little experience.
I wonder how long he'll even
be able to stay in the race.
Not me.
I actually think he has a chance.
--Why?
--Because...
--Hey.
I better hurry. Good night.
Yeah.
The only reason I think Takumi has a chance...
...is that he's Bunta's son.
The son of that crazy Bunta...
The crowd is gigantic, as expected.
If I were Takumi, I would want to run away.
I would be petrified in
front of all these people.
--Isn't that Usui's Sileighty?
--Really?
I was right.
--They're both cute.
--Yeah.
How about around here?
We may see some good tactics
at these complex corners.
By the way, Mako...
...which one are you rooting for?
Which one?
The Eight-Six, right?
Me, too.
He has a mysterious charisma
that only those who have
raced him can recognize.
You want to root for him
even though he beat you.
Besides, he's...
...so cute! Right?
Come on, Sayuki.
It's almost 9:30.
This is it!
I'm so pumped up!
Here come the Red Suns.
The Takahashi brothers are so cool!
--This is the enemy, eh?
--Ryosuke!
Ryosuke Takahashi is finally here.
Now we wait for Takumi to show up.
The Eight-Six is not here yet.
I expected that.
He always shows up at the very last minute.
Keisuke...
I've been thinking about this for a long time,
but when I lose a street race...
...I'll retire.
What?! What are you saying?
You'll never lose.
Just hear me out.
By "retire," I don't mean quitting racing.
I'll just step down from the number-one spot.
I'll still continue to contribute to the team.
What about our "fastest in Kanto" plan?
It can't happen without you!
Don't make a face.
I have no intention of losing yet.
Remember this, though...
It is inevitable that someday
I will lose to someone.
By the way, there are only two racers
who I think could beat me one day.
One of them is you, Keisuke.
--Me?
--That's right.
I see a racing genius within you.
You'll be even faster one day.
And the other is...
Takumi is here!
Yay, Takumi!
The other one is the Eight-Six, isn't it?
I won't lose to anyone just yet.
Tonight, I'm ready for
my full-scale drift battle!
Ai ni tsukare hate samayotteta koro
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa
Mujaki na hitomi ni miserarete yuku
Sake bara no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku kimi o daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi o shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi o kanadeyou...
Kagayaku mirai e
Kazoe kirenai hodo tashikame aou
Jounetsu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no you ni akaku
tsuyoku, tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani o ushinattemo
kono ude o hanasanai
Utsukushiku karen ni sake...
Kiseki no hana yo
What's wrong, Takumi?
I've been taking challenges as they come,
but this race seems very
different from the others.
--Yeah?
--My heart's pounding,
and I don't know what to do.
--Yeah?
--I find racing very fun and exciting.
--Yeah!
--I'm not sure how successful I'll be...
A very different Takumi is fired up!
Next on Initial D: "The Last Battle!"
Don't miss it!