"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
One, two...!
What's this all about? Joshima and
Hoshino are coming? That's unusual.
The biggest names of Purple
Shadow coming together...
I wonder what's going on.
Don't you know? Project D is coming.
Project D? So Joshima and
Hoshino plan to take them on?
No, no way. One of the younger members
of Purple Shadow will do it, right?
There's no way either of them would
go out in a race. I mean, those two...
They're gods!
They're here! "God Arm"Toshiya Joshima
and "God Foot" Kozo Hoshino!
That stomach of yours is bulging again.
You better lower your cholesterol
or you're not gonna live long.
Leave me alone. "Fatten up,
then slim down," that's my motto.
Also, I make it a point
not to listen to my doctor.
That's a good one!
Project D, huh? It's been a while
since I've felt my blood race.
This may be the folly of a couple
of middle-aged street racers,
but I'm looking forward to it.
"Act 19: God Foot and God Arm"
Mr. Joshima, Mr. Hoshino,
do you really intend to participate?
In this upcoming race...
You bet. Something strange about that?
No, not "strange," but...
Our opponents are basically kids,
so there's no need for you,
our seniors, to participate.
No, age has nothing to do with it.
These folks are kind enough
to come here from Gunma,
so responding in kind is just a matter
of common courtesy, don't you think?
True, they're coming all the way here,
but it's not as if we asked them to...
C'mon, don't say that.
In this case, just keep quiet
and let us do it our way.
It's not as if we're vain enough to think
we're the absolute greatest there is.
When Purple Shadow was first formed,
we taught you guys a lot of different things,
but now, I don't think we could
even keep up with you youngsters.
You must be joking, Mr. Hoshino!
We still don't even come close to you!
Come on, don't be so modest.
You've stood on the winner's podium
at the Tsukuba amateur circuit
race any number of times.
We really like this sort of thing.
Even at our age, it makes us feel like kids.
Okay then, should we bang out
two or three more laps?
Yeah. Gotta shake off some
more of these cobwebs, huh?
Honestly, what a joke. "Cobwebs," my foot.
Those two are always polished
to razor-sharp precision.
God Arm, so named for his
godlike handling capabilities...
Toshiya Joshima.
And God Foot,
named for his superhuman
ability to work the accelerator...
Kozo Hoshino.
They've fought their way through
countless fierce battles...
They're the gods of the mountain pass!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Is Pops not home?
Jeez...
Hello, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
This is Wataru.
I'm in the area. You wanna
get something to eat?
So? Where to next?
Ibaraki.
Ah.
I...
I really am grateful to you. I feel like
you've given me an important hint.
It makes me happy to hear that.
Recently, I feel like I've finally
started to understand the Eight-Six.
Huh?
There it is, the spacey side of him...
We normal folk can't understand
what you say sometimes.
But it's true! I've come to sort of understand it...
...how to race in order to bring out
the Eight-Six's full potential.
What I should do when tackling
a course for the first time...
How to get the right
underbody balance point...
One by one, I've gradually come
to understand those things.
Well, I guess that's what they call progress.
Me, I don't see how you've been able to
race like this without knowing anything.
I might lose someday...
But if that day comes, I think
by then I will have learned more.
About the Eight-Six...
What's this all about? There's
one more support van this time.
Ryosuke and I wrote up a list
of the things we'll need,
and thought that three vans
wouldn't quite be enough.
That's the kind of formidable
opponent we'll be facing.
It's simplest just to think about it that way.
We'll be traveling a long way
this time, so everyone drive safely.
All right!
Let's head out!
Boss, did you hear?
Project D's next opponent...
...is Purple Shadow in Ibaraki.
Huh.
What's more, Kozo Hoshino and
Toshiya Joshima will face them.
That's a surprise.
If you two have time...
...you should go watch that race.
Is Purple Shadow really that good?
Daiki, you may not know this,
but even Mr. Toudou acknowledges
Hoshino and Joshima as his betters.
No way...
Sir, do you think Project D
has a chance of winning?
Every race boils down to luck.
No one knows what'll happen.
Rather than tryin' to
predict somethin' like that,
you should think about how
you would take them on,
then watch what Project D does to face
the giant wall that stands before them.
It should be a good learnin' experience.
Here they are!
"National Park"
"Touge View Park"
Understood. We'll do our part to
make sure things run smoothly.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Huh. They're a nice bunch
of young men, very polite.
Agreed.
Their homepage is a bit confrontational,
so I thought they'd be cocky little brats.
I like these guys.
In return, I'll do them the courtesy
of giving this challenge my all.
For the first time in a while...
this looks like it'll be a good night.
As always, five laps at 80%.
Be sure and concentrate.
Incredible...
Van #4 is filled mostly with spare tires!
And one moped? What would we use this for?
Well, that's for the drivers to use.
The drivers?
I thought I'd have them scout the course
tomorrow evening while it's still light.
Apparently, a moped makes
it easy to spot fractures
or small slopes in the road surface.
That way, you can come up with strategies for
courses where the slightest variable counts.
Walking the course is really the best way,
but this is what Ryosuke came up with,
one of the new approaches
we'll be using from now on.
I get it. Ryosuke sure does
think up a lot of ideas.
I suppose this means if we stick
with the same approach as always,
we won't be able to win...
Now it's okay!
I think this tire balance will
give you a good clean ride.
Just be sure to keep a close eye on traction.
Okay. Here I go.
How is it, Matsumoto?
It's in great shape.
Fujiwara's in fine form as well, eh?
Even the settings he requested make it
seem like he's got a handle on something.
He's different from how he used to be.
I feel that as well.
There were times in the Saitama
area when he was quite conflicted.
Even outside of D's activities, Fujiwara has
been practicing, in ways we haven't seen.
He is definitely getting a handle on something.
In this race, regardless of
whether he wins or loses,
he will experience sudden
explosive growth, Matsumoto.
In any case, Keisuke's FD
sure has gotten flashy.
For your information, the exterior
is 100% to Keisuke's taste.
How is it?
The slopes are steeper than I'd thought,
so this tire balance relies too much on the rear.
Should we raise the back area a bit?
Please do.
Are you Keisuke Takahashi, driver of the FD?
You're quite the looker.
I bet chicks dig you, huh?
I was a hit with the ladies
when I was younger, too.
A guy like that's got an aura,
something you can instantly tell.
Youth is somethin' you can't get back.
Once I hit middle age, I got all this
activity around the belly here,
and getting the young ladies
to turn 'round and look
takes so much effort it makes you wanna cry.
And then there's the extra
money you've gotta spend!
Still...
When I score me some sweet
thing after all that effort,
I feel a kind of happiness I never
could've known in my younger days!
Anyway, one day you'll understand.
You've gotta play the field while you're young.
See ya.
No, wait. I almost forgot
what I really wanted to say.
I've got an important proposal
to make about tomorrow's race.
Proposal? What is it?
How should I put this...?
Normally, a mountain pass
has an uphill and a downhill.
In my case, I haven't tuned my car
thinking only about the uphill...
Aiming for total balance is
the mark of a true racer, right?
That's where my proposal
comes in. For just our race,
what do you say we opt
against an uphill-only stage?
You mean, race on a stage that
combines uphill and downhill?
That's what I mean.
If that's how this is going to be,
I'd like to show off some of
my killer downhill techniques.
Okay. I accept your proposal. With pleasure.
Yes! I appreciate that.
I look forward to our race.
Oh, and one more thing.
Can we do our race first?
Before the downhill?
I get more fired up that way.
I'm the impatient type.
Waitin' just drives me crazy.
Fine. That's okay as well.
Okay! Well, that's that,
and I'm lookin' forward to it!
See ya!
Was that a bad move, brother?
I didn't think I had any reason to refuse.
It's fine. It was an unexpected
proposal, but sure enough,
there was no reason to refuse...
Rather than being disadvantageous,
his proposal in fact counts in our favor.
I take my hat off to him. He casually
made us a most fair proposition.
He is a formidable opponent, Keisuke.
I feel like... sort of invigorated.
It's been a while since I've felt this!
Like I could lose...
That old dude is something else!
What is this? I feel so much
pressure. Far more than usual!
This will be one incredible race!
Man, I'm tired!
You said it.
Keisuke, Fujiwara.
You two will be staying
at a bed-and-breakfast
at the foot of the mountain.
A bed-and-breakfast?
Yes. You can get a good night's
rest in an air-conditioned room.
That's fine and all, but why just us?
It should be obvious.
Because you're the drivers.
No way! I'm fine without!
I'll sleep in my car as always.
Ryosuke, please take the room in my place.
No, Fujiwara. This is my order as team leader.
We are in that season. With days as hot
as these, one can hardly sleep inside a car.
It's important you be rested to
preserve your powers of concentration
for tomorrow's race.
Getting a good night's rest
is for the sake of the team!
I'll take you to the bed-and-breakfast,
so grab your things and get into Van #1.
Fumihiro said he'll come get us around 4:00.
We'll be able to get quite
a bit of sleep, won't we?
I feel bad for the others,
but I sure am grateful to be able to
stretch my legs and sleep like this.
You said it. This is the first time, isn't it?
Since we've started D's expeditions.
Still, this course will make it
hard to go on the offensive.
It's pretty short, but it has some
points that're hard to nail down.
There are lots of corners with lazy turns
and no visible exit point, aren't there?
The roads have lots of twists... It doesn't
seem like a race that'll be settled soon.
That was fast! The idiot's already asleep!
Does he not feel pressure or anything?
He looks like a pushover, but he's
got an irritatingly tough core.
I'm way more sensitive...
What is that boy Kenta doing?
He said he put some tanning oil on
and was going to get some sun.
Idiot. What does he want to get any darker for?
Anyway, these days sure have gotten hot.
Being inside our cars
would be unbearable, huh?
It was a good call, having Keisuke
and Fujiwara rest someplace cool.
That's right. This race will require
peak physical and mental strength.
He even thought this part through.
That's Ryosuke for you.
Yes, indeed...
Fujiwara sure is taking his
sweet time inspecting the course.
He doesn't seem to be coming back, does he?
Keisuke breezed through it
and was back in about 15 minutes.
It's not a competition, you know.
I've got my own pace. I may be fast,
but I saw what I needed to see.
Well, do your best. You'll be racing first today.
Just leave it to me!
I slept nice and cool,
and my body's in top form!
It's about to start. Tonight is a big event!
Just having Joshima and Hoshino participate
in this kind of event makes it big enough!
Those guys are legends in their own time!
Seriously, what do you think about Project D?
Can their drivers compete with the
duo that people refer to as gods?!
They're no ordinary racers, that's for sure.
Both of them are young guys still in their 20s,
but they've been to all the
mountain passes in northern Kanto
and have never lost once.
Then they'd better give it their all.
After all, we came here to watch the gods race!
There sure are a lot of onlookers.
Yeah. Having too many people
here would just cause problems,
so apparently D didn't advertise the time
and place on their homepage this time.
Still, there are fansites out there
that posted the info themselves.
Oh, really? It sure is rough.
Being famous.
My arms are twitching... I can't wait
another second to get out there.
Now Ko, you control your bad
habit of letting your guard down
and not staying alert.
Don't you worry. I've got a reputation
to uphold in Purple Shadow.
I won't lose to some youngster.
I'll show him the techniques
of a middle-aged pro!
We'll start with the hillclimb.
Once you've reached the top,
there will be a pylon.
Without stopping, turn around and come
back down. That will count as one race.
Is that acceptable?
Yeah, sure. It's a combined stage
with an uphill and a downhill.
For the first race, I'd like to lead.
Understood.
All right. Shall we begin?
Let's state our names again. I'm Kozo Hoshino.
Keisuke Takahashi.
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie