"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Tobidase wicked show, kuuki biribiri saku noise
Shibaite norikonase, abarenbou no party
Zettai hikanai kihaku, the dogfight
Buttoi red zone no himei ni shibiretai
Hakanai senkou, like a ryuusei
Isshun no kagayaki demo kamawanai
Kaimamita kichou na fuukei itsuka kataritai
Sou, ima wa honnou no mama dogfight
Shibiretai yume nara koko ni aru
Kagerou yaburu kaze, backfire
Kinou nado sutetekina,
ima kara rocket dance (Dogfight!)
Sakebenai negai ga itamu nara sugu ni oide
You're big time gambler
Orokasa wa utsukushii kyokusen
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Souon mo everywhere
Yokonaguri, 5G hodo no heavyweight
Giri de soukou, miri no koubou
Za-za-zan!
Rakushou de funde ikeru ze, madamada
--They're so fast!
--Awesome!
Wait, Ninomiya's EK9 is comin' from the rear?!
If he'd gone in front, the race prob'ly
would've been over in a second!
Isn't that kinda killin' his advantage?
B-But that Eight-Six ain't exactly slow!
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe it's just me, but it seemed super fast...
I believed he would take the starting position,
but he chose to come from behind, eh?
Impressive. A wise choice.
Big brother?
You told Fujiwara something on the phone
earlier before the race started, right?
What kind of advice did you give?
It was nothing that would
warrant being called "advice."
I merely gave him two basic instructions.
Such as?
I said no matter what, do not look in the
rearview mirror till the end of the first race.
The rearview mirror? In other words,
don't look behind you?
"Act 4: Two Pieces of Advice"
Yesterday, someone said
that racing by outside rules
would be nice and fun or something.
Shit! This is no joke!
At this guy's level, he could participate in
Toudou School races and even hold his own!
Who the hell is he?!
I'm shocked, and not in a small way!
There's never been anyone who
could run this course a single night
and get to this level of mastery,
not even at the Toudou School!
What's more, I don't know what
kind of tuning his car's gotten,
but it can go up against my B16 engine,
and is even incredibly good at turning.
This thing is no Eight-Six!
If an FR is done up this well,
this is the kind of race it's capable of!
With this, they've no doubt
had the advantage in their traveling
battles, winning victory after victory...
But this time, they're out of luck!
This is the home course of us, the Toudou School!
Up till yesterday, we made a lot of
fun of our opponent's Eight-Six...
But right before the start, there was
something about him, a feeling.
That's probably why Daiki
chose to come from behind.
I'm sure I would have made the same choice.
I'd like to see from behind
what kind of race the "fastest
in the Gunma area" can run.
If it's some lousy racing that
betrays your expectations,
you can tear out ahead and end the race.
Yeah, that you could.
They say he's the best of us
currently racing, right?
What's his specialty?
Daiki's good at braking.
Though when you hear "braking,"
it sounds sort of bland...
Nah, that ain't bland at all.
There's no better weapon
than that in the downhill!
If you're a graduate of the Toudou School,
you understand why all too well.
He chose to come behind for the first race?
Fujiwara, listen closely.
Do not look in your rearview mirror,
right up to the end of the first race.
Concentrate solely on your
strategy for the course.
If you run your own race,
you will not be overtaken.
Listen, Fujiwara. No matter what...
...do not look behind you!
I've got the general idea of what
that Eight-Six is capable of.
It's better than I'd thought, but apparently
nothing for me to get worked up about.
Even with the pride of
the Toudou School on the line,
I want to finish this in the first race.
I've gotta tear around him somewhere.
I'll make my chance by putting
as much pressure on him as I can.
I want to see how much he can take!
Awesome! They're so close!
Their bumpers are gonna hit!
It's common knowledge now that in
this class, the FF is faster than the FR.
So this guy must have
the most power ful type R.
I can't just stay behind this Eight-Six forever.
I will definitely end this in the first race!
The thing about braking
when going into a corner is,
what's more important isn't when you
start to brake, it's when you finish.
If the point at which you finish decelerating
and start to turn is too far or too soon,
it'll result in lost time.
Guys with good driving skills will
recover well and won't screw it up,
but every corner definitely has only one
ideal point for releasing the brake pedal.
That's right. Mr. Toudou is always saying that
braking is the most difficult driving skill.
Of course.
Daiki's assessment of that
point is always accurate.
No matter how long a braking maneuver,
the point at which he releases the pedal
is always right on the money.
It's what you call an innate sense.
Daiki...
These days, ABS has become
standard in the racing world.
That's how efficient the current ABS is.
And yet, the Toudou School
has done away with ABS.
First, you gotta learn how to
brake without relying on ABS.
Unless you bludgeon yourself with the
difficulty of braking till you can't stand it,
you'll never understand how to really use ABS.
It's a rule of the Toudou School.
This course doesn't have a center line,
but it's still plenty wide.
There are several points from
which I can overtake him...
But now what?
I use braking to wedge myself into
position, but I can't quite make it.
Who would've thought an FR's
corner entry could be this fast?
It's awesome how close he's on his tail,
huh? Those are some serious skills.
No matter how ya look at it,
Ninomiya's EK is so much faster!
An Eight-Six is too slow!
It's not that simple.
He wouldn't stay neck-and-neck
with some slow dude, would he?
Unless he really believed in that guy's skill,
he wouldn't be on his tail like that.
The guy in that Eight-Six must be super fast.
--For real?!
--Yeah.
Even in a race with other
students from the school,
I've never seen Ninomiya get
that close to someone before.
It's proof that cool, collected Ninomiya
is starting to get unusually fired up.
This guy's got some serious willpower.
No matter how much pressure
I put on him, he won't budge.
Even someone from the Toudou School
would surely have reacted to this by now.
I don't have to look in the rearview mirror
to know he's staying right close behind me.
I can feel the pressure on my back,
a prickling so sharp that it hurts.
Still, having decided not to
look in the rearview mirror
feels strangely good, lets me concentrate.
Ryosuke had two instructions.
All I have to do is follow them!
Big brother, what's the other one?
The second instruction you gave Fujiwara.
The other is...
...controlled RPMs!
The Eight-Six has up to 11,000 RPMs.
But I have him not using
the top-end 2,000 RPMs
and shifting up when he reaches 9,000.
Are you serious?! Why bother
doing something like that?
Because I don't wish to show our
opponent all the cards in our hand.
As Fujiwara is not yet capable of
executing a more refined strategy...
...this was the only way I could think of
that was both simple
and would produce results.
Limiting our strength against such
a powerful enemy is of course a risk,
but if Fujiwara successfully
evades him for the first race,
we can draw up a simulation
for him to win the competition.
It is an enormous bet, all-or-nothing.
So he's restricting the top-end 2,000 RPMs
and still outracing that
Toudou School downhiller?!
When did he acquire that level of technique?
Fujiwara...
...converts all of his experiences
into self-improvement!
To that end, an exceptional degree
of concentration is required.
I get it. That's why you told
him not to look behind...
So he wouldn't be rocked by
his opponent's pressure tactics
and lose concentration.
This isn't funny... This is bullshit!
I didn't see this turn of events coming.
Choosing to follow in the
first race was a mistake!
It's like I...
I'm actually havin' difficulty with this!
All right, here goes the second race!
I had him show me plenty
during the first race...
...both the Eight-Six's racing
capacity and his driving skill!
It doesn't have enough
speed to keep up with me.
I'm going to finish this in a flash!
He's fast!
He's so fast. This is really bad!
I've got no wiggle room at all...
I'm really at my limit!
This is definitely at a faster
pace than the first race.
Can I really even keep
up with him at this rate?
Fujiwara will expend considerable powers
of concentration when coming from behind.
His senses are such that he will be able to
deal with speeds he has never experienced.
He should be able to keep up.
In the course of being dragged along
by a local racer faster than himself,
he will make his enemy's speed
completely and utterly his own.
If things proceed according to my simulation,
he will overtake the racer from Toudou School.
I'm counting on you, Fujiwara.
Rely on your senses!
What's going on?!
I should have a clear idea of his
max speed from the first race!
But he's definitely racing
above that speed now!
There's no way he should be able to keep up!
So what's he doing there?!
I'm scared!
Up till now, I've never thought that
doing the downhill could be this scary.
If I let off the gas, it'll all be over.
It would be easy...
But the other part of me is saying,
"Don't you dare let off!"
Is that for real?!
All right.
I just heard from the guys at the first hairpin,
and it looks like there's no space
at all between the two cars.
What does that mean?! This is bad.
I can't shake him off!
This is at a much faster pace than the
first race, but he's keeping right up!
If Fujiwara can keep up in this second race,
a certain advantageous element will
present itself as he enters the second half.
Do you know what that is?
Uh, no. I don't have a clue.
And you, Keisuke?
I get it, for the most part.
It's the difference in drive systems, right?
With the FR, the rear tires do
the job of accelerating the car...
But in the FF's case, in corner entries
and also when it accelerates,
only the front tires get worked.
A downhill attack places load on
front tires that are already taxed.
The tires of the front-wheel drive
EK-9 will start feeling the strain first.
Dammit!
Unbelievable! I thought I could
settle this in the first race
and pushed my car too hard
along unreasonable angles!
That was an incredible mistake.
It's put excess strain on the tires.
The RPM limitation was a confusion tactic.
A driver of that caliber would be able
to accurately grasp the capabilities
of the car driving ahead of him--
in other words,
determine he could overtake it
and plan a short, decisive battle.
So you wanted to put added
wear on his tires and brakes?
That's incredible, bro.
To think that those two pieces of
advice had such deep thought to them...
The important part is yet to come.
The Eight-Six's tires can't
hold out that long either.
It's unknown whether he can make use of
the slight chance he has been given.
It's not just my imagination.
His corner entry has suddenly gotten sloppier.
His tires?
The tires are causing heat shear...
but mine still have strength left in them!
I can tear past this fast EK and end the race!
If it were you, where would you start looking
for the point to strike in this situation?
On any mountain pass, the more you
run it, the more there will be points
where the gear ratio simply will not match.
For example, a point where,
as you accelerate toward a corner,
you waver between shifting up or not.
I get that much, but what if your
tachometer's in the red zone,
but you don't have enough room
to shift gears and accelerate?
In cases like that, you do nothing
and just grin and bear it, right?
That sure is terrible.
It's like your hands are tied,
unable to speed up or slow down, huh?
Oh! So that's it!
I've got it!
The Eight-Six's engine has
more RPMs than the EK9's!
That engine's got some
kind of ace up its sleeve.
Advising him to rein in
the top-end 2,000 RPMs
and not showing them to the opponent...
That was the real objective!
What?!
He passed me!
Braking is my specialty, but...
...it let him pass me!
Daiki...
I'm sorry. He beat me.
What the hell's going on?! I don't believe it!
You, a local, lost?
Well done, Fujiwara. You really did a good job.
I'm glad. I got so worked up that
I'm dripping with cold sweat...
Ryosuke almost never makes that sort of face.
I was able to follow through
with what Ryosuke had hoped.
And I'm glad. I really am.
Please do your best, Keisuke.
Of course I will. I'm going on the
attack, right from the first race.
All right, now beginning the hill climb!
Hey sanjou, new generation
Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou
Itsu made wasureta furi o shiteiru no?
(Chigiresou na heart no tension) Mune no uzuki
Sono hitomi no oku, osaekirenai mono
(Sou matowaritsuku kono image) yoru o niramu
Sou dare no kokoro ni te o
nobashite fureru subemo
shiranakatta futari, mou koko kara
(Hey sanjou new generation,
Hora, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Nemutta yume o tatakiokoshite
(Kirisaku you na skill)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
Jidai o furuwasete risky tune
Blast my desire
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
break what you wanna break)