"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
He's making it obvious that he's just cruising. He's not pushing it to the limit.
Even so, he's still fast, and
maintaining a high speed pace.
Nice execution.
I didn't expect him to be able
to pull off such an elegant move.
I didn't realize he was so
skillful until I drove behind him.
That aside, his car seems so fun to drive.
It's quite shocking to see a driver who can compete at this high of a level.
Has my NSX ever looked
like that from the outside?
I'm being sucked in...
I'm being sucked in
by this pleasant rhythm
and getting synchronized.
You can never be certain about
the outcome of a competition.
We were outsmarted in data collection, but it's still within our expectations.
We ran our simulation with a reasonable margin, just in case. We're not stupid.
Maybe not by 15 seconds, but our
car still has an absolute advantage.
After all, unlike circuits, unexpected things happen on mountain passes.
So far, our opponent is doing an excellent job.
We haven't lost yet.
This time, our leader will
turn the situation around.
If he can manage this second run,
there's no reason for us to lose.
Nothing can shake our absolute advantage.
This pleasant feeling will
eventually come to an end.
There'll be a moment when
it will switch to combat mode.
He'll make a full throttle dash
like I did in the first run.
If my NSX and I can't keep up
with it, this battle will be over.
Where? Where are you
going to make your move?
This is beyond our expectations.
An FD's cruising speed can't be that fast.
I can do it. I'm focused.
This is fun.
I've wanted to fight a battle like this.
Act 14  [ End of the Ultimate Hillclimb! ]
I'm not mentally ready yet.
Why did my spurt fail in the first run?
Is he better than Kubo and I had imagined?
I don't get it.
Does my car really
have an advantage?
Or am I the problem?
I have so many doubts that
I have nothing I can rely on.
I don't know how to turn this around.
What should I do, Brother?
You beat your best time again today.
You're noticeably getting better
because your times are consistent.
Your advice is always spot on.
You know exactly what to
do to improve the time.
Circuit racing is really fun.
I like the fact that my time
clearly shows how I've improved.
You can't find a situation where
you can go flat out elsewhere.
Right.
But you have the right aptitude.
Your rate of improvement is incredibly fast.
I think you have talent, Gou.
What was it?
What did my brother say right
before the start of the race?
You're fortunate.
As a man who loves cars and mountain passes, you can't be happier than this.
Do your very best.
Use everything you've learned.
And enjoy yourself.
Hey, Mako
doesn't Shinji remind you of Takumi?
He does, he does.
The moment I saw you, I felt that.
You just seem to have a similar
atmosphere, especially the pure side.
Who's Takumi?
Project D's Fujiwara Takumi.
You'll be able to see
his driving from here.
Do you know Project D's Fujiwara Takumi?
More or less.
We fought a battle against him, and lost.
A battle?
I'm beginning to understand.
If he's better than me, it's pointless
to try and figure out what to do.
As a driver who pursues
speed and technique
if I can see something unprecedented, it should be a thrilling opportunity.
Make your move.
But remember, I'm persistent.
We were partners back then, and we were
confident that we would never lose in our area.
They fought a battle against Fujiwara Takumi?
Takumi had something
superior, even back then.
Even if you lose, you feel refreshed.
He has a pleasant aura. He's got a soothing smile once he gets out of his car, too.
Is that so? Is it cool to
be able to drive a car well?
That's a definite yes.
When it comes to a guy
I don't think his looks matter.
Any guy who's the best in his field
is always popular no
matter what he looks like.
Do you think so too, Mako?
Huh?
Not again. She's pretty
cunning behind the scenes.
Mako is head over heels for fast drivers.
She had a secret crush
on a guy like that before.
Hey, don't get carried
away too much, or I'll kill you.
But it was true.
She did?
(Hey, you're blushing)
Her joke aside, have you ever seen a race in the circuit before, Shinji?
A handful of chosen drivers, who race
in front of crowds, are admired heroes.
Admired heroes?
The four drivers who are competing in this stage today are truly special to us.
They're even more awesome than the
professional drivers who race in the circuit.
The idea of enjoying driving
varies according to the driver's skills.
In my Zero theory, enjoyment is
only attained by high level drivers.
Those who regard adrenaline pumping risky
situations as enjoyment are still low level drivers.
You can relax your mind under pressure and tension
only when you have the skills to control various factors.
Don't you think that such a relaxed
mental state is synonymous with enjoyment?
Conversely, if your mind is not relaxed, your brain can't function at its best.
I think, to a lesser extent, it's similar to a top
athlete's ability to reach a special mental state.
I don't know what to say.
Ikeda, you're a nice guy, but your problem is your over philosophical character.
I can almost smell the incense,
probably because you're a monk.
Well, excuse me for
smelling like incense.
Your Zero theory is very well constructed
but what I wanted to tell
Gou was a little different.
They just passed hairpin 3.
The gap is negligible.
I wanted to remind him of...
I have a hunch of where
you're going to make your spurt.
As a local driver, I know too much about this course, which makes me blind to simple things.
It's so simple.
eagerness to defeat the
opponent right before his eyes
and also a strong fighting spirit
backed by the confidence of not losing.
Call me childish, but that's the
basics of street racing, isn't it?
You think adrenaline is bad, but I disagree.
It's fundamentally different from
risky maneuvers by amateurs.
Because they possess such high skills
they were done with course strategy and vehicle tuning even before the race began.
After it begins, they just
have to be eager to win.
Today, the higher the
blood adrenaline level the better.
"Blood adrenaline level."
You sound like a physician.
I can almost smell the antiseptic.
Still, it's too risky.
I don't like it.
It can't be helped.
That's what a mountain pass is all about, and that's how you enjoy it.
There!
Amazing.
What happened?
Gou looked different.
He was never like that before.
His red car looked excited.
That's never happened before.
Are you crying, Mako?
I don't know why,
but I'm so moved.
It felt like something traveled through the air.
Both drivers are amazing.
What's this feeling?
Am I envious?
Can I impress Mako so much
that she has to shed tears?
I want to drive like that.
This must be it. It's the point where I made my move in the first run.
It's the simplest and easiest answer.
I'm going to use all the
strength I've been saving.
Let's begin our battle, Hojo Gou!
I knew it.
I feel very much like,
"Do your best and leave the rest."
I've done everything I could,
so drive as you see fit.
You outgrew me a long time ago.
From here, your strength
will be put to the test.
Go for it, Keisuke.
Incredible.
Is that the sound of the car
slicing through the air?!
I've never heard it on a mountain pass before, but the sheer speed gave me chills.
That FD is wicked. It's sick.
I've got the intermediate time
from section 4. Have a look.
This is bad. It's too fast.
They're using their cars'
potential beyond the preset limits.
We shouldn't maintain this pace in a course without any escape zone.
Hojo, you only have one life.
When it comes to a street fight, Project D is a notch above us because they have more experience.
Our strategy was to race
without reaching that level.
If we could fight this battle as a
motor sport, we would be superior.
Don't get overeager.
Our opponent is struggling just as much.
He can't maintain such a pace for long.
This is fun.
It's not about logic.
You can't just allow your
opponent to pull away.
If I see a car trying to
outrun me, I must chase it.
That's only natural.
It makes my blood boil.
They're incredible.
They give me the chills.
It's like a fist fight.
Their exit lines at full throttle are closer to the outer edge by a few centimeters compared to their previous run.
If they continue fighting like that,
they could lose control at any time.
Their concentration won't last forever.
I hope this won't end in tragedy.
But for some reason, I'm a little envious.
Same here.
I'm deeply impressed.
They look awesome, don't they?
There's no doubt I share
the same DNA as theirs.
It's the stubbornness and pride of
simply hating to lose in a sprint race.
Without it, we wouldn't be
racing in the first place.
I want to race so bad.
I want to jump into
that high tension race.
The view is different from usual.
I'm going at an extraordinary pace.
I can't stop. How can
I quit having this much fun?
He's fast.
Not only is my car under steering,
but it's over steering as well?!
I've never worn the front tires
so much in a hill climb before.
He must have the same problem.
Dammit!
Warming up already?
The hill climb hasn't ended yet.
If they can't settle the match in this second run, there will be a third.
Don't be in such a hurry, just relax.
Right, but I don't think
there will be a third run.
It will be over in this second run.
Fujiwara, your prediction sounds
convincing, but why do you think so?
Keisuke's in excellent condition.
I can feel it because
we practice together.
I always thought he was great, but he's extraordinary this weekend.
We're not pros, so our driving precision
varies by our physical condition at the time.
He raised his condition to the highest at this critical moment. That's impressive.
You're observant as usual.
I think our opponent
is an impressive driver.
But Keisuke is better at the current moment.
I'm glad he's not my opponent.
He gives off a dangerous aura.
I can gain on him a bit if I can go
flat out for 3 seconds or longer.
I have to shed every tenth of a second I can in order to maintain the gap.
There's a flat out segment of
4 seconds after that curve.
I must take every opportunity one by one.
Is my entry speed too fast?
No, I've gotta go for it.
Swing the tail a bit,
and use four wheel drift.
Step on it. I can't even
lose a tenth of a second.
I have to keep on pushing, or I'll fall behind.
I have to push it.
Mako, Sayuki, I have to go.
Go? Where?
The best part of the
show is about to begin.
Why don't we watch the
down hill race from here together?
No, I...
I must go.
What's wrong with him?
Don't know.
We won!
It's awesome, just awesome.
Just like Takahashi Keisuke.
He's in a class by himself!
Now Takumi, you should win, too!
They've done so well that
the outcome is meaningless.
The stopwatch doesn't lie.
The car I built must have been possessed by something. It's like a miracle.
I've been in the biz for a long time,
but this is some kind of culture shock.
Humans are incredible.
Mako, please watch me from here.
I might defeat Fujiwara Takumi.
What is that supposed to mean?
Could Shinji be?
No way!
Fujiwara Takumi
vs
Inui Shinji
The final battle has begun...!
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.