Hey, the goal is all on the satnav.
Space out and go on, no problem.
100% safety, 0% risky?
Don't stress over minor things,
just toss that out the window.
Who decides what's right?
Don't bother about stuff like that.
You just have to stay focused on
All the things you love, and beyond the raging storm.
(So now it goes above and beyond)
To infinity!
Outsoar the Rainbow.
Don't just stand and watch.
Amp up your senses and fly high.
Let go and fly free even farther.
(Ain't no satisfied, so never stop to fly)
Infinity.
(You can reach the goal on your own)
Initial D
Crawling desperately several thousand times.
Only they are the ones that deserve to look back and talk.
History will prove that someday.
Who could have imagined that Takumi's
very last opponent would be an Eight-Six?
Yeah.
One is the two-door and the other is
the three-door, but both are Truenos.
On top of that
don't you think that the mood is different from
the battle against Akiyama's Levin a while ago?
I feel the same way.
I feel like something unexpected will happen.
Look, I've got goosebumps.
Now I'm getting chills.
Are goosebumps contagious?
Why?
I fell behind a little through a
series of a few tight corners.
Both are Eight-Sixes, so why?
I can't keep up with him in the corners.
I've never had this happen before.
Act 2  [ Strongest Opponent ]
So, Shinji is really Takumi's opponent.
This is truly amazing.
The quiet types tend
to have an extreme side.
Oh yeah, the same as Takumi.
Both cars are Eight-Sixes,
and the drivers are the same type.
I can't even imagine how the battle will end.
Think of him as your strongest opponent ever.
Keep up with him, even if you
have to use the tires to the fullest.
He's tough.
I understand. I'll do my best.
I'm doing my best
but I can't catch him.
I'm falling behind.
Did you see that?
Yeah.
Fujiwara's Eight-Six seems faster on
the straightaway because he's tailgating.
It's got a special engine, and Ryosuke must have improved the car quite a bit over the past year.
On the other hand, the leading Eight-Six's
driving style seems boring, and lacks impact.
Smoothness seems to be the only advantage of that driving style.
If he's the type of driver who was chosen by the practical Kubo for this critical situation
the driver must be the type of
opponent Project D hates most.
There's a meaning behind
the letter "D" in Project D.
I couldn't have even started this
without Keisuke and Fujiwara Takumi.
This battle is not just about winning or losing.
Fight the best you can, Fujiwara.
You've found the most ideal and toughest opponent
who can help you move on to the next level.
Do you want me to explain, Seiji?
The reason why I said Project D
would hate that Trueno most.
Yeah.
When we drive the mountain passes in Lan Evos,
we basically think of WRC drivers as the ideal.
You make a relatively large yaw motion at
the entrance of a corner, and turn by drifting.
Because of the nature of rally racing,
such a style is reasonable, and safer, too.
You mean that steering is only a trigger,
and you turn by using the accelerator.
Isn't that safer?
But having a safety margin means
losing something elsewhere.
Closed-circuit drivers don't drive like that.
They'll let the tires grip by using the full
potential of the tires, because you can go faster.
But because you can't see what's ahead in a
mountain pass, I believe the rally style is better.
Those who are fast on mountain
passes all drive like that.
Fujiwara is no exception.
In fact, he likes to swing his car around.
But Sidewinder's Eight-Six is different.
Wait a sec, Kyoichi!
Your explanation is getting complicated.
He can't understand it, huh?
This is just my hypothesis, but
If there was a driver who could drive the mountain pass with lots of blind corners as if it was a closed circuit
If there was a driver who knows the course
so thoroughly, beyond anyone's imagination
Fujiwara Takumi's drifting style made
him the fastest in northern Kanto
but he won't be able to beat the boring
gripping style with his drifting style.
Do you understand?
There's a stylistic issue here.
Is that so? Dammit!
That said, I didn't understand any of it.
He's not particularly fast
during the entry or the exit.
He's fast during the entire sequence.
Just a little
It's only a little, but I'm
falling behind in the corners.
In most corners of a mountain pass, you can't
see the entire curve from the entrance to the exit.
No matter how experienced they are, drivers
instinctively maintain some sort of safety margin.
This issue is unrelated
to the level of technique.
But Shinji doesn't have that
kind of hesitation at all.
I feel like he can see the exit of the corner,
which is invisible to the rest of us.
Why is that?
He used to
sit in the passenger seat next to me,
and watch the corners from the other side.
That might be why.
He always seemed curious
about the roadside scenery.
Every day for twelve years
The part you can't see
at night is visible in daylight.
You can pick up many pieces of information when you're free from the steering wheel in the passenger seat.
In each corner, there's a slight elevation change from the entrance to the exit, and the change of radius.
Also any minor damage in the asphalt, the flow
of rain water, as well as loose gravel can be seen.
The accurate shape of the gutters is hidden
by summer weeds during this season
but he can see them because
they can be seen in the winter.
I see.
He learned the course from the opposite side.
Every corner can be visualized from its exit first.
He learned every corner
from the opposite side?!
Even if I can catch up with him
in the longer straightaways
this course has no straightaway, but instead,
it has lots of tight corners near the goal.
I won't be able to keep up with him there.
What should I do?
No good.
Not good at all.
It's a strange sight, isn't it?
The finale of this big event turned out to be an
unexpected battle between two Eight-Sixes.
What's your take, Daiki?
Fujiwara is better at braking.
He can delay his braking point.
The way he uses heel-and-toe engine braking to slow down his car is at a professional level.
On the other hand, the leading Eight-Six
driver's corner entry control is loose
and he's using heel-and-toe
just for the hell of it.
But his brake release point was
so perfect that it gave me chills.
He must know this course very well.
Just like you, the braking artist, Daiki.
Your observation is unique.
Even through my eyes, Fujiwara's racing
technique seems to have improved.
Even so, he didn't seem
to have any margin.
No margin?
That means the pace is fast.
Even if they drive at the same pace,
Fujiwara has a smaller margin
because he's fighting to the fullest.
On the other hand, his opponent's
driving is gentle and smooth.
That will put less stress
on the tires and the car.
It's amazing that he doesn't
have to swing his rear end.
His style is totally
different from Todo School's.
This won't go well for Project D.
At this rate, it will be
Fujiwara's tires that wear out first.
His braking from a straightaway is fairly loose.
That's almost like how I was last year.
Then why?
I'm struggling to keep up
after a series of corners.
What's making the difference?
The potential of the two Eight-Sixes?
It can't be.
This car's maintenance is handled by Ryosuke
and Matsumoto, the best team out there.
That means
I'm the one losing here.
If I fall behind in the next hair-pin curve, things will get even worse.
What, why?
I don't believe this.
What is he thinking?!
I want to see them
There were wings on the back of your car.
I want to see the wings again.
Those breathtakingly cool wings.
I won't be able to see them from out in front.
Show them to me again.
Did you see that, Kobayakawa?
Yeah, he gave way.
That's one hell of a crazy
move that you never see.
Maybe he doesn't understand
the rules of this battle.
What the hell?!
He lit the blinkers and fell behind?!
Are you serious?
I heard it from a record keeper
who happened to be nearby.
I don't know what's going on.
My bad feeling turned out to be true.
He didn't understand
why we chose the lead.
Or perhaps, he doesn't know
the rules of this battle at all?
I'm very sorry.
Once the positions are switched, it's the
end unless he overtakes somewhere.
Oh no, he'll lose.
If I lose two winnable battles,
I can't stay in this business.
I love it.
This is so awesome.
Hojo
Sidewinder's Eight-Six driver gave way.
What the hell?!
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
Beats me.
I don't get it.
What the hell is that kid thinking?!
He told me he wanted to become a hero.
I was moved while I was
watching you drive, Hojo.
I want to be a hero.
I want to race. Let me do it.
I like your expression. Go for it.
There's no one else.
Only you can stop
Project D's consecutive victories.
Oh, right.
You don't need to hear stuff like that.
Just express yourself as you like.
Drive freely and have fun.
Tonight's stage is so thrilling.
You're the star, Shinji.
Okay.
He can't be called a hero if he loses,
so he understands the rules.
No doubt. He's willing to win.
In other words, this reckless act is out of
his confidence that he can retake the lead.
And against the fastest driver in northern Kanto, no one
has ever dissed that undefeated downhiller so badly.
All hell just broke loose, and
no one knows what'll happen.
Project D must be panicking, too.
Ryosuke and Iwe're all
just spectators from here on.
What's going on?
This is a battle, right?
What are you thinking?
Brother?
What would you do, Keisuke?
I don't know. I'd be panicked.
No one has ever given
way to me during a battle.
It's humiliating
and one's motivation would hit rock bottom.
It'd take a while to switch your mindset.
Probably so.
This is unexpected.
But it's not too bad.
If this battle had gone as I simulated,
our chances of victory were very slim.
We needed to stir things
up to change the mood.
We can't control anything, but this is
suitable for Project D's final battle.
The stars are out there, so there's
no need for a mediocre scenario.
The greatest drama is about to unfold.
Iketani, Kenji, what's going to happen?
How would I know?
Right.
All we can do is believe in Takumi.
He's our downhill ace.
Bring it back, hey, rock'n roll!
Life goes on, I was content with a little bit of hope.
Someone decided my future so I only had to wait.
(Just got to get you back and bring it back on)
How small I was, bust it up!
(Here we go, 1, 2)
Move it up and break it!
I've gotta run for my dream now.
(Bring back, yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll!)
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
It's a stage on the edge.
(Oh, Yeah)
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
Not even a millimeter of hesitation.
(Check it out, come on!)
Truth is, there aren't many things worth holding on to.
(Give it up yo! Give it up yo!)
Act a bit tough and gamble away all I've got.
Play the game!
Let's gamble, hey jumbo.
Now shake your bum and do the rumble.
Three sharp lines and maxed out tension.
Here comes the M.O.V.E trio while everyone's asleep.
Even if they call us annoying for all the noise
I like to move it, move it.
I'll make you move into it.
Let's play the sensual noise of the domestic cars.
Show a dazzling desire.
Warp all the way from the start to the goal.
Let's overtake at Mach 55, to your next stage.