Hey, the goal is all on the satnav.
Space out and go on, no problem.
100% safety, 0% risky?
Don't stress over minor things,
just toss that out the window.
Who decides what's right?
Don't bother about stuff like that.
You just have to stay focused on
All the things you love, and beyond the raging storm.
(So now it goes above and beyond)
To infinity!
Outsoar the Rainbow.
Don't just stand and watch.
Amp up your senses and fly high.
Let go and fly free even farther.
(Ain't no satisfied, so never stop to fly)
Infinity.
(You can reach the goal on your own)
Initial D
Crawling desperately several thousand times.
Only they are the ones that deserve to look back and talk.
History will prove that someday.
What, why?
I love it.
This is so awesome.
Hojo
He told me he wanted to become a hero.
He can't be called a hero if he loses,
so he understands the rules.
No doubt. He's willing to win.
In other words, this reckless act comes from the confidence that he can retake the lead.
And against the fastest driver in northern Kanto
No one has ever dissed that
undefeated downhiller this badly.
All hell just broke loose, and
no one knows what'll happen.
What's going on?
This is a battle, right?
What're you thinking?
We can't control anything, but this is
suitable for Project D's final battle.
The stars are out there, so there's
no need for a mediocre scenario.
The greatest drama is about to unfold.
Act 3  [ Scent Of Danger ]
So I just have to maintain my lead
like this.
Shit!
I can't concentrate at all.
But you know
this is a matter of winning or losing, so we should take advantage of any chance we're given, right?
Fujiwara may not like this
but we can win at this rate.
Fumihiro
you don't get it, do you?
Letting your opponent pass obviously
means you intend to overtake him.
Overtake?!
That's impossible.
The later section of the course narrows.
How can he overtake him?
A top class battle is fought very closely.
Fujiwara is our downhill ace.
Whether in northern Kanto or Kanagawa,
he's never lost when it comes to a dead heat.
You may be right
but this isn't about logic.
I've had some rough times.
But I think something
unexpected will happen.
I share Keisuke's impression.
I don't think Fujiwara can maintain his lead.
It's an unlikely scenario.
Hey, you too, Ryosuke?
You should let go of your
common conceptions, Fumihiro.
This is why I said Fujiwara's opponent
was a worthy driver for our final battle.
I never expected to find this kind of talent.
I've gotta keep running away.
The real match will happen in the
technical section just before the goal.
I have to preserve my tires until then.
Compared to a hill-climber,
the Eight-Six is underpowered
yet both unexpectedly manage to
pick up speed on the straightaway.
It's probably because the cornering speed is fast.
The Eight-Six is so mysterious.
This battle might look
close to ordinary spectators
because the speeds are high.
Probably so.
But to our eyes,
they haven't gotten serious yet.
It's like the calm before the storm.
You're right.
But there's a strange awkwardness.
I wonder why I feel so
nervous watching this race
I understand what you mean.
The pursuing Eight-Six
is going to do something.
No, something abnormal
may have begun already.
There's a strong sense of danger in the air.
This battle is going to be rough.
I can't see them.
I can't see the wings today.
Why?
I'm a little disappointed.
If I can't see them,
it's pointless to stay behind you.
It's hard to drive behind Shinji
because people lose their rhythm.
It's probably because of his unusually fast entry into the corners and his own unique rhythm.
It tends to make skilled drivers
lose their rhythm even more.
They make small mistakes
as if they're hypnotized.
Those who've driven behind
him say the same thing.
Some of them almost spun out
while trying too hard to keep up.
That's why he should be driving in the lead.
He can only use half of his
strength if he drives behind.
Don't get so riled up, Kubo.
It's clear that he intentionally switched positions.
He must have felt something in Fujiwara Takumi, since he drives the same Eight-Six type.
That's a good sign.
This is the first time Shinji has taken
an interest in someone else's driving.
Normally, he's only
interested in his own driving.
If this is just to win tonight's battle,
he doesn't have to see or learn anything.
But in order for Shinji to break
out of his mold and grow further
it's probably better for him to
face confusion and struggle.
While his inexperience is his
strength, it's also his weakness.
The trigger, which will help Shinji break out of
his mold, is the other genius driver from Gunma.
I'm so confused.
Why did Shinji give up his position?
The local Sidewinder team would normally stick with
the usual theory of choosing the lead position
and trying to pull away.
That'd be a more aggressive strategy.
You take the initiative to
win a battle quickly, but
I don't understand,
no matter how I look at this.
Besides, how could someone so young
represent Sidewinder, the toughest
team in the Kanagawa prefecture?
I don't know.
But now that you mention it, look at Takumi.
Even he was just a high school kid when he raced against us in Usui's mountain pass a year ago.
Yeah, that's true.
It turns out there's more than one miracle
boy with incredible potential out there.
It's not a fantasy anymore.
Here they come!
Impossible
He passed
That Eight-Six sedan is nuts.
This isn't a normal passing zone.
I can't believe this.
The super fast Fujiwara Takumi, who has defeated Kanagawa's best drivers one after another
was overtaken?!
He was passed.
The Eight-Six from Gunma?!
T-T-T-Takumi was overtaken?
That's impossible.
How could that be possible?!
What now?
Is there another overtaking point left?
This is unreal.
What do you think, Mako?
I think it's unreal, too. I really do.
The entry to this hairpin is twisted like
an S-curve, so there's only one line.
No one would think of going
side by side in a place like this.
But he dove into the corner so casually.
Plus, his opponent is Takumi.
This is just speculation,
but do you want to hear it?
Sure.
Maybe Shinji just wanted to show
you his overtaking maneuver.
Whatever the line or layout is,
he could have passed anywhere.
That can't be.
He bumped into my car.
It's unexpected, but that's
the kind of driver he is, huh?
If that's what you want
It went just as you predicted, Hojo.
It's almost scary.
He passed in the hairpin
at the viewing platform
disregarding any theory whatsoever.
In a place like that?!
Yes. When he's focused,
he enters his own world.
Then he can be nasty, which is the
polar opposite of his usual self.
He almost has no fear
of damaging his car's body.
That fact alone makes him very unusual
because street racers hate
to damage their car's body.
He doesn't really care about keeping the
car free from scratches while he's driving.
He learned to drive in a
beat up car with lots of damage.
He doesn't care about brushing the
body against a tree or the guardrail.
Even so, for some reason,
it's always just a minor scuff.
He's never caused any
serious damage to the car.
It's like a master of martial arts dodging an opponent's attack by the slightest margin.
I had the body damage repaired and painted.
That was part of my strategy.
If I hadn't, our opponent would
have become more cautious.
That was an unexpected passing point.
No one can understand Shinji's natural talent.
But his move seems too early.
I don't think this will end without a hitch.
"Fearless" is the word that fits him best.
But, Shinji, Fujiwara Takumi is a far more terrifying
opponent than you can imagine.
The hairpin at the viewing platform?
You've gotta be kidding.
In a place like that?!
Unthinkable. He's got guts,
making a move in a place like that.
He keeps humiliating our downhill ace.
Dammit!
I guess the person who's
actually racing must be shocked.
I hope Fujiwara doesn't lose his motivation.
He won't, not for a trivial matter like this.
He's driving for more than his own sake.
Yes, those rivals he defeated
in northern Kanto are watching.
He's driving with a strong tailwind at his back.
There's no way he'd lose motivation.
The battle begins now!
It's awkward to stay in the same position.
Think of it as handing
over the position to get even.
Yeah. That's right.
Yeah.
He has a point.
To Fujiwara, this won't be as
dramatic an incident as the others think.
I can see the situation.
He would've been shocked quite a bit if
he was trying to pull away at top speed.
But even at high speed, he should have
been cruising in order to preserve his tires.
I can't be sure whether he was caught off
guard by the unexpected attack or not, but
he probably didn't block that reckless move even
though he could, and intentionally gave up the position.
That scenario sounds more plausible.
Not bad.
He tends to break new ground
when he gets into trouble.
Fujiwara Takumi
he's the type of genius who keeps
evolving, becoming faster and faster.
This is good.
Now that he has the lead position back,
I have nothing to worry about.
I don't want to sound like an idiot by
stating the obvious aloud, so I won't, but
I think this battle will end smoothly.
Fujiwara Takumi is tough.
But the more confidence in their speed the driver has,
the more dangerous it is to get behind Shinji.
No one can drive like Shinji.
If you try, you'll end up crashing.
Just like you'd expect from a local driver.
We drove Usui every day, so we know
what it's like to feel every bit of the course.
It's the type of feeling you can only gain by constantly driving hard, even in the rain or against the wind.
He was able to make such a bold pass because he knows this course so well that he could almost drive blindfolded.
He's at a serious disadvantage.
Takumi is racing on this
course for the first time, right?
What?
He isn't falling behind, but is
managing to keep up with my speed.
He's a little faster than before.
Sayuki, do you remember the battle
against Takumi on Usui's mountain pass?
How can I forget?
Takumi drove Usui for the first time and
I think it was the essence
of his expeditionary battles.
We were the local specialists, but he
stayed right on our tail and synced with us.
It was like he instantly figured out and
copied your cornering lines and entry speed.
His concentration was extraordinary.
Maybe he can do the same thing here.
No matter how well Shinji knows this course,
or how fast he can drive by ignoring theory
if Takumi can humbly accept that fact
I think he can awaken the
same senses from that time.
I think that's what his essence is, even after growing up to become an undefeated downhiller now.
He perfectly copied my maneuver on C-121,
which is the toughest spot on Usui's mountain pass.
I've never forgotten that shock.
You're incredible indeed. You're very fast.
But you have the same Eight-Six as I do.
Therefore
there's no way I can't clear a
corner at the same speed as you.
The next curve is the one that I think
is the toughest on the entire course.
The exit is tighter than the entrance.
Nobody has ever kept up
with me at the same speed.
Wow, what's with him?
No way. That was the first time
someone has pulled that off.
Looks tough, but I can make it.
What?
Why isn't he falling back?
I'm doing my best, but he isn't falling back.
Oh man.
I just heard a report from the third hairpin.
As you know, it's a really
tough spot on this course.
It's not difficult to climb there
but when you go down, it gets more and more dangerous as you try to tackle it harder.
The guardrail there is incredibly damaged.
Shinji is in a class by himself when
it comes to that mid-speed hairpin.
When other drivers enter the corner at the same speed, they slide out at the exit
and crash into the guardrail
as if they were pulled into it.
Fujiwara Takumi stayed right behind him
and cleared the corner with no difficulty.
This must have had a huge impact on Shinji.
Based on the section time,
Shinji is going at full speed.
This is a good sign.
Huh?
A genius instantly surpassed the world Shinji's
built for himself over the past thirteen years.
Fujiwara Takumi is persistent.
Excuse me for saying this
but you've changed in a good way, Hojo.
You seemed so obsessed with victory
until yesterday, but you're different now.
It looks like you have a broader perspective.
Not just victory, but you're also
thinking about developing Shinji's skills.
Maybe so.
I lost my battle.
That must be when I lost my obsession.
It'd be a waste if you end this battle
with only winning or losing in mind.
Everyone who has participated in this event
could be considered part of Project D.
Shinji is fortunate that he
can be on the ultimate stage.
I don't know whether he
can win this battle or not.
I'm rather surprised that he showed up
at the starting line, instead of running away.
From how he looked this morning,
I thought he'd run away right before the start.
He must be scared, because he's wimpy
and timid when he's not at the wheel.
Once he starts racing,
he can't depend on anyone
and can't make any excuses.
Drivers are alone.
This guy's fast.
I'm no good after all, Mom.
He's desperately fighting his
weakness, but he will grow up.
I don't like this anymore.
I want to quit and drive off.
No, Shinji isn't weak.
He's put in a lot of time.
He has unique senses and technique.
Even if he feels weak and loses
confidence for a short period of time
a driver with that kind of speed can't be weak.
In the end, a fighter can only rely on
the backbone he's built for himself.
He has it, which makes him strong.
I'm scared, Mom.
Bring it back, hey, rock'n roll!
Life goes on, I was content with a little bit of hope.
Someone decided my future so I only had to wait.
(Just got to get you back and bring it back on)
How small I was, bust it up!
(Here we go, 1, 2)
Move it up and break it!
I've gotta run for my dream now.
(Bring back, yo, it's the right time, hey boy, rock'n roll!)
Gamble, you gotta chance to make a Rumble!
It's a stage on the edge.
(Oh, Yeah)
Gamble, you gotta dive into a scramble!
Not even a millimeter of hesitation.
(Check it out, come on!)
Truth is, there aren't many things worth holding on to.
(Give it up yo! Give it up yo!)
Act a bit tough and gamble away all I've got.
Play the game!
Let's gamble, hey jumbo.
Now shake your bum and do the rumble.
Three sharp lines and maxed out tension.
Here comes the M.O.V.E trio while everyone's asleep.
Even if they call us annoying for all the noise
I like to move it, move it.
I'll make you move into it.
Let's play the sensual noise of the domestic cars.
Show a dazzling desire.
Warp all the way from the start to the goal.
Let's overtake at Mach 55, to your next stage.