"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Ryosuke
What's going on?
The Grim Reaper is acting strange,
showing true hostile intent.
The other guy is well aware of it,
but he isn't even trying to escape.
This is no ordinary battle.
It looks like I ran into
an extraordinary situation.
Just like you, Ryosuke.
Your earlier hesitation is gone.
You've got incredible adaptability.
You're a much better
driver than I expected.
Are you nearby, Kaori, watching us?
I dedicate this battle to you.
Even if I die here tonight, I won't regret it.
I'm not afraid of anything.
No one can escape the Grim Reaper.
That car is
outrageously fast.
Is he going to do it?
For real?
Act 10  [ Full Stop ]
According to Takumi, that white FC doesn't
sound like Takahashi Ryosuke's car.
So, it's just a Takahashi Ryosuke fan?
I only heard it from the guy
who caught a glimpse of it.
Come to think of it,
he said the car had a wing.
Then it's someone else's.
Takahashi Ryosuke's FC has the stock one.
You're right.
It must be someone else, then.
Even though he's retired,
he still has hardcore fans.
As expected of Takahashi Ryosuke,
Akagi's White Comet.
I'm so envious.
I wish I could be like him.
That's impossible in terms
of looks, brains, and money.
You're finished, Ryosuke.
Disappear.
No, don't do it!
That's insane!
Taking advantage of the ATTESA E-TS 4WD system,
he pushed from the side while accelerating.
No one stands a chance
against that heavy body.
The Rotary Meister, who used to be known
as the best of the northern Kanto area
will perish in the mountain passes of Hakone.
Take him, Kaori.
What the hell?!
Damn, he climbed up the
slope as if it was a bank.
Impossible.
I can't believe what I just saw.
If he forced the car
to stay on the road
it would have hit the curb and
bounced back uncontrollably.
He aimed straight for the slope,
instead of trying to recover.
It was a split second decision. It would
have been too late if he tried to think about it.
He's even more of a natural than
that downhiller, Fujiwara Takumi.
You have strong luck,
but how long will it last?
Is that all you've got, Senpai?
I won't run or hide.
I won't lose that easily
so throw everything you've
got at me, Hojo Rin.
What's wrong, Takumi?
You spaced out again.
Oh, I'm concerned about that phone call.
About an impersonator?
Sorry, but can I make a phone call?
Sure, no need to worry about that.
Thanks. I'll be back in a bit.
Hello?
Oh, Fujiwara, what's up
at this time of night?
Oh, about that...
Sounds like it's Ryosuke's car.
No, you don't have to worry.
We don't know where he is, or what he's doing.
I'll hand you over to Keisuke.
Hello, Fujiwara? Listen.
You don't have to worry about my brother.
He's not so weak that he
needs you to worry about him.
Don't worry about this, and just focus
on preparations for the final battle.
This isn't the time to be
goofing around with a girl.
Trust my brother, and don't worry so much.
Okay.
Later.
Dammit..
I can't say.
It has nothing to do with you.
But I can't be satisfied until you tell me.
You love someone else, don't you?
Tell me the name of the
guy who took you from me.
Who is he?
Dad
How could you be so selfish?
Are you going to destroy everything?
Everything from my company's
existence to your carefree college life
is owed to Director Hojo.
You know that, don't you?
Change your clothes, Kaori.
We're going to visit him and apologize.
If we apologize sincerely,
the Director should forgive us.
I've talked to Rin, and he had the same idea.
No, I won't go.
Enough is enough!
How much are you going to trouble me?
Please listen to me.
This is for you, too.
You have no other choice.
I don't want to go, Dad.
I don't want to go,
even if I have to die.
Ryosuke
The RB26 is impressive.
It must be making at least 650 HP.
I'll be out accelerated
on a long straightaway.
Sorry, Ryosuke.
This time, there's nowhere to run.
How pathetic.
I can't do anything.
All I can do is watch?!
This time there's no bank to climb.
Beyond the guard rail is a cliff.
He recovered?
The Grim Reaper's fatal
side press didn't work?
What just happened?
Oh, I know.
The speed.
The FC's cornering speed is very fast.
The side press was believed to be
inescapable, but it was completely nullified.
He dodged my attack by releasing
the side G-force to absorb the impact.
Why can't I shoot Ryosuke down?
If you follow the basics of slow in and fast out,
you'll become a victim of the Grim Reaper.
You sacrificed the exit speed
for a high speed approach.
On top of that, he sees his
opponent's moves very well.
He's so strong minded that he
doesn't flinch at dire circumstances.
Instead of resisting, he remains open
to fear and anger, and lets them go by.
That's the ideal Zero mindset
I've been trying to achieve.
He's shown me something I don't have.
You're incredible, Takahashi Ryosuke.
No matter how fast the Grim Reaper's car is,
he's no match for you in a normal race.
Their mindsets are totally different, and the
Grim Reaper looks noticeably impatient.
That's why, with the GT-R still trailing
behind, the situation is even more dire.
I've never met Hojo Gou of Sidewinder, but
Hojo Rin was three years senior to me in college.
I want to save Hojo Rin, because
both of us suffer from the same pain.
That's why I can't run away,
and must face this head on.
I have to do it for my own sake.
The Hojo Rin I knew was sensitive and smart.
He knew everything, but couldn't
accept it, so he shut himself in.
He just needs a chance, and I believe in him.
Words are convenient, but powerless.
Sometimes you can convey a message
through means other than words.
What you said is very complex.
Besides, I don't understand why it has to be now.
Since they're brothers, Sidewinder and the Grim
Reaper might be collaborating behind the scenes.
This could be a trap in order to gain
an advantage in the final Kanagawa battle.
That's not likely, Matsumoto.
How can you be so sure?
Hojo Rin picked this date
for a reason, an obvious one.
Today's the second anniversary of Kaori's death.
It's only been two years.
What I can't stand is that
you've recovered and moved on.
How can you be so cold hearted?
Was it so easy for you to forget?
That's the extent of your feelings for Kaori?
No
You shouldn't let the depth of the scar, depth of sadness,
or the intensity of your despair keep you from moving forward.
No matter how strong the pain is,
it's our duty to move forward.
You're wrong for running away from reality.
Shut up, Ryosuke!
You're the one who's running away!
Both of us are responsible for Kaori's suicide!
Don't forget that, Ryosuke.
I'll never let you forget that!
I haven't forgotten, nor run away.
It has never escaped my mind.
That's why I made my
choice to move forward.
You think she wishes for
us to keep fighting like this?
This will only make her sad!
Why can't you understand this, Hojo?
Please, snap out of it.
If you intend to drive me into despair,
I'll wake you up for her sake.
Crap.
He's checking the brakes
effectiveness far too often.
Is the pedal feeling weird?
Is there something wrong with the GT-R's brakes?
I just wished she were alive and well.
Kaori, you're the best woman I ever
met, no matter what others say.
Even if you're not mine, so long
as you're happy, I'd be alright.
Soft hair, a breathtaking gaze
translucent white skin
slim body, and gentle curves.
To me, you're like a work of art.
But you're not here anymore.
My god, what a nasty side press!
Instead of thrusting out the nose, he put his
car's body against the other to push it out.
This is not a matter of dodging or not.
You can't be serious, Grim Reaper!
You're on the bridge over the valley!
He hit the brakes to pull the nose out!
Both cars will lose control at the same time!
This is furious.
The under steered GT-R hit the curb
while the over steered FC crossed
the line with full counter steering.
No doubt, this is a deadly dogfight.
But I've been witnessing a beautiful exchange
of splendid skills over and over again.
How I pity you, Grim Reaper.
With such skills, why do you have to turn
your precious car into a lethal weapon?
I can't get him even if I attack that hard?
You're foolishly honest,
despite your looks, Ryosuke.
Are you trying to play along with me?
For what? For whom?
Again! Something's wrong.
The braking distance is getting longer.
It's fatal to have a brake problem
on the downhill of this course.
So why is your foot still on
the gas in these circumstances?!
What is your dream, Ryosuke?
To become a good doctor?
Sounds good, and I admire it, but
you can hardly call it a dream.
It's just a practical goal.
I think men should be eager to chase dreams.
Mine?
Girls are different.
I can live with practical goals.
I'm not strong enough to turn away
from reality to pursue my dream.
I think men have the privilege
of being able to chase dreams.
I wish I could keep watching
it with the person I love.
Dream...
What terrible under steering.
The front tires have no grip.
The brakes are even worse than that.
This is unexpected.
I never thought this game would last this long.
This downhill puts more stress
on the brakes than the circuit.
There's one more emergency
escape area beyond the next corner.
If you can't stop, use it, Grim Reaper.
You've done enough!
Now, use it.
You idiot!
The GT-R's pace is strange.
The possible cause is the brakes.
Damn, what should I do?
I'm disappointed in you, Kaori.
Do whatever you want.
This whole thing has displeased
both my father and me.
You'll regret it later.
I hate to say this, but your father's
business will suffer from now on.
Someday, you'll regret
that you didn't choose me.
It didn't have any deep meaning.
I couldn't help saying such a foolish
thing because I was so frustrated.
Kaori, was it me who
drove you into a corner?
It slid outward that much even
though it had an inside line.
It may have lost most
of its braking potential.
All that's left is for the Grim
Reaper to launch a suicide attack.
Run, Takahashi Ryosuke. Shake him off.
I'm afraid the Grim Reaper has lost his mind.
You don't have to continue playing his
game. Get out of his attack range.
Why did you release the accelerator
way before the braking point?!
Why did you slow down here?!
What the?!
What're you doing, Ryosuke?!
You can't stop the heavy body of the R32.
My brakes are completely gone.
Your FC's brakes can't
take the weight of two cars!
Goodbye, Ryosuke.
What are you talking about?
Kaori, where are you now?
Thank you for everything.
Although it was brief, I had fun.
Tell me where you are.
I'll be right there.
I'm glad I met you, Ryosuke.
Goodbye.
It's so hard to maintain control
because the two cars are misaligned.
It's an unrecoverable mistake.
I can't get the maximum braking ability.
It's no good, we aren't slowing down.
I can't stop!
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.