"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Tobidase wicked show, kuuki biribiri saku noise
Shibaite norikonase, abarenbou no party
Zettai hikanai kihaku, the dogfight
Buttoi red zone no himei ni shibiretai
Hakanai senkou, like a ryuusei
Isshun no kagayaki demo kamawanai
Kaimamita kichou na fuukei itsuka kataritai
Sou, ima wa honnou no mama dogfight
Shibiretai yume nara koko ni aru
Kagerou yaburu kaze, backfire
Kinou nado sutetekina,
ima kara rocket dance (Dogfight!)
Sakebenai negai ga itamu nara sugu ni oide
You're big time gambler
Orokasa wa utsukushii kyokusen
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Souon mo everywhere
Yokonaguri, 5G hodo no heavyweight
Giri de soukou, miri no koubou
Za-za-zan!
Rakushou de funde ikeru ze, madamada
"Steep Curve"
"Sadamine"
Hey Nobuhiko, did you hear?
Yeah. They say they're coming...
Project D.
What do you want to do? It's kinda scary, huh?
Why? There's nothing to
be scared about, right?
R-Really?
I'm incredibly curious.
I wanna see just how good
that famous team is.
I'm happy they're even coming
here to our home course.
Right, Kyoko?
'Scuse me.
Are you looking for a cell phone? A silver one?
What is this feeling?
Maybe I've met him...
My darling!
Oh, wait!
Kyoko.
Hey, Kyoko!
Were you even listening? This time
we're going up against Project D!
And I say we have the hillclimb covered.
You're our team's ace, Kyoko.
Okay, understood.
I'll get myself focused and race.
Just leave the hillclimb to me.
You want me to tell you about
their team's hillclimber?
No, that's fine. I can concentrate
better if I don't hear too many details.
But I'm just going to run my race.
"Act 8: Fateful Battle of the FDs"
It's no good.
The race is tomorrow, but I'm just not into it.
I can't get pumped up the way I usually do.
"Steep Curve"
Okay. Got it.
That was our people in
the parking lot down below.
They're finally here, Kyoko.
Something feels strange about the engine...
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Just for today and tomorrow, I have to
concentrate and think only about the race.
I definitely don't want to lose! No matter
what kind of opponent I'm up against.
Looks like they've arrived, huh?
That yellow FD is Project D's
hillclimber ace, Keisuke Takahashi.
He's the guy you'll be riding against tomorrow.
K-Keisuke Takahashi...
What's wrong? You scared?
It couldn't be! He's got an FD, same as you.
The way you race, you can hold
your head high anywhere you go.
Be confident and show 'em how it's done.
Keisuke...
...Takahashi.
I don't know what I should do. I never
thought it would turn out this way...
How could we have met like this?
Very well, we shall now start our practice runs.
Okay, let's begin.
Five runs at 80%.
A word of warning: your usual
tactics will not be applicable here.
Especially for you, Keisuke.
It was to provide you with strict
training that I chose this course.
Give it your all.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Preparations are complete!
All okay here, too.
Those two cars are incredible.
It's a thrill just to look at them.
Hey, quit talkin' like you're a spectator!
Those are the guys we'll be racing tomorrow!
What do you plan to do now, Nobuhiko?
Stay here and watch them till tomorrow.
I already took the day off from work.
A chance like this almost never comes along.
I'll have them give me a
nice, long look at the tactics
they come up with for our home course.
And after that, I'll come up
with a strategy of my own.
Those two Project D drivers
certainly are incredible.
But the really incredible one is
the guy giving out the orders.
But I'm going to find out...
how to hit them where it hurts!
This course is sort of hard to run!
It's really terrible, Fumihiro.
There are all these cracks
and ripples in the asphalt.
And they set off sparks,
like in the old F1 races.
I raised the car more than usual and
tried a couple of different configurations,
but nothing really does the trick.
That's how it looks.
The Eight-Six seems to be having a
hard time with its suspension, too.
More to the point, did you notice, Keisuke?
Notice what?
There was a girl in a black FD when we
came to scout the course before, right?
She was there with the group we'll be racing.
I didn't notice that.
She watched you going out in your FD
with an intensely serious look on her face.
That girl couldn't possibly
be their hillclimber, right?
You wouldn't think it,
but that might be the case.
After all, she's driving an FD.
Anyway, I could care less
who their hillclimber is.
I think my real opponent will be this course.
That's awesome! It's like a fateful encounter!
There's nothing awesome
about it. I just want to run away.
Why? A chance like this
almost never comes along!
Chance?
That's right! You've got the same hobby,
so no matter if you win or lose,
it's still a great chance for
you two to get friendly, right?
It is?
Yes, of course! You definitely
have to do this, Kyoko.
If you show him how good a driver you are,
he's bound to get interested in you, too.
You can't let him get away.
This is your chance!
I stuck around yesterday and kept
a close eye on them till dawn,
and sure enough, these guys are top-class.
Especially that downhill Eight-Six.
He's already beyond street-racer level.
We don't have a downhiller
in his league on our team...
I'll go ahead and challenge him,
but don't get your hopes up.
That's why we're going to have
to pin it all on the hillclimb.
And when it comes to the hillclimb, we have
the incredibly talented Kyoko on our team.
Depending on your approach, it will be
possible for you to pull out in front of him.
That's why I've thought up a strategy.
I'm counting on you, Kyoko.
Just leave it to me. I'm feeling
extremely motivated right now.
What's wrong? It's not working?
I-I was racing, and all of
a sudden it lost power...
With no warning?
N-No, not like that.
It's felt a bit strange since
the day before yesterday.
I thought maybe it was just my imagination.
But the power clearly cut out just now.
I got scared, so I pulled over.
Say, you...
Are you supposed to do the hillclimb today?
I was.
But at this rate--
What a disappointment.
It's like I got the short end of the stick, too.
You have the same FD,
and it looked pretty fast, so I'd
been looking forward to this...
If your car felt even a little off, why didn't
you check it out while it was still daylight?
If you think you can win without giving
your machine the proper maintenance,
I'm shocked.
Racing someone with a half-assed
attitude like that is a waste of time!
I... I...
Kyoko's FD has stopped?
I heard it was pulled over
with the hood popped up.
It broke down?! What do we do, Nobuhiko?
For now, let's just go see.
This is pathetic.
Why couldn't I listen properly
to what my FD was telling me?
Like an idiot, I went up anyway...
and this is how it turns out?
This is terrible. And I was so excited!
From the bottom of my heart,
I wanted to race that man!
Everything's ruined. He completely hates me.
Hey, your car can still run, right?
Quit spacing out and hang a U-turn.
As I thought, a pipe's slipped off.
The intercooler hose
has probably deteriorated.
Can you fix it?
I think I can manage something.
I brought a whole range
of parts for this section.
Okay, do it. On the double!
Can it be fixed?
Probably. He brought the
whole minivan full of parts.
That's just like Keisuke, all right.
Say, Ryosuke.
You said you chose this course to
give Keisuke some "strict training,"
but you meant that seriously
and not as a joke, right?
It was serious. He has mastered
aggressive full-throttle acceleration,
but sometimes that alone lends
itself to too many victories.
He also tends to prefer clean courses,
so this place will be more than a handful.
A fiery fighting spirit matched with
pedal work delicate and cold as ice...
That is Keisuke's current assignment!
She's not here!
That's strange.
The boost is working perfectly. This won't let
you complain about not having any power!
Um, I really don't know what to say...
That's fine. There's no need
to say thanks or anything.
Just return the sentiment in our race.
All right, let's move out.
Understood.
Well, he sort of got us there.
He may be our rival, but that was too cool!
I like him... I like him so much!
I can't control myself!
You want to take the lead?
It's good that you're going on
the offensive, but tactics-wise,
I wonder If it wouldn't be better for you
to come from behind for the first race.
As far as I can tell, their guy in the
FD isn't used to this kind of course.
I'm sorry. But please let me do this my way.
I'm determined to take the lead!
Um, I...
I'm Kyoko Iwase. It's a pleasure.
I'm Keisuke Takahashi of Project D.
Keisuke.
I have just one word of advice.
If something strikes you as odd in
the middle of the race, remember this:
Your opponent drives a single turbine.
Huh?
What is that?! I don't know what it even means!
Let's begin. Fumihiro.
Okay.
Very well, here comes the start!
Go!
Say, Nobuhiko, what was the real
strategy you'd thought up for Kyoko?
That doesn't matter anymore.
I could talk and lecture,
but Kyoko is the type who'll race
only out of pure motivation.
She probably felt indebted
to him for fixing her car,
so she wanted to attack him head-on
without resorting to cheap tricks.
That's Kyoko's way.
She's good. She's really good... But why?!
Is she enough of an opponent
to really make me struggle?
I don't get it. Am I racing that badly?
Or are my car's settings off?!
Calm down... Don't get riled up. Just stay cool.
This has only just started!
It's strange.
Tackling the mountain pass has
never felt so fulfilling before.
Even though, no matter what I try,
I could never beat him...
I just...
...want him to see.
To watch me now, and see
the best racing I'm capable of!
That's why I chose to race in front!
Right now, I'm the only thing
he's paying attention to.
And that's enough to make me happy!
Watch me, my darling!
This is who I am!
I'm shocked. She's fast!
I didn't think too much of her 'cause
she's a girl, but I was completely off.
And knowing that, I'm starting over
again and giving this race my all!
I don't plan on being beaten
by someone with the same 13B.
Let's go, my 13B turbo!
Roar for me!
I see.
This is a surprise. Now it's
apparently an even fight.
It has long been theory that single turbine
engines can attain sudden explosive power
when pushed past a certain RPM threshold,
but modern turbines are highly functional
and will operate rapidly even
when there is little back pressure.
That type of power generation
is well suited to this course,
no doubt making the car easier to drive.
The person who worked on it knew this
course inside and out, and was quite clever.
By comparison, Keisuke's car is a twin turbo.
Its method of power output
is not suited for this course.
That acts as a handicap, meaning
that at present, this is an even race.
If you knew all that, couldn't you have
given us a little hint during the practice runs
so we could've done
something with the car's settings?
No. To have to rely upon power settings
is to be unfit to be a driver in Project D.
I told you that Keisuke's assignment in this
race had to do with accelerator handling.
The road's surface is in poor condition,
resulting in limited traction
and making it the ideal stage for
training in accelerator handling.
If we were to assign a level of five
in terms of maximum acceleration
that Keisuke can currently control...
...ideally, that will become doubled to level 10.
Level 10?!
I underwent the same
training myself, long ago.
The space between us opens up
a bit in the straightaways...
She has more power than me?
If so, then why is she so stable
when coming out of corners?
No matter how you look at it,
I should have more acceleration power,
but I'm having a harder time with this.
Am I just that bad a driver?
I don't get it, big brother!
You said she has a single turbine,
but what does that mean?
What's different between a single and a twin?!
Even if we step on the gas at the same point,
she moves smoothly
while I slide out too much.
No matter how you look at it,
I'm putting more load on the tires.
So what do I do?
Delay my acceleration timing?
No, that won't work. I'll fall behind.
It's not the acceleration points I have
to change, it's the way I accelerate!
Maybe more delicately.
Up till now, I've been stepping
down about two centimeters.
If I do half of that, one centimeter.
Take a breath, hold it, one more centimeter...
I'm still stepping too much.
Dammit! This is so hard!
This is the first time I've tried this
kind of delicate accelerator handling!
Incredible... I'm tingling!
I can feel his gaze on my back,
so much that it hurts!
Right now, beyond a shadow of a doubt,
my darling and I are in our own private world!
It's wonderful... I don't want it to end.
I want to keep racing like this forever!
This is a strange feeling. Something
is different from my normal races.
What is this strange peaceful sensation?
I was so wound up and full
of tension, but now...
We're almost to the goal already.
If I keep going like this,
we'll enter the second race.
That's it! I get it now, brother!
That's a single turbine's weak point!
Pitiful... I'm such an idiot!
Why didn't I realize it sooner?!
She's definitely fast when
she's running smoothly,
but if her racing gets thrown off even
momentarily, it makes her vulnerable.
I can't be sure, but I think a single
turbine is probably a peaky engine!
She didn't step on the gas
and her boost pressure dropped!
Yes!
The twin turbo has a little time lag...
...and now is when it does its thing!
No...
Don't pass me!
I want to keep racing. I don't want to let it end!
Don't go... darling!
Hey sanjou, new generation
Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou
Itsu made wasureta furi o shiteiru no?
(Chigiresou na heart no tension) Mune no uzuki
Sono hitomi no oku, osaekirenai mono
(Sou matowaritsuku kono image) yoru o niramu
Sou dare no kokoro ni te o
nobashite fureru subemo
shiranakatta futari, mou koko kara
(Hey sanjou new generation,
Hora, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Nemutta yume o tatakiokoshite
(Kirisaku you na skill)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
Jidai o furuwasete risky tune
Blast my desire
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
break what you wanna break)