"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Tobidase wicked show, kuuki biribiri saku noise
Shibaite norikonase, abarenbou no party
Zettai hikanai kihaku, the dogfight
Buttoi red zone no himei ni shibiretai
Hakanai senkou, like a ryuusei
Isshun no kagayaki demo kamawanai
Kaimamita kichou na fuukei itsuka kataritai
Sou, ima wa honnou no mama dogfight
Shibiretai yume nara koko ni aru
Kagerou yaburu kaze, backfire
Kinou nado sutetekina,
ima kara rocket dance (Dogfight!)
Sakebenai negai ga itamu nara sugu ni oide
You're big time gambler
Orokasa wa utsukushii kyokusen
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Souon mo everywhere
Yokonaguri, 5G hodo no heavyweight
Giri de soukou, miri no koubou
Za-za-zan!
Rakushou de funde ikeru ze, madamada
What? Really?
Where are you watching from?
The C-21 hairpin?!
They're already that far?
What does this mean?
They're running tail to nose.
They've gone almost halfway and
the Eight-Six is still on Tohru's tail.
I can't believe it, Atsuro!
There's no way anyone could
keep up with Tohru this long!
I don't want to believe it either.
For the Eight-Six to be this fast...
I've got a bad feeling.
Tohru hates to lose, so he'll dig in his heels
and get more and more worked up.
This downhill is gonna get dangerous.
One of 'em just might crash!
"Act 2: Full Throttle! Downhill Battle"
In the underpowered FR,
he is a downhill specialist.
To be sure, he has several points
in common with Fujiwara.
They both have an instinctive sense for speed,
and have mastered cornering at high speeds.
Perhaps what decisively
separates the two will be
the degree to which they've
refined their technique.
Meaning the fact that Fujiwara is
coming from behind on the first race...
...will be of great importance
in determining victory or defeat.
What do you mean, Ryosuke?
Fujiwara has been observing his
opponent's racing from behind,
and should have begun to
understand it on a sensory level.
I feel like I've sort of got it now.
By looking at him from behind...
...I see the difference in how he and I race.
They're here! There they are!
Did you see that just now?!
They're both awesome!
They were only like this far away from the wall!
Those are some crazy sons of bitches!
You spend too much money on your car.
If you're going to say it
like that, I'll lend it to you.
But...
...on one condition.
Condition?
If you lose this next race,
you have to give up racing!
I mean it this time.
If you don't keep your promise,
I'll break up with you for real.
I ain't gonna lose!
H-He's right up on me!
Why?! This is me driving here!
I'm the best racer there is.
What the hell's going on?!
This Eight-Six...
What the hell is this guy?
Tohru can't shake the Eight-Six?
Wh-What the heck's going on?!
I just don't get it!
Tohru's greatest weapon,
learned from a long time of racing,
is the unbeatable speed of his corner entry.
No one should be able to match that cornering!
His opponent knows all the
corners here inside and out.
It's way beyond having run it just one night.
And yet, not only has the
Eight-Six not been shaken off...
...it's actually keeping up!
What incredible corner entry!
He knows every inch of this course!
But...
In the time between recovering from corners
and entering the next braking,
the Eight-Sixis faster.
Why? It's not a difference in automotive power.
On a mountain road of complex terrain,
there are more corners
than can even be counted.
In particular, in a downhill race,
there are far more "partial" areas
that are neither straights nor curves
than one would expect.
To be sure, there are lots of places
where you'd waver between
going in at full- or half-throttle.
The ability to adapt to those sorts of areas
will be the difference between the
racing of Fujiwara and his opponent.
Remember that, Keisuke.
In the theory of high-speed
public racing that I espouse,
this is a most important point.
Okay.
Shit! You think I'm gonna lose?!
That's crazy dangerous! I'm, like, shaking!
I've never seen such awesome
corner entry before!!
To be able to keep up with
Seven Star Leaf's Roadster...
Who the heck is in that Eight-Six?!
He ain't even a local...
This is friggin' incredible!
Project D's got crazy mad talent!
It won't be long now. They're approaching
the point that will decide this race.
Yeah.
Say, Ryosuke, don't leave me hanging. Tell me!
What kind of plan is it? The strategy
for the uncovered drainage ditches.
Looks like Tohru's still bein' followed.
They've already passed C-10.
C-10?!
This guy's a lot better than we'd thought.
But Atsuro, even if Tohru can't shake
him off, that doesn't mean he'll lose!
They'll just change positions
and go into the second race.
The real battle's still to come, right?
There's no way Tohru could be overtaken!
You're right. This whole
overtaking thing is unthinkable.
The area up ahead is gonna be just impossible.
That's right!
Even if you can't get rid of him,
there's nothin' to worry about, Tohru.
Go into to the next race and don't lose!
Very well, I shall explain.
The strategy for the uncovered ditch
area that I explained to Fujiwara...
Yeah?
Fujiwara had already acquired
a specialty technique, correct?
You mean putting his tire into
the drain? The "drain drop" thing?
Correct.
So you're gonna use that?
Unthinkable. It would not be
applicable with this type of ditch.
Even you should recognize that.
The strategy is to use the exact
opposite of that technique.
The exact opposite...
He's an unbelievable driver! I can't shake him!
I really want to look at his
driving from behind! His driving...
Just what kind of driving is it?!
How is he tackling my home course?
How's it different from mine?
No matter what, I'm goin' into the second race!
I wanna see this guy's technique!
His cut-in timing is a little early!
I've seen the line!
Bastard! You're just gonna
ignore that uncovered ditch?!
He's pulled forward! He's gonna
go in on the next right, huh?
Shit! I won't let you!
Even if I'm just half-way in front,
the road is still mine!
I won't give you any space!
I've got local pride, dammit!
I won't let you pass!
What?!
Idiot! There's not enough
room for you to get by!
There shouldn't even be any road there!
This is bullshit!
You... Where the hell are you driving?!
I told you it would require
load shift techniques.
Cornering at maximum speed places the
majority of load on the two outside tires.
Accelerating at that point causes
increased load shift to the rear.
So both outer-side loads
are borne only by the rear?
Correct. In other words, the driver
intentionally creates a strong load shift
and reduces as much load as
possible from the inner-side front.
If you can do that...
...then at full throttle, you can
shortcut directly above the ditch.
He passed me! Am... Am I dreaming?
What was that just now? What happened?!
Try that again at the next right!
What the hell just happened?!
Show me that again so I can see!
Dammit! If an Eight-Six can do it, so can this!
I don't feel my right front
tire gripping the ground!
Is it in the air?
I'm gonna fall!
It's no good! I can't get back up!
--He wiped out!
--You okay?!
This is bad...
Are you all right?
You're not hurt?
A crash at C-7?
Was it Tohru?!
Any injuries?
I see.
The Roadster was overtaken by the
Eight-Six and crashed. It can't race.
You win.
What's going on?
What the heck is going on?!
At first glance I thought it was an R34 GT-R...
I do like those FR GT turbos.
That's a nice hobby right there.
Take a good look at the true
power of an ace driver.
Fujiwara!
I'm Atsuro Kawai.
I'm Keisuke Takahashi.
He doesn't intimidate his
opponent, but at the same time
he doesn't seem to be
putting on any airs at all.
This is our home course, and he shouldn't
know anything about what I'm capable of...
So how can he be so calm?
Just what is this?
This unknown feeling of intimidation?
Atsuro...
I'm shocked, Tohru. Even before we've started,
I feel like I've been made
to walk to their rhythm.
Don't think about it! Just keep your own pace.
I couldn't, which is why that happened to me.
Yeah...
Also, let me give you one piece of advice.
In the area starting around C-6, where
the drainage ditches are uncovered...
Be sure not to open any room on the in-side,
and stay right on the corner line!
If you open up more than a meter,
he's sure to go past you.
These bastards will shortcut
right over the ditch.
What are you talkin' about, Tohru?
That's ridiculous.
These guys can do it!
Believe what I'm telling you!
Do not open up any space on the in-side!
Very well, let's begin.
Don't let him pass you, Atsuro.
I'm counting on you!
Atsuro... These are some
incredible drivers we're up against.
They let me know just how
big a gap there is between us.
You might not even have a chance of winning,
but at least make it through the first race!
These Project D guys are incredible!
It's like they have an aura!
Welco--!
Hey there, Kenji.
What the hell kind of face is that?
Well, it's not like you're gonna
get any high-octane or anything...
Hey now! Anyway, I've got some news.
Project D has won again.
Really?! Where this time?
In Tochigi.
How did Takumi do?
He won, of course! And he
set a new course record.
Looks like they won both
the uphill and downhill!
Bit by bit, Takumi's moving up the ranks, huh?
As opposed to...
Meaning we're no different from
ever, eh? Come on, don't say that.
What? You're going to quit racing?
That was the deal, wasn't it?
I lost last night's race.
What's wrong, Tohru?! Did you hit
your head in yesterday's wreck?
I don't like this. Get a hold of yourself!
What are you talkin' about?
You're the one who said
I had to quit racing if I lost!
I know, but... I just said it trying to
be mean, because I was frustrated.
It's all right. It's actually a relief I lost. Really.
Up till now, I thought that as a local,
I could never lose to any out-of-towner
and that I raced faster than anyone.
I had total confidence in myself.
But I lost outright to some guy from another
pass, who'd only practiced for one night.
Sure it was a shock,
but it feels good that when I got
beaten, it was done so perfectly.
Tohru...
Don't make that face, Naho.
I'm not sayin' I'm never
gonna drive a car again.
Simply toeing the line isn't
how a racer does things, right?
I'm just gonna have a different relation
with cars than I have had up till now.
It really was the best night.
I've never been that stoked.
I think it was great that
I got to meet those guys.
It's like any profession... There are
very few who ever make it to the top.
Those guys are probably among the select few.
But I know now that I'm not.
Project D... They really are awesome dudes.
Project D? Oh, that team from Gunma
that people are talking about recently.
They're coming? Hm.
What are you doing on the weekend, Tomo?
There are no races this week, right?
No races, but I'm busy with tests.
Hey, you're not trying to
drag me into this, are you?
Of course not.
There's no need to worry.
I definitely won't lose.
I swear it on the name of the Toudou School!
Hey sanjou, new generation
Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou
Itsu made wasureta furi o shiteiru no?
(Chigiresou na heart no tension) Mune no uzuki
Sono hitomi no oku, osaekirenai mono
(Sou matowaritsuku kono image) yoru o niramu
Sou dare no kokoro ni te o
nobashite fureru subemo
shiranakatta futari, mou koko kara
(Hey sanjou new generation,
Hora, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Nemutta yume o tatakiokoshite
(Kirisaku you na skill)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
Jidai o furuwasete risky tune
Blast my desire
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
break what you wanna break)