"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
In the silver smoke amidst the frozen city
Payback for a dream I've seen so many times
My body is frozen in a
memory that I can't shake
Slam on the accelerator and deceive myself
Broken in the night
My eyes become sharper
All from someone's whim
It seems like the world will end any minute
Break into the night, it's the time
With scared eyes, I'm lost in the night
Embraced by a falling dream
Scared of being alone, missin' my heart
Even hurting myself
Love me so much,
enough that I could fall apart
If only I could throw everything away
And just love you
Then I know I could face the truth
--Takumi, it's for you.
--Who's it from?
Ryosuke Takahashi.
What?!
Ryosuke...
...Takahashi.
Less power, but fast!
He clears the corners faster.
There's no way my brother will lose to him now!
A battle?
--Yeah.
--Is that like a fistfight?
No, a "battle" is a car race.
If you don't want to race, just ignore him.
It's not that I don't want to.
I may lose to him,
but I don't want to not race him.
You still don't think Takumi can win?
No. I know he's exceptional,
but he's still in high school.
I wonder how long he'll even
be able to stay in the race.
The only reason I think Takumi has a chance...
...is that he's Bunta's son.
The son of that crazy Bunta...
Keisuke...
I've been thinking about this for a long time,
but when I lose a street race...
--...I'll retire.
--What?!
By the way, there are only two racers
who I think could beat me one day.
One of them is you, Keisuke.
Me?
And the other is...
"Act 25: The Last Battle!"
Takumi!
Good luck, Takumi!
I believe in you! I know you can win!
And I hope you beat Ryosuke Takahashi
and become the fastest
racing star in Gunma, Takumi!
Takumi!
Okay, we got it, Itsuki! Now get off of him!
You're late.
It's already 10:00.
You're still so ignorant.
I've been waiting for you.
It's impressive that you've
learned so much technique
at such a young age.
I've just driven Akina Pass more
than others, so I'm used to it.
I don't have any special technique.
I think you are just overestimating me.
That's interesting.
I guess you don't really
understand your own potential.
What?
You're so unique.
It'll be nice to sit down
and talk to you someday.
Big brother...
Let's get started.
This should be a fun evening.
All right! Move your cars!
Yes, sir!
Is it all right if we Red Suns run this race?
Sure.
Get some guys from Speed
Stars to be officials, too.
--Got it.
--Iketani, I'll be at the goal.
All right. Do a good job!
Keisuke, I'll be at the five hairpins.
Okay.
Of course Ryosuke will win, won't he?
We're going to get our revenge, right?
Of course we are.
No matter how fast that guy is,
there's no way my brother will lose.
You're right. Okay, I'm off!
Hello, Fujiwara Tofu-- Oh, it's you.
Hey, Bunta. I just got to Akina.
There's a huge crowd over here.
You'd be amazed if you saw it.
Yeah, and...?
So, what do you say?
Do you think Takumi can win this?
I hear that his opponent is
Gunma's fastest, a street racing king.
Who cares?
If you don't have something
else to say, I'm hanging up.
Hey, Bunta!
Wait a minute, Bunta!
I told you not to hang up!
All right! How are the corners looking?
Okay! The first corner is ready whenever.
Skate Center here.
This straight section looks good.
The 17th hairpin is ready anytime.
Five hairpins here.
No cars around here, and we're ready!
This is Number Six.
We've moved all the
spectators' cars. We're ready!
I'm so nervous!
My throat is completely dry,
and my heart is pounding out of control!
The air around this whole
pass is filled with tension.
I wonder if Takumi is feeling all right?
Takumi...
You're racing against the best.
It doesn't matter if you lose. Just do your best!
Come on, Takumi!
I know you can win this!
There's no way my brother will lose.
But something always happens
in Akina Pass when that Eight-Six is racing.
Excuse me. What's happening with the race?
It hasn't started yet.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
This is the starting line.
How does it look at the finish line?
Yeah... we're ready here anytime.
Okay! Let's get going!
Hold on a minute!
Let me do the countdown.
Just for this race. Okay?
I have to do the countdown for this race
between my big brother
and the Eight-Six myself.
I'm starting the countdown!
Five... Four...
Three... Two... One...
Go!
Go, Takumi!
All right! Takumi's going right by him!
Takumi is ahead of him now!
Takumi! Keep going!
That's my big brother's strategy.
He always lets them get ahead at first,
and then catches them later.
That's how he's been winning his races.
His "fastest racer" theory can't go wrong!
They're both amazing!
Extremely close twin drifts!
Using that much drift isn't
Ryosuke Takahashi's style at all!
What a show, right from the beginning!
Even Ryosuke Takahashi
started using drift right away!
I bet he wants to beat Takumi
using Takumi's specialty,
just to show the willpower
of a street racing king!
Takumi is doing great, too!
This is going to be an amazing race.
Wow, Takumi! You've got to win! Go Takumi!
Right, Iketani?
Um... right...
How impressive...
The Eight-Six has never driven like this before.
I knew it. He has improved!
He uses very little
counter-steering as he stabilizes
in the final moment of drift.
That hasn't changed.
But he counter-steers less
right after a turn-in maneuver.
I don't understand.
It hasn't been that long since the last race,
and his weakness is already gone.
He is improving in every race.
I need to change the scenario a bit...
...but that's all.
The result will be the same.
My "fastest racer" theory is invincible!
Hey, Takeshi...
Let me just tell you that I didn't park
here just because your car was here.
Don't you make any mistake about that.
I was planning to park here
before I even arrived.
Why don't you go away?
No way! I also knew that this was
the only spot to watch the race.
You're the one who should go away.
All the beginners usually want to
watch it from such obvious places...
...like the five hairpin curves.
Right.
The race isn't decided in a spot like that.
This is the only point where
they could go for the win.
So, that's what you think too, huh?
Let me just say that you're impressive.
You, too.
So, this place is really deserted, huh?
If someone sees us here,
they'll think we're friends.
Shoot! How annoying!
Here they come!
Whoa! They're both getting
so close to the guardrail!
Oh, my god! That was amazing!
Whoa! What am I waiting for?!
I've got to tell him.
How annoying...
--Hello, Fujiwara...
--Hey, Bunta! Are you listening?!
Heck, it's you again.
Listen hard!
They just passed in front of me.
They were both drifting very hard,
with Takumi's Eight-Six ahead
and the FC right behind him.
Takumi was ahead?
That's not good...
Not good? Why?
Calm down a little, Yuichi.
It's more advantageous to chase
the other car than to run from it.
That's common sense.
That's true.
The rear driver can study the course
and rhythm of the other driver.
If he's skilled enough,
he can also copy the driving.
But maybe he can also just drive away.
The driver in front is
under tremendous pressure.
Having another car follow
you at the same speed
gradually pushes you into a mental corner.
The harder you try to get away,
and the longer you're followed,
the more threatening your opponent seems.
On top of that, Takumi is still
new to such racing tactics.
I'm sure he's really freaking out by now.
You think so?!
Anyway, I'll give you a call
later with the outcome.
All right.
That boy... Will he lose?
Maybe not...
Here they come!
This is incredible!
This is the 24th corner.
The Eight-Six and
Ryosuke's FC just passed here.
We've checked the time, and it's just amazing!
If they hold this pace, they'll break
the Eight-Six's course record...
...by seven or eight seconds!
Anyway, that's my report.
Seven to eight seconds faster
than when I raced against him?
Give me a break!
Is this what happens when my
big brother gets really serious?
This is starting to get scary.
This race is going to become legendary.
It looks like Takumi is still in the lead!
All right! He can win this thing, right, Iketani?
Yeah. But I wonder how
long he can keep this up?
--What?!
--That's Ryosuke Takahashi he's racing against.
I'll be happy if Takumi can
just finish this race safely.
I'm going at full power,
and he's right on my tail!
No matter how fast I go, I still can't get away!
It's no good... I might lose this race.
Ryosuke Takahashi...
I can't even compare to such a great racer!
I really don't want to...
...but I'm going to lose!
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
--You know...
--I don't want to lose.
--Fujiwara Tofu...
--This race...
--His sense for drift...
--I don't want to lose!
Ryosuke, I...!
--Takumi, go!
--You can't lose...
Just like that!
Keep going!
Win!
Heading towards the conclusion
of this emotional race...
Next on Initial D: "The New Downhill Legend!"
Don't miss it!