"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
I didn't notice when I was in front...
...but his lines are different!
I don't get it. How can he be
so fast using a line like that?
"Act 23: Endless Battle"
This is the fiercest opponent you've
yet faced. He has no weaknesses.
At present, there is only one
piece of advice I can give:
Endure.
As much as possible, look at the
course and not the other driver.
Don't forget.
Just how long should I endure?
Hey, how many rounds does this make?
Let's see... The Eight-Six started
out in front, so... Four, five...
Six.
I never thought that things
would stalemate like this.
Yeah. At this rate, it's hard to imagine
how the race could be settled, huh?
He did it again... His line!
It's different each time!
I don't understand it!
Is this how he races when he
goes to record racing times?
If this is how he sets record times, then I
don't understand what his lines mean!
Sure enough, this is strange.
Something doesn't feel right.
Would the great Toshiya Joshima really
be unable to outrun an opponent?
I think there's something we're not seeing.
Like what?
If he's stringing the
Eight-Six along on purpose,
then perhaps a shocking
turn of events is in motion
under the water's surface, so to speak.
Not good. It's showing up far too often...
Fumihiro.
Once this sixth round is finished,
I want you to have them stop refueling.
Okay.
It's really intense. He's just pulling
me around all over the place.
Sure enough, this is an enemy
that's not easily defeated, eh?
Yeah. By the way, Fumihiro.
I'd like to see the calculations
that've been run so far.
Is there a lot of variation in the times?
That S2000 uses a really random driving style.
Whoa, hang on. The one that's showing
a lot of time variation is you.
Take a look.
These are the second, fourth and
sixth races when he was in front.
The times are so exact,
it almost makes you sick, huh?
He's like a computer,
keeping a set, precise pace.
I don't believe it. This can't be right!
Aren't you dragging this
out a little too long, Jo?
I know you're having fun, but...
No, no. It's no fun at all.
This is taking everything I've got.
That's how good a driver this fellow is.
But Jo, middle-aged guys like us taking
on teenagers in a war of attrition...
That puts us at a disadvantage.
I know. I'll end this in the next round.
Okay. Well, we'll be waiting
for you down there again.
Yeah.
Don't be fooled by his tricks.
His goal is to confuse the line he takes.
Your times when you have the lead
are erratic and becoming worse,
which is proof that you've fallen into his trap.
Do not be led astray by his line,
and instead believe in your own.
In this seventh round,
things will take a dramatic turn.
Be sure not to match his pace.
You must counter in your own way.
You should also have noticed
that this course's ditches
and side areas may be of use.
Listen, Fujiwara. This is the only way
that will give us a chance at victory.
That Fujiwara...
It seems like he's taken quite a shock.
It was really unbelievable...
For the lines to be so different
while keeping a consistent time...
Is that even possible, Ryosuke?
Even on lines that at first
glance appear random,
enough torque at the right points
can result in matching times.
This is, after all, a course
he has run many times.
But is it even possible?
However, this time would clearly
not be close to one's best.
You mean...
I think Fujiwara has probably noticed as well...
His opponent is not yet racing at full capacity.
Sure enough, the appellation
"God Arm" is not just for show.
Toshiya Joshima could have the ability
to travel at the same speed
no matter what his driving line.
And yet, he most assuredly has a chosen line
that he uses when out to secure his best time.
He has yet to reveal that
line to Fujiwara even once.
"Cunning" is the only way to describe it.
Oh! So that's why Ryosuke said to look
at the course and not the opponent!
That's what he meant by "ghost"!
Fujiwara's ability to absorb the racing
style of his opponents when behind them
is in this case counting against him.
He's been shown numerous fake
lines and gotten quite confused.
However, this battle shall
shift in the seventh round.
Toshiya Joshima plans to settle the
race by pulling ahead from behind.
Is that true, Ryosuke?
This isn't funny.
He's made me race for all I'm worth, but he
hasn't even been running at full speed?
My tires are already giving out!
This time in particular, I feel like I can't win.
It's like he's got me completely
in the palm of his hand!
I probably have a neurosis
about guys in that age group.
No matter what I do,
he's always one step ahead of me.
I have no idea what I should do!
Judging by the times so far,
this whole thing has been
at Mr. Joshima's pace, eh?
Project D's Eight-Six is worn out by now.
The grip on their guy's tires
is probably more worn down.
The single-handed steer is easy on the tires.
But more importantly...
...when Jo comes tearin' past from behind,
it's enough to throw any
opponent's rhythm off balance.
For high-level racers who've
mastered their techniques to an extent,
the tendency for that will be especially strong.
When he's racing, Jo looks surprisingly
unconcerned about his driving line,
but the truth is, even that is
calculated and under control.
The way he disrupts his opponent's rhythm
is planned, like a premeditated crime.
He's learned to control the car
behind him while he's up in front.
That's the only conclusion you can draw.
That young driver in the
Eight-Six sure has it rough.
Bein' shown Jo's driving for three
straight races is pretty unbearable.
I wonder if this seventh round
will settle it, like Jo said.
In the first half of this course,
there is a section of winding roads
with more than ten left-right directional shifts.
If a race that had become deadlocked
were to resume, it would be there.
Toshiya Joshima will spring some sort of trap!
Ko made fun of me, but I've had good
reason for dragging this out so long.
It's plain to see when behind the Eight-Six
like this, watching his movements.
Now I can do this the smart way, using
the difference in our tire per formance!
But there's not much room for error.
My own tires are already at their limit.
But victory must be smart.
That's how an adult wins!
In the area from the eighth
continuous winding road to the ninth,
there's a point where the
rhythm changes slightly.
What's more, it's just up ahead...
There!
Awesome!
"Beware of Brush Fires"
There's nothing to be disappointed about.
This in no way means you're unskilled.
On the contrary, considering
an Eight-Six's capabilities,
it's been a miraculously good fight.
There's no doubt that you
have exceptional talent.
I hope you'll let this experience
contribute to your future growth.
I see. Understood.
Ryosuke... Fujiwara's been passed.
I guess it's over.
We put up a good fight, though.
He may be our opponent,
but that was brilliantly executed.
Right up until he overtook Fujiwara,
he's controlled the
progression of events 100%.
Everything has occurred exactly as planned...
And the ultimate expression of
this is his single-handed steer.
Even knowing that, we were unable to stop it.
"Steep Curve"
Dammit! What's that idiot Fujiwara doing?!
And after Keisuke won the hillclimb for us!
He got passed, huh?
At this rate, there's nothing we can do.
Shit! We can't win the downhill?!
I'm not so sure.
If it was anyone else racing I'd think that,
but that's Fujiwara out there.
We still don't know what could happen.
Keisuke...
The truth is, I don't want you to lose...
...because I'm going to be the
one who beats you! Fujiwara!
Toshiya Joshima's technique is so refined
that it is a siren song for
sensory-oriented drivers like Fujiwara.
Before they know it, they've matched pace
and are being dragged forcefully along.
I knew from the start that he
would fall into the enemy's trap...
But it has changed the course
of what was a deadlocked race.
What do you mean, Ryosuke?
Freed from the "spell" that bound him,
Fujiwara can return to his own pace.
Something may yet be done...
Our chances are not zero!
I guess I'll end this. There's no more
need for me to preserve my tires.
I'll use up the rest of their grip
and make a dash for it!
D-Did you see that just now? That Eight-Six...
Yeah. But it can't be... That was impossible!
The tires on Fujiwara's Eight-Six are
not the only ones reaching their limit.
The enemy's S2000 is slightly heavier...
True enough.
No matter how skillfully one
manages tire performance,
they have a physical limit.
That time will certainly come
for our opponent's tires as well.
The conditions will be the same...
When that happens, there will actually
be more options for the Eight-Six.
I said earlier that the single-handed steer
is the expression of Toshiya Joshima's driving.
To have achieved steering with just one hand
is to have complete mastery over
the outcome of driving itself.
What does that mean?
In a panic, anyone would grab
the wheel to steer with both hands.
In other words, our opponent believes
such a thing could never occur.
I get it...
The conviction that though
racing near one's limit,
one has predicted with 100%
accuracy what will occur next
and failure is an impossibility
is perhaps what predicates
the single-handed steer.
Unless we somehow shatter that conviction,
we will continue to be
powerless, and we will lose.
We must make him grasp the wheel
with both hands, if only for an instant,
or we'll never make our chance.
Causing the single-handled steer to fail
will also bring down Toshiya Joshima's
method of predicting driving outcome.
It can't be! There's no gap between us!
This is impossible.
What is he doing?
Be sure not to match his pace.
You must counter in your own way.
You should also have noticed
that this course's ditches
and side areas may be of use.
This is the only way that will
give us a chance at victory.
Now I get it. So that's how!
He's gone...
It can't be!
Unbelievable!
What just happened?
Another pair of headlights, suddenly
shining out from the darkness...
I lost it for a moment. I never thought
he'd cut in at such a sharp angle!
That was truly godlike driving.
I had a vague feeling he'd try cornering
using the raised road shoulder boundary...
but that technique brings
with it an incredibly high risk!
Just a single mistake in timing
would cause you to momentarily lose control.
For my car, which has already been
lowered about as far as it can go,
something like that would be impossible.
For older cars with an open underbody,
it's a game-changing ace-in-the hole.
Mr. Joshima... He got passed.
What the heck happened?!
What did I say? We don't know what'll happen.
That's the kind of guy Fujiwara is.
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie