"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
Eew, it's all sticky!
What do we do with all this
oil-soaked newspaper?
We'll burn it out in a field
somewhere, so gather it all up.
The only thing we can do with the remaining
oil is use a bunch of water to wash it off.
Time to get some water from
the river and play bucket relay.
We won't be able to get it completely clean.
A single good rain spell would wash it all off.
"Act 16: Hillclimb of Fury"
"Honzaka Tunnel"
"Corporate Reforestation Area"
--Hey.
--Is there anything we can help with?
Huh? Where's Kenta?
In Gunma, getting more parts.
Once we have those,
we might be able to fix this.
Huh? Jeez, even Fujiwara
got up and came out here?
Um, is there anything I can help out with?
I appreciate it, but you need to
get plenty of rest for tonight.
That's part of your job, too.
But...
I'll say this to all of you.
I'm aware that even if we do this,
it could all be for nothing.
But D has made it this far
with a perfect record of victory,
and I can't sit back while my stupidity
causes the loss that breaks that record.
Even if it costs me my life, I will race!
Please pick up the pace in small increments.
Don't try to push it too far.
Okay.
The front left side is badly damaged, so be
especially careful going into right corners
that'll place excess load on it.
Yeah, got it.
Okay. Here goes.
I'm counting on you, FD!
For the sake of everyone who's gone
without sleep to make this happen...
And for my own pride...
Let's pull off a miracle!
Them idiots all turned white as sheets!
Especially that spiky-haired bastard
in the FD. He was shakin' like a leaf!
Those guys talk a lotta crap, but they just
can't bring it. What a bunch of losers!
If we can scare that other driver in the
Eight-Six as well, we win both races!
Ducks in a barrel, man!
I don't like the way this
vibrates when I'm braking,
but it looks like I can pull off left-side cornering.
The problem is the right!
Unless I see how it acts when I push
it to the limit, this'll be impossible!
Shit!
Son of a bitch!
I was only going at 80% speed,
but as soon as I shifted the
balance of load to the front,
it suddenly spun out.
I thought that with a little more work we
could turn this around somehow, but...
...I was naive!
What should I do? I can't
face the others like this.
Brother... I'm sorry. I just want to cry.
Oh, no. Someone's coming.
Wait a minute. That's the
sound of a rotary engine.
Hi! I came to cheer you on again.
What are you doing out here?
Um...
Is my darling mad at me?
Am I being too persistent?
Please listen. I...
I need to ask a favor!
"Reduce Speed"
Since the days of the Red Suns,
it's been an unwritten rule
that we only race our own cars.
But I'm breaking that rule!
Let me do this, brother!
If you don't approve, I still intend to race.
It doesn't even have to be
an official Project D race.
Let me race! No... I have to race!
Hello? It's Ryosuke.
I'm sorry for the short notice, but I
won't be needing that car after all.
Yes. That's right. Sorry. I'll call you again later.
Brother... Wait, were you trying
to get another car ready?
Not a very elegant solution, I thought,
but there was no other alternative.
The last thing I wanted to do was
concede defeat without having even run...
Especially to those whom we face this time.
Yeah!
But Ryosuke, will they accept a change of cars?
They'll gladly push rules on us to
put the advantage in their favor,
but I bet they'll raise hell over anything
that gives us the least bit of an edge.
I have reason to believe they'll allow it.
Be forceful with them, and be defiant.
It will probably work.
What?! I don't care if it's the
same model, it's still a different car!
Screw that! I ain't gonna allow it!
Huh. I thought you said we could
"use the Eight-Six or somethin',"
as I recall.
Shit. I didn't say nothin' like that!
F1 rules allow a "T car"
for use as a backup, yes?
So let's cut to the chase.
We'd be using a borrowed car
we've never driven before.
The odds are overwhelmingly
in your favor, correct?
If you don't allow this, our only option
is to say that Project D was never here.
We can take both cars and head back
to Gunma. Is that what you want?
Talk about a surprise. Just like you said,
I was forceful with them and it worked.
Meaning there's more to
this than meets the eye.
For all their complaining about what
an inconvenience it is to race us,
they're strangely adamant about
what constitutes a victory for them.
That's something we can't overlook.
There must be a reason
they're so determined to win.
And not for victory's sake,
but for something more tangible.
Don't tell me... Money?!
It could be.
Hearing that makes me that much more
determined not to lose to those guys!
How pitiful.
Wantin' to win so bad you'd
wheel out someone else's car...
What a disgrace. These guys got no pride!
Don't let them provoke you, Keisuke.
If you get in a fight with them, we lose.
Yeah, I know.
I'm just happy to be here at the starting line.
Compared to that, I could care less
about their idiot attempts to provoke me.
I'm grateful. To everyone...
Even to him.
Okay, here we go! Starting in five seconds!
Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
I'll tear ahead of 'im while he's still
tryin' to get used to an unfamiliar car.
That's why I chose to go
in front for the first race.
I ain't no fool! I'm gonna win this for sure!
Say, Ryosuke, there's
something I want to ask you.
I didn't expect you to cancel
the car you were preparing
and let Keisuke use the other one.
It's not like you, that way of thinking.
You've misunderstood slightly.
If either were to be driven for the first time,
I chose the one that would be
slightly less of a burden for Keisuke.
Do you understand?
Oh! Keisuke had raced against that car once!
Correct.
He had seen up close how it
performed at maximum levels,
and is probably aware on a sensory level
of how it is different from his own FD.
To me, it was the only choice that
would prove advantageous in battle.
There were no romantic
concerns at all in my decision.
That girl's coming here tonight...
...was the greatest luck that
Keisuke could have asked for.
As I thought, this car's got power and
the underbody carries itself smoothly.
Thank you. This is a good car!
Still, this was a bit of a shock.
Kyoko, letting someone
borrow your FD for a race...
You'll forgive me for saying it like this,
but you've had a sort of
unnatural affection for that car.
It's strange even to me.
I always hated the idea of letting
anyone but me drive my car...
But I didn't hate it, I was really happy.
I've never felt this way before!
If my FD can help my darling,
then I'll gladly let him use it.
Sure enough, my darling is special to me.
Win, my darling!
Awesome! That was perfect slide control!
That's a borrowed FD, right? Sure enough,
Keisuke Takahashi is an FD specialist!
Still, there's a bit of space
between them. This looks rough.
Apparently they couldn't practice
running this course at all last night.
But they still agreed to go
up against a Lancer Evo?!
This race could be a dangerous one for them!
Some journalist wrote in some magazine...
When it comes to general street racing,
the Lancer Evo is the fastest in the world!
Some stupid FD doesn't stand a chance!
I ain't got time to be playin' around, boy.
Just disappear already!
I've been thinking... I think what will
make this race is extremely simple.
Keisuke has two major handicaps.
The first is that he's not in his own car.
The second is, he hasn't practiced this course.
Normally, this would be a
completely unwinnable race,
but with enough of a difference in the
drivers' abilities, the handicap is lessened.
Keisuke's skills are far
superior to his opponent's.
You know that, do you?
It's just instinct, but if I
saw it, I'd know for sure.
He's not that good a driver.
Under normal conditions, I think
Keisuke would've already won by now.
I see.
Because of the handicap, right now
there's a kind of balance between them...
That's what kind of race the hillclimb is.
I can't shake him. Why?!
This is ridiculous. This is a Lancer Evo!
My foot's so far on the gas that
I'm takin' corners so fast and scary
that I gotta keep my eyes
from poppin' outta my head,
so how can some guy who hasn't even
practiced this course be keepin' up?!
Pick up the pace, idiot!
You're gonna make that Lancer Evo cry!
He takes winding corners the orthodox way,
on a line that goes toward the center.
I take corners tighter, close to the in-line.
The Lancer Evo pulls ahead
where the line's a bit tough for me,
but at the next left, I'll take a wide
line and pick up cornering speed.
Then I'll tear ahead of him on
the course's longest straightaway!
I'll use the cornering tactic I used
in Tochigi against the R34,
where speeding as you come
out of the corner entry is key.
Against a high-speed, 4WD Lancer Evo,
it will be make-or-break time!
You stupid son of a bitch!
Don't you know? Up ahead,
there's a construction barricade
that makes the road narrower!
There ain't enough room for
two cars to go side by side!
Don't come any closer!
I ain't got enough space!
You dumb son of a bitch!
What the hell?
Hey, asshole!
You suck! This is Project D?
This is how you do things?
Hog the road like a damn maniac?!
If I hadn't pulled back,
that would've been a huge accident!
You really think that?
What?!
You just don't take in
your surroundings, do you?
What'd you say?
If you'd gone far enough over to the right,
both cars could've passed side by side.
If you couldn't instantly see that,
you don't know what you're talking about.
This wasn't some winding,
G-shaped curve. It was a straightaway!
I'd planned on going two centimeters
toward the left barricade,
which would've opened up about five
centimeters for you along the guardrail.
Quit talkin' crap!
You just don't get it. Not with
that amount of driving instinct.
That you couldn't adapt on the fly,
changing course to come in at full speed...
It's really disappointing.
After that, the real battle should've been how
we execute braking techniques at top speed.
Those are the kinds of
races I've run up till now.
I've got nothing else to say to your ass.
True to form, eh?
Yeah.
Thank you.
It's a good car.
There's no way we can deny
this one. We had witnesses.
Dammit!
I didn't expect him to lose on the hillclimb.
The next opponent is that kid. Whatever.
That Lancer Evo's got a rear wing, huh?
How many Evos does this make now?
Six. They make for tough races.
There's somethin' I wanna
say before we get started.
You're pretty young. What's your name?
Fujiwara.
Okay, Fujiwara. This is just between us,
but all you guys are sorta in trouble.
That guy that lost the race
just now has sort of flipped out.
He's called up a bunch of his friends,
really bad characters.
There's a lot of them, and they
should be on their way right now.
C'mon, don't look at me like that.
I don't like stuff like that, either.
But you seem like an all right guy,
so I thought I'd give you a heads-up.
It'd be best if you sorta didn't race too hard.
In exchange, I can cover for ya...
make sure you at least don't get hurt.
So, in other words...
You're telling me to lose on purpose?
Nah, I didn't say that.
All I said was not to race too hard.
I'm sayin' this to be kind. Think about it.
Unbelievable. Somebody blew a
race that should've been easy as hell,
so now it's up to me.
I'm gonna have to win at least one of these.
I've already gone and planted the seeds...
What is it, Fujiwara? You're looking
more serious than usual. You nervous?
Matsumoto. The truth is, just now...
He said that, did he?
Yes. What do you think about it?
I don't. Who's gonna buy
a cheap threat like that?
Forget everything that doesn't matter.
Just concentrate on the race.
The only reason we're even here is to win!
Understood. I was thinking the same thing.
All right, here we go!
Starting in five seconds!
Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
I gave no advice to Keisuke or Fujiwara.
This time, I will have them act freely.
The driver of the Evo VI is
more skilled than I thought.
While he appears nondescript at first glance,
on the downhill, that is likely
to turn out to be a ruse.
I've got no illusions about beatin' Project D's
driver fair and square on the downhill.
The key is to not let him
enjoy himself durin' the race.
Nobody, no matter who they are,
reacts well to violence.
It breaks their concentration...
In other words, "don't race too hard."
It's not like I said anything wrong.
All I need is for his racing to be just a little off.
I'll take care of the rest,
leaving him in the dust!
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte