"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it's an era
where it travels in a second
But you don't know what
choice you should take
"Money can't buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don't realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can't even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let's warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That's our law!
Don't feel bad.
The Eight-Six of Mount Akina
will simply turn into metal junk.
I'm pissed off! He did that on purpose.
I refuse to lose to scum like you!
"Act 15: Takumi's Fury!"
Wow, watch out!
Didn't he just hit the guardrail on purpose?
And he used the rebound to reverse-drift!
What's that Eight-Six thinking?!
Are you serious?
The Eight-Six is closing the gap!
That's impossible!
Does he have a death wish?
That Eight-Six driver has lost his cool.
When an average racer
loses his cool, that's the end.
He keeps making mistakes, so he can't go fast.
But this guy is different.
His innate driving sense takes over
and controls the Eight-Six.
The hotter he gets, the faster he goes.
This race is over, Shingo.
Darn...
My EG6 has been running near its limit.
What the heck is going on?!
I'm scared.
I've never felt this scared
in a downhill race before.
He's on my tail!
I can't believe my EG6, the best of its class,
is being overtaken by an Eight-Six!
It's not about the speed anymore,
but something fundamentally different.
That Eight-Six is unreal.
But all I have to do is make
sure he doesn't pass me.
After these hairpin turns, the finish is near.
I'll win this race!
Don't think I'll give you the inside!
No! Is he gonna bump me back?
Oh, no!
I thought he was gonna bump me, but...
...that cornering!
He slipped right through on the inside.
Yeah, Eight-Six!
He passed me...
That's incomprehensible!
I hope Takumi is okay.
Maybe we don't need to
worry about him anymore.
What?
He's come this far,
which means that he has
adapted to the situation.
Who knows? He may be
way ahead of that EG6.
If that's the case,
that Night Kids punk must
be sweating like a pig.
Yeah. Right about now,
he may be regretting
having challenged Takumi.
This death match was my idea...
If I lose, I'll be the laughingstock of the team.
I'll make sure to protect my pride,
even if it means a tie.
This is a short, straight line,
but the B-16A engine can
get me side by side with him.
He can't escape.
How about ending this race...
...with a double crash?!
Here they come! Who is ahead?
The EG6, of course.
The Eight-Six?!
What's wrong with him?!
Was he gonna kill me or what?!
The EG6 isn't coming.
What happened to Shingo?
My EG6...
--Is that Takumi?!
--No!
Did you crash?
You're lucky it wasn't worse.
Are you okay? Injured?
Get in.
I'll give you a ride to the hospital.
It's faster than calling an ambulance.
I can't let you do that much.
Just make a phone call for me.
Don't act so tough. You're hurt.
When we crash, we help each other out.
We're locals, so we know
an emergency hospital.
Thanks. I owe you one.
He's unbelievable.
Who is he, anyway?
Takumi? Takumi!
Are you awake? Come down for a second.
What?
I'm awake. I'm on time.
Just come down a minute.
How do you explain this mess?
You bumped the car, didn't you?
I see three scratches
made by hitting guardrails.
I don't remember...
Maybe it was you.
I didn't drive at all yesterday!
Only you drove it!
Look at these scratches on
the bumper and the fender!
You're right! Who did this, really?!
It's you!
Ouch! What was that for?
--Oh...
--What?
I may remember bumping it a little.
What's wrong with you?
You're still too young to forget things.
I raced against this jerk yesterday
and lost my cool during the race,
and came home all
flustered and just fell asleep.
I don't know how it happened,
but as long as you bump the car,
you're still a beginner.
I wouldn't have bumped it once.
And did you win?
Yeah...
I see.
Are you allowed to do that, Itsuki?
Yeah. The test results showed no problems.
I'll be out soon.
I brought you flowers.
I'll put them in here.
Thank you.
So, I heard, Takumi!
You won the duct tape death match!
Yeah.
Takumi, you're the best,
defeating him with that FR-killer rule!
You're nothing short of a genius!
Itsuki...
...I really wanted to win
that race, no matter what.
He pissed me off, but that's not why.
I just didn't want to lose the race.
I had never felt that way before during a race.
You're becoming more like a real street racer.
A street racer? No, it's not like that.
I'll refine my skills when I get out of here
so that I won't embarrass you
and our Akina "Levin Trueno" team.
What were you talking about?
Um, nothing...
By the way, how is Saori?
I'm worried about her.
She's fine. She says hi.
Cool!
When I get out of here, all four
of us can go for a drive again!
--Sure.
--Yeah.
I'm glad that Itsuki is okay.
Yeah. His Eight-Five should be back soon, too.
I lied about something.
Saori was shaken up so
badly after the accident
that she doesn't want to
think about it ever again.
Hmm...
So she knows that he's a nice person,
but it wouldn't work out between them.
"Practice Guide"
Saori isn't coming to see me...
Darn it!
A street racer doesn't need a girlfriend!
What brought you here tonight?
I was on my way to an ATM
and thought I would stop
by to see your ugly face.
Takumi banged it up pretty good, didn't he?
Of course, with that race, he couldn't help it.
That idiot... but he's heading
in the right direction.
You have a smile on your face
after he messed up your fender?
His style is changing.
He was good before, but there
was something missing.
Lately, he's going faster.
He stepped it up a notch.
How can you tell, Bunta?
When you see this Eight-Six
day in and day out,
you can tell how he's driving.
I guess that makes sense.
I'll stop by on my way back.
Let's have a drink tonight.
Yeah.
Takumi is crazy...
...but his dad's just as crazy.
He hasn't changed a bit.
"Mountain Kamameshi Bowl"
I just can't help it...
Not that I expect anything,
but I can't just pass by...
Um, I'm not a crazy person or anything...
I was just wondering
what's wrong with your car.
I have no idea what's going on in there.
No matter how much I turn the
ignition, the engine won't start.
I can take a look at it, if you don't mind.
I'd appreciate it.
It sounds like something electrical...
Let's see...
S13...
Speed Stars.
Ouch.
--What do you think?
--Well...
My face has never been this close
to a woman other than my mother.
My heart can't take this...
She is so cute!
What a nice smell!
I'm smelling a cute girl
for the first time in my life.
Oh, no! I hope I don't smell like sweat!
Okay, it should start now.
Go ahead and try the ignition.
Good!
Wow, it started! Amazing!
Thank you very much for your help.
You saved me.
No, it was nothing.
That's not true.
I respect guys who are good
with mechanical stuff.
I'd like to thank you later, so...
...can I have your number?
Don't worry about it, really.
Okay...
Oh, no!
This could be the only chance I'll ever get!
I'm such an idiot! An idiot! I'm an idiot!
Excuse me?
Yeah?
Here.
My name is Mako Sato. Call me!
I stood there for thirty minutes
wondering what had just happened.
This isn't a dream!
I happened to run into an angel
under the Kamameshi billboard.
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
You appeared before me
suddenly in the bright light.
And I instantly became a puppet
by your blinding beauty!
What's wrong, Iketani?
I can no longer live without you!
You have become my queen,
my angel, who controls my mind!
He's deep in his own world...
Next on Initial D: "The Angel of Usui."
The angel?! Oh, my Mako!
Don't miss it!