"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Tobidase wicked show, kuuki biribiri saku noise
Shibaite norikonase, abarenbou no party
Zettai hikanai kihaku, the dogfight
Buttoi red zone no himei ni shibiretai
Hakanai senkou, like a ryuusei
Isshun no kagayaki demo kamawanai
Kaimamita kichou na fuukei itsuka kataritai
Sou, ima wa honnou no mama dogfight
Shibiretai yume nara koko ni aru
Kagerou yaburu kaze, backfire
Kinou nado sutetekina,
ima kara rocket dance (Dogfight!)
Sakebenai negai ga itamu nara sugu ni oide
You're big time gambler
Orokasa wa utsukushii kyokusen
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Souon mo everywhere
Yokonaguri, 5G hodo no heavyweight
Giri de soukou, miri no koubou
Za-za-zan!
Rakushou de funde ikeru ze, madamada
I get it now, Nobuhiko.
Sure enough, in a sense this car
could be a monster machine.
Even just taking it out for a
light spin, it got this kind of time.
That's why I said this was about
something extremely simple.
Weight, huh?
Yes. One weapon that no opponent
has yet used is to be lightweight.
On the downhill stage,
being lightweight is the ultimate
weapon that breaks all rules.
If we use that as our counterstrike,
and on a difficult course
specific to the Saitama area...
...we will be able to beat
Project D's Eight-Six...
...with our Cappuccino minicar!
In any case, that's a Ferrari racer for you.
Personally, while I'm not entirely opposed,
I don't much care for taking a car
sideways during corner entry.
That car has a shorter wheelbase,
allowing it to enter spin mode faster.
I told you, didn't I? He's a fanatic.
No matter what kind of car
or how narrow the road,
he'll always take it out sideways.
Doing that, he can pin down a
car's quirks as well as its limits.
He's a lot like Akina's Eight-Six,
that same fanaticism.
I'm really looking forward to this.
The time has finally come to put a stop
to the mighty Eight-Six's consecutive wins.
Come anytime, Project D.
We'll show you the true power of a
united Saitama-Northwest Area team!
"Act 10: The Saitama Area's Ultimate Weapon"
--I'm done.
--Good job.
Ya know,
I've noticed that something
about this car is always different.
And a lot of work's been put
into it in ways ya can't see, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Even the headlights have been
changed out for lighter ones. Somehow.
If taken to this extreme, even a
kid's game stops bein' a game, huh?
Say, Takumi.
I'm givin' ya the Eight-Six.
You're a workin' man now. Sharin' the car
fifty-fifty has gotta be inconvenient.
I guess... But are you being serious?
What, you're not happy?
For myself, yeah. But what will you do?
I've already decided to buy
another car. A used one.
What kind of car?
One that's practical and
easy to drive. I'm gettin' old.
Practical and easy to drive?
That doesn't sound like something he'd say...
You take care of changin' it into your name.
And startin' next year, you pay taxes on it.
--Okay.
--Of course...
That's assumin' the car
is still runnin' next year.
Of course it'll still be running.
Don't say weird stuff like that.
I really like this car. I want
to keep driving it forever.
That's all fine and good. Just make
sure you handle things properly.
The course we'll be scouting
today is supposedly narrow
and intersected by
occasional drainage ditches.
--Ah.
--Well, courses in Saitama prefecture
are apparently the same everywhere.
--Yeah.
--By the way, Keisuke...
This may come across as
needless meddling, but...
What?
I thought she was a pretty
decent lady. That girl. She's cute.
And coming all the way to Akagi...
That was touching, don't you think?
What is it you don't like about her?
Nothing, really.
It's not a matter of like or dislike.
Like I told her, I just want
to concentrate only on D.
I've always thought this, but...
Keisuke, I think your way of thinking
is too focused. Or rather, too linear.
It's like driving techniques, right?
Instead of always just flooring the gas,
being brave enough to
take your foot off the pedal
can sometimes lead to increased speed.
"Reduce Speed"
Still, me trying to tell you
about driving techniques
sounds incredibly pompous, huh?
In any case, you don't have to stoically
push yourself to such extremes, do you?
Dating a girl could probably be a plus.
The truth is, you like that girl, don't you?
With that girl, things wouldn't turn out
like with your last girlfriend, right?
After all, she races too.
That's not the point. You just don't get it.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
A union of the Saitama and Northwest areas?
Yeah. Project D operates so
much like an organization
that we're no match for
them if we act individually.
The only way we can fight them is
through our network of associates, right?
That's why Nobuhiko and the others joined
together to form a temporary team.
Is that so?
And the thing is, they need money,
so everyone's pitching in a little.
Kyoko, can you give some too?
If that's what it takes...
Will 5,000 yen be enough?
Kyoko. Got a minute?
--Are you all right with this?
--With what?
The collection to defeat Project D.
With things coming to this, I'm going to
ask you straight up, whose side are you on?
In terms of feelings.
Whose side?
If you feel kind of on the fence about it,
it's okay if you don't pitch in.
Nobuhiko and the others are
serious about beating Project D.
If you're not in it 100%,
you don't have to participate.
I'm not saying this trying to be mean.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Hey Kyoko, did you know?
The Takahashi brothers of Project D
are the sons of someone
who runs a huge hospital.
Really? I didn't know that.
They're good-looking and have money to boot.
You should think twice about that sort of guy.
So I'm just trash?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
But they're popular with the ladies.
Even if you go chasing after a guy
like that, all you're going to get is hurt.
I'm saying this for your own good.
You should snap out of this, and soon.
No, I can't accept that.
My darling is the only one for me!
Coming along nicely, huh?
Call it against the rules or whatever
you like, but I want to beat Project D...
And this is the only way to do it.
A change of title? For the Eight-Six?
So what's your dad gonna do?
He'll buy something else.
Whoa... Like what?
He didn't say specifically, but he said
it'll be practical and easy to drive,
so maybe an automatic van or a minivan.
Are you serious?! There goes his image.
The man called the "legendary racer of Akina"
driving an automatic van or minivan...
Where's the harm? He is getting old and all.
It'd be nice if he got some old-man
car and just settled down.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Speaking personally.
Well...
I'm going to be late for the
rendezvous, so I'd better get going.
Okay. Break a leg, Takumi!
I'll be going with Iketani and the
others to cheer you on tomorrow!
Say, Fumihiro.
This latest expedition could turn
out to be the greatest challenge
Fujiwara has yet faced.
Fujiwara? But all his races are tough,
one right after the other.
That time he raced the Toudou School,
he went up against a pro racer.
This could turn out to be even more difficult.
Someone more difficult than a pro racer?!
His greatest enemy does not
necessarily have to be the driver.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
You'll understand soon enough.
I'm going to sleep now. Don't wake
me until we reach our destination.
Okay. Understood.
His "greatest challenge"?
Just what is that supposed to mean?
They're here.
Hey! We've been waiting for you. Eagerly.
You remember me, right?
Yes, I remember you.
This time it won't be me you're up against,
but I'm still looking forward to your race.
Huh? You!
Forgive this old foe for coming
back under a new guise,
but this time I'll be
participating from the sidelines.
In any case, we'll open up the course now,
so race it as much as you like.
All right.
See you.
There's a moisture to this wind.
There appears to be a 50% chance of rain.
Can't say I'm too thrilled about the rain.
So long as you etch the details of the course
into memory, there will be no problem.
Concentrate. Your goal is
to make 50 runs by morning.
All right.
Okay.
Standby prep complete. We're good, Keisuke.
Okay, let's go.
She's not here, eh?
I wonder if Project D
has started racing by now.
I want to race right over there,
but I feel discouraged somehow.
I'm like the bat in that
Aesop's fable I read as a kid...
Like I'm the only one without any friends.
I wonder if it'll rain come tomorrow...
Probably. Rain would be welcome.
It would make the perfect
curves for Sakamoto.
The worse that conditions get,
the more effective our weapon,
lightness, will become.
But if the rain gets too bad,
we'll have to cancel the race, right?
I doubt it. All four cars are FRs, which
means they're on equal footing. Also...
These aren't the kind of opponents
who'd run away over something like rain.
We couldn't ask for a more
perfect turn of events.
If there is such a thing as fate, that
which could sway the course of a race...
...then without a doubt,
it has turned in our favor!
Gas it up. Ten liters will do.
Okay.
Keisuke.
Once you're comfortable, race the latter
half of the course with your headlights off,
fog lights only.
If it rains, visibility will worsen.
This will be training to rely
not just on your eyes,
but on your mental image of the course.
A rain strategy, huh? Okay, I'll give it a try.
Sure enough, I worried about my darling...
My darling's FD?
"Keep Out"
I want to touch it!
H-He showed up!
"Protected Forest"
What do you mean I "showed up"?
That would be you!
You scared me! I thought
my heart was gonna stop.
What are you doing out here?
Well, I was taking a nap.
The race is tonight, you know.
Th-That's right. Um, good luck!
I need to sleep for tonight, but...
Once I wake up, I can't go back to sleep.
On top of that, now I'm hungry.
Are you free right now?
Um...
Do you come to places like this often?
"Places like this"?
Casual dining restaurants and stuff.
Yeah. All the time!
It's one of the basics, right? Street
racers go to casual dining restaurants!
Y-Yeah, you're right!
His family may own a big hospital, but he's
like a down-to-earth prince. What a relief!
Huh? Keisuke's not here.
I wonder where he's gone.
Maybe he went to get something to eat.
On foot?
Nothing we can do now.
Shall we go ahead and eat?
Yeah, might as well.
If the weather stays nice, it kinda puts
you in the mood for a little hiking, huh?
--Hey, pass me a tea.
--Here.
Thank you.
--Could you sleep?
--Two or three hours, I think.
It'd be best if you get some
rest after you're done eating.
Even if you don't sleep, closing your eyes
and resting will take away the tiredness.
Okay.
But I want to get in two
or three races if it rains.
I'd like to check which areas collect puddles
and whatnot while it's still daylight.
Yeah...
Sure enough, it looks like
it could rain right now,
even though it hasn't gotten around to it yet.
Do you always sleep in your car
when you're out for Project D?
For the most part, yeah.
But we don't get much rest.
Bucket seats are terrible for sleeping in.
That sounds rough. Why not stay at
a bed-and-breakfast or something?
We race until morning and
then sleep once it gets light.
There aren't any bed-and-breakfasts
that'd give us a room then.
Oh. I guess you're right.
Now that I'm full, I've gotten kinda sleepy.
"Open 24 Hours"
What do you say we head back?
It's started raining.
What should I do? My darling fell asleep!
Poor man. I'll make sure not
to wake him. Slowly, slowly...
I wish time would stop for this moment.
Please God, make time stop for this moment!
Not good. It's really gotten wet.
Nothing for it but to prepare
for the worst and head out, eh?
You can't race in rain like this.
You're crazy, brother,
and so are the rest of you.
Doesn't look like it's gonna let up, does it?
Nope. Looks like it's going to
keep raining like this all night.
There's no way they'd cancel the race, right?
I certainly doubt it.
Let's get ready to head out.
Yessir!
Huh? Oh, no!
I totally fell asleep!
What time is it?
Um... It's 6:00.
I was out for so long. But I've never slept
this soundly on any of our previous races!
Are you all right? We've spent
half the day out here.
I'm sorry. You probably had
things of your own to do.
No, I'm fine! Don't even worry about that!
I didn't have any errands or anything, so...
Thank you.
Okay, I have to go.
This is bad. I still have to
finalize the car's settings!
Thank you!
Ah! Here they come!
A Cappuccino?!
Ryosuke, more and more I've come
to understand what you said...
That this race would be
Fujiwara's greatest challenge.
They got us. They completely
caught us off-guard.
They have someone, too...
Someone with brains.
Here we go!
Starting in five seconds.
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Go!
He's fast! He's so incredibly fast!
Hey sanjou, new generation
Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou
Itsu made wasureta furi o shiteiru no?
(Chigiresou na heart no tension) Mune no uzuki
Sono hitomi no oku, osaekirenai mono
(Sou matowaritsuku kono image) yoru o niramu
Sou dare no kokoro ni te o
nobashite fureru subemo
shiranakatta futari, mou koko kara
(Hey sanjou new generation,
Hora, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Nemutta yume o tatakiokoshite
(Kirisaku you na skill)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
Jidai o furuwasete risky tune
Blast my desire
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
break what you wanna break)