"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
In the silver smoke amidst the frozen city
Payback for a dream I've seen so many times
My body is frozen in a
memory that I can't shake
Slam on the accelerator and deceive myself
Broken in the night
My eyes become sharper
All from someone's whim
It seems like the world will end any minute
Break into the night, it's the time
With scared eyes, I'm lost in the night
Embraced by a falling dream
Scared of being alone, missin' my heart
Even hurting myself
Love me so much,
enough that I could fall apart
If only I could throw everything away
And just love you
Then I know I could face the truth
Takumi, you don't look too sharp.
Are you sure you'll be okay in the rain?
Who knows?
I can't go too fast in the rain,
so I'll drive normally.
Who knows if I'll be fast or slow?
I'll take it easy,
'cause if I crashed, my dad would kill me.
I'll count down!
Five... Four...
Three... Two...
One... Go!
"Act 23: The Rainy Downhill"
The S14 got off to a faster start.
It's not a turbo, but it has a two-liter engine.
It's not just the size of the engine.
He used the clutch well on the wet surface.
No wonder he's confident.
That wasn't the Eight-Six's best start.
He knows he can catch up once he gets going.
He took the lead!
Oh, no! His powerful S14 will widen the gap,
and we'll be left behind!
He's way behind.
This hill is too much for an Eight-Six.
But it's downhill from here to the finish line.
That Eight-Six is known for
his killer downhill technique,
"Sekimon Entrance"
so he'll make a comeback.
Hello?
Hey, big brother.
The Eight-Six and Kenta in the rain?
Yeah.
Kenta is very confident
racing against the Eight-Six,
but I know it won't be that easy.
I agree. Drifting through corners at low speed
is completely different from an actual race.
Yeah. It gets very difficult when
you have to floor the gas pedal.
What tire grip can
compensate for on a dry surface
is severely limited in the rain.
You have to shift the weight properly,
or you'll lose control and crash in no time.
I wonder if those two really understand
the difficulty of a rainy race?
Interesting...
"Those two..."
You liar!
You're only interested in the Eight-Six.
Help! I'm not ready to die!
Darn... it's coming down harder now.
The opponent is from Akagi,
so neither one has the advantage here.
The problem is the rain.
I wonder if he can perform in the rain?
I'm sure he can,
because he makes deliveries every day.
I'm sure he's driven on rainy days.
Of course he has!
Then his technique
should be effective in the rain, too.
I won't let you catch up!
I'll widen the gap.
In the rain, I can even
outrace turbo-charged cars.
He swung his tail!
The S14 is running well in the rain.
It's hard to control an FR in the rain.
Yeah. It only spins to the side, not forward.
It's the Eight-Six!
Unbelievable!
What a drift in the rain!
What was that?
That drift was scary.
I have goose bumps.
Is this the same person
who was lost in a daydream?
He said he would take it easy...
So is this how he normally drives?!
Besides, it's impossible to see in this rain.
How does he do it?
It's so dark that I can't even see the road!
Stop that ringing!
This speed is insane!
He's not human.
He's a monster!
I'm on!
I'm in top form tonight!
I'll put an end to the
Eight-Six's undefeated streak!
It's not Keisuke or Ryosuke,
but me who will defeat him!
What?!
The Eight-Six is on my tail.
How? It can't be!
What's happening?
We haven't gone through
that many downhill corners yet.
This isn't happening!
I got caught so easily...
...going downhill in the rain.
But...
...it's not over yet!
They're only inches apart!
Look! The Eight-Six is cutting in!
The Eight-Six is passing him!
He made it look easy.
Are you kidding?
It was worth waiting in the rain.
Yeah.
I can't keep up!
The gap widens with each corner!
I can't go around the corners as fast.
What could be making the difference?
I thought the rain was on my side!
Right, I see.
Word from the mid-point.
The Eight-Six passed your guy.
I guess he was way out of Kenta's league.
He did well, though.
The Eight-Six is even fast in the rain.
It was obvious even before the race.
The weather plays no part
in defeating the Eight-Six.
It's finally your brother's turn.
--Welcome!
Welcome.
Anyway...
...we now know that he can
race just as well in the rain.
He's becoming more like
a true racer every day.
He willingly took the S14's
challenge last night.
His daydreaming seems to have passed.
I think our operation was a big success.
Yeah.
Anyhow, Itsuki, you were lucky
to be able to experience
that rainy downhill battle.
It was so scary that I
thought I would die for sure!
Besides, he told me to sit in the back instead.
In the back?
--Why?
--No idea.
I don't even think Takumi
knew the reason for it.
I get it.
I think I understand the reason.
Really?
What is it?
It's because...
--Well...
--Well?
Itsuki's annoying.
It must be hard to focus when
Itsuki's screaming next to you.
That makes sense.
That's why!
That's not it at all, you boneheads.
He had Itsuki in the back
because he thought he
could get extra tire traction.
I bet he knew that intuitively.
Thank you very much.
I have no idea how much better he'll get.
Takumi!
Who is she?
Is that...?
--His girlfriend.
--What?!
"Card Club Pricing"
I don't know why I came,
but I just ended up here.
Yeah?
--Is this a bad time?
--No.
He looks obsessed!
This isn't good.
"Card Club Pricing"
I hate to bother you at work, so I'll go.
Yeah.
Trouble!
He may start daydreaming about her again!
Do something, Itsuki.
There aren't any more races for him to see!
There's no time for him to daydream
before the big race next week.
I know that!
Hey, Takumi!
Let's go to Akina for a spin tonight!
It looks dirty.
I guess it's because of last night.
Hello?
Who is this?
It's me. It's been a while, Bunta.
Oh, it's you.
What's the occasion?
Did you crash and get hospitalized?
You wish.
By the way...
...I hear people are talking about your son.
I hear he's good.
What? This Saturday?
Against Ryosuke Takahashi? Who is that?
You don't know him?
Even my people know who he is.
I hear he's the best street racer in Gunma.
My son and he are racing, huh?
Who do you think will win?
Who knows? We'll find out this Saturday.
You haven't changed a bit.
I'm curious about the drift
your son learned from you.
You scarred me for life
with your monstrous drift.
That was years ago.
--Mr. Tsuchiya, we need you.
--Yeah.
Later, Bunta.
I can tell that you've improved a lot, Itsuki.
You really think so?
That means a lot coming from you, Takumi!
I've been practicing the "grip run," you know?
Just for you, here's a
brilliant technique of mine
that resulted from hours of practice.
"Illusionary Hell and Tear!"
This is strange!
I had no problem with it yesterday.
The next corner, then!
"Incredible Braking!"
Hold on, Itsuki!
I can relax now.
I was worried you were
daydreaming about girls again.
Girls? What do you mean by that?!
I wasn't doing that!
But you were acting so weird.
I told you that I was thinking...
...about what would
happen after this big race,
regardless of the outcome.
Don't you get what I'm saying?
No idea.
It's all a riddle to me.
Why do you need anything after the race?
You don't need anything.
You're already fast as it is.
I'm not fast.
Yes, you are!
You have an undefeated streak going.
I don't know.
I just don't know where I'm headed.
Can't you just focus on the big race for now?
You don't have much time left.
Ryosuke Takahashi...
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
It's the moment of truth for your
"fastest racer" theory, Ryosuke.
I'm looking forward to the opportunity.
So, what exactly is your theory?
I'm sure you're familiar with E = mc.
It's Einstein's Theory of Relativity.
I've added my own sub-theories to it.
"E" symbolizes the opponent's
average speed and...
Next on Initial D: "Akagi's White Comet!"
Don't miss it!