"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let's look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let's go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
It's the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let's look for explosive thrills, it's the time!
"Act 11: The Seal is Broken"
Thank you!
Hey, Itsuki!
Itsuki!
Hi, Kenji!
Were you daydreaming, Itsuki?
Well...
He's been like this for a while.
Maybe Takumi's "daydream" bug bit him.
I, uh...
Kazumi, did you get the day off today?
Kazumi?
I'm sorry to bother you at work.
It's okay.
What time do you get off work today?
Huh?
I'm free the rest of the day,
so I thought maybe we could hang out.
I'll wait somewhere until
you're done with work.
Can you hold on a sec?
Wait here for two... one minute!
--Hey!
--Boss!
I'm leaving early for personal reasons!
What the heck?!
Where are you going? Itsuki!
Cover for me, Takumi!
--Hop in, Kazumi!
--Is it really okay?
Yeah, come on!
I guess I'll give him a break just this once.
Who is that girl? His new girlfriend?
Something like that.
What? He just got dumped.
He got another girl already?
What happened to the "Lonely Driver"?!
Are you sure you can leave work like this?
I'm sure.
It's no big deal!
My boss may get mad at me tomorrow...
...but I don't care!
I've been thinking about Kazumi all day.
I wanted to go see her so much.
Knowing she decided to come see me...
...made me so happy!
So leaving work is no big deal.
When I was growing up, I always
hung out with my brother.
Yeah?
You two still seem very close.
After he got into racing,
I'd always go with him to his races.
There was a time when I was using
most of my salary to maintain his car.
Really?
There was nothing I wanted to do.
It was easy to just follow
my car-crazed brother.
But that's no good.
He and I are two different people.
I need to find out what I want to do.
Yeah.
Unfortunately...
...there's nothing I'm
passionate about right now.
But I'll find out what my dream is.
Until now, I haven't had
anyone to talk to like this.
So I'm very glad I met you, Itsuki.
Me, too! I'm very glad I met you, too!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
The power is sealed on purpose.
For what reason?
A racing engine?
I don't know what's going on!
Fine, I'm lacking an essential element.
It's gotten dark.
I'll drive you to the hotel after dinner.
I don't want to go back there.
Oh, so you don't...
What?!
Something happened at work today.
What happened?
I have this mean co-worker
who blames me for her mistakes
and lies to our supervisor about me.
It's unbearable.
All right! I'll stay with you
until you feel better!
For as long as it takes!
There!
--Steer while braking lightly.
--Okay.
You're good at this!
Yeah, it feels good!
You're a better teacher than Takumi.
My brother taught me things
while I sat next to him.
They just stayed in my head.
Really? I bet you'll be good at
this once you get your license.
That's not true.
I'm all talk.
I can't race a mountain pass myself.
You don't have to.
That's just one of the many
pleasures a car brings.
You should get your license.
Driving will open up another world for you.
If you get your license at a driving school,
it may lead you places.
Stepping on the gas
and steering with your own hands,
you can go anywhere you want.
It's a lot of fun.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I absolutely can't lose to you.
We'll settle this shortly.
I probably can't avoid...
...this race.
Are you asleep, Itsuki?
No, I'm not.
I was going to quit my job
and go back to Saitama.
But I'll give it another try.
Quitting is easy,
but I'd just be back where I started.
Hey, Takumi!
Itsuki.
If anyone asks,
I was hanging out with you
from last night until this morning, okay?
What?! You just got back this morning?
Yeah.
Were you with Kazumi?
Why are you blushing?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
We just went to the pass is all!
We slept in my car.
But isn't that improper?
Kazumi is a girl.
But she said she didn't
want to go home last night.
It's a man's job to stay with his girl.
Is it? I don't really know.
I was so happy yesterday.
We talked about lots of things.
It made us closer.
It was like a dream!
Takumi, how about you?
Come to think of it,
Natsuki's been absent lately.
Is she sick?
I don't know.
You don't know? That's weird.
Dad?
I guess he's out.
Hello, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
What?
You're probably wondering
how I got your number.
I remembered the
Fujiwara Tofu Shop emblem...
...on your car.
I'll be coming to Gunma
tomorrow to get my sister.
I heard she took off from work yesterday
and didn't come back until this morning.
So irresponsible!
I can't stand irresponsible people,
even when it's my sister.
Itsuki is in trouble.
But that's my problem. Let's talk business.
I want to race you.
Leave tomorrow night open.
Make sure your engine is
fully operational by then,
or it'll be pointless.
I trust you.
I'll be in touch.
Hey, Takumi.
What's up?
I have a favor to ask.
I may be racing the
Eight-Six Turbo tomorrow night,
so I want to make this engine usable by then.
I need your help installing a tachometer.
A tachometer?
You know car stuff.
I have no clue, so I need help.
Please show me how!
Okay.
I don't know the specifics,
but I can tell that this engine
isn't just another engine.
--Yeah.
--It has a good carburetor
and a wildly twisted header.
It's a new five-valve engine,
and it's really tuned-up.
It sure is hard to believe that this engine
has less power than the old one.
This Wataru guy
said that I would get
more power at a higher rpm.
I want to believe what he said.
Unlocking a sealed high-rev zone...
If that's true, it's exciting.
It's not that hard to install a tachometer,
but there's one thing I'm not so sure about.
Are you sure you want to
change the current setup
without asking your dad first?
My dad wasn't home tonight.
And he wouldn't say yes
if I asked him face to face.
So, I've decided to do it myself.
I want to be able to use the
engine to its full potential
by tomorrow night.
Okay.
In that case, I'll help you.
I'll buy a tachometer
first thing in the morning.
After school,
bring the car here as fast as you can.
Thank you so much, Iketani!
You're a huge help.
You and your Eight-Six
have saved my butt many times,
so this is the least I can do.
What?! It'll take a week?
I need it today.
This is bad! No one has it in stock.
I guess very few cars
use 10,000 rpm tachometers.
What am I going to tell Takumi?
I guess no one carries it.
Boss, do you know anyone?
Well, maybe I do.
Hello?
Hey, Yuichi.
Yeah, I have one.
What?! Are you sure you have one, Masashi?
Bunta asked me to get one for his Eight-Six.
A racing tachometer, and water
temperature and oil pressure gauges.
Hold on.
This is a surprise, Iketani!
I've got goose bumps!
This is what Bunta meant by "sealing it."
Hey, Masashi! Bring those
gauges over here right now!
Hey, Takumi!
What's your hurry?
Mogi!
Hi, Takumi...
Sorry, but I'm busy right now.
But, Takumi!
Takumi...
Mogi...
Okay, now you just have to screw it down.
That's it.
Now it's done.
Wasn't that easy?
Thanks to you guys.
I wouldn't have known how to do it alone.
Installing the tachometer isn't the end of it.
Just because it's a high-rev engine
doesn't mean that it'll rev infinitely.
Without knowing its top rpm,
you can't have a full-blast race.
I'm sure your dad knows.
If you don't know its limit,
you may end up damaging this engine.
My dad.
Isn't that...?
It looks like you're ready.
We'll race tonight as planned.
I'll let you pick the course for our race.
Haven't we seen that Eight-Six Turbo before?
Yeah, and he's Itsuki's girlfriend's brother.
What?! That sounds very complicated.
Okay, that's fine.
I'll see you there.
Later.
Takumi, where are you two racing?
We'll come root for you.
"Matsuya Inn"
Big brother!
This is serious.
I told you not to make our aunt look bad.
You made Mom and Dad worry.
Get your stuff together tonight.
I'm taking you home.
That's my decision to make!
It was wrong to stay out till morning
without letting anyone know.
But I did nothing I'm ashamed of,
so I shouldn't have to go home!
Why don't you explain that
to Mom and Dad instead of me?
If you like it here,
you can tell them so and come back.
I can tell you've changed a little,
and I have to admit
that you've even matured a little.
But they don't know that, so they worry.
They'll feel better if they hear it from you.
Okay, I'll go.
"Takeuchi"
What's going on?
I'm racing tonight.
What?! With who?
Not with Kazumi's brother?
Yeah, and I have a favor to ask.
I'm a little scared, so can you come with me?
Yeah, of course.
Thanks. I'll pick you up later.
What is it?
I'm racing in this car tonight.
It has a new tachometer.
Please tell me what the top rpm is.
Please.
Make sure to rev up to 11,000 rpm.
Don't lose.
Thanks, Dad.
Takumi, why are we taking the highway?
He told me to pick any course I wanted.
So, where did you pick?
Shomaru Pass.
What?! That's his turf!
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
Takumi's new engine vs. Wataru's turbo engine!
The climax!
Next on Initial D: Second Stage...
"Eight-Six vs. Eight-Six: A Spirited Race."
Don't miss it!