"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Fog?!
I can't see anything...
A white void!
Incoming call
which means no oncoming
traffic in the target area.
Nice Kenta. Perfect timing.
Full throttle in these conditions?!
That's impossible for a human.
Cleared the fog, and visibility is back.
I lost.
What a guy.
That was so splendid that for some
reason I smile before feeling the frustration.
If someone can pull that off,
there's nothing you can do.
Your performance is
beyond my imagination.
It's my total defeat, Project D.
Act 8  [ White Demon ]
Keisuke
You did it!
Yeah.
It worked out well, Kenta.
I was scared to death.
The fog was thicker than expected,
and I was so anxious while I was waiting.
When your FD burst
out from that white fog
I was so thrilled that
I had tears in my eyes.
Keisuke came up with the idea of
where and how to make his move.
I gave him some hints, but I
didn't give him any concrete advice.
Is that right?
You've really grown, Keisuke.
Aren't you saying the same
thing after every battle?
That's what I think every time,
so it can't be helped.
It was incredible that you made your
move in the high speed segment.
That segment has an S curve,
so it's not a simple straightaway.
I'm impressed that you
kept the throttle open.
I spent a lot of time on rehearsal, and the
usual blind training must have helped, too.
Still, the fear of not
being able to see is strong.
I couldn't have stepped on the gas unless
I was sure there'd be no oncoming car.
My temples are still throbbing.
I must have really exceeded
the limits of my concentration.
I tired myself out by building up the pace in the fog.
In the end, I didn't have
enough mental strength.
Maybe this is the result of the
difference in our fighting spirit.
I can't accept the result of this battle.
We should request a rematch.
There's no way you'd
lose in normal conditions.
How can you be so sure, Sakamoto?
You might have to race in order to see it.
Sure the road was wet, and the visibility
was the worst thanks to the fog.
The time must have been far
slower than the course record.
But I'm satisfied with the race's quality,
which can't be shown by just the time.
We used everything we had at
unimaginable speed in the fog.
I can't repeat such a miracle
battle even if I'm asked to.
Such moments only come once.
That's why I'm satisfied.
As long as we race on public streets,
the weather can't be an excuse.
This also means the Zero
theory is not perfect yet.
Improvement begins with a realization like that.
I just have to keep improving
myself and my Zero theory.
How could he choose
the lead in this fog?
Ikeda lost because of his strategy.
In the first run, I'll just
put on pressure from behind.
If I'm lucky, my opponent will crash on his own.
Fog is that dangerous.
It's nothing when you drive slowly, but once the pace
picks up, it's like walking on a wire between tall buildings.
In any case, I won't be the lead because
the chaser has a definite advantage.
That was quite a
"meaty" hill climb, wasn't it?
Very interesting.
Yeah, more or less.
Street battles are so deep.
That dramatic scenario could only be
equaled by top category motor sports.
I feel sorry for the gallery of spectators.
Without any info, they don't
know what's going on.
Quite literally, you can't see anything.
What a shame, because the upcoming
downhill will be even more impressive.
They chose to be the chaser.
I see.
Let me give you some
advice on pace management.
Visibility is poor, so go at
80% right after the start.
Once you pick up the rhythm, raise it to 90%
and when you're confident, go full throttle.
I see. How long should
I wait for that timing?
No more than one third of the course.
Finish it off before that.
I'm starting the count down.
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Go!
It's begun.
Is that so?
Okay, I'll tell him.
As you expected, the yellow car won.
Two cars are coming down the hill, and
Hojo said you should pay attention to them.
To be honest
I'm not interested, at all.
Here they come.
I saw wings.
Huh? Wings?
On the white one in the lead.
On the Eight-Six?
It didn't have a wing.
No, I didn't mean that.
I saw
white wings like on birds.
Alright, I can do this.
He's not slow, but not as fast as I thought.
It's only natural because of the fog.
I'm gonna give you a hard time by
putting pressure on you from behind.
I was absolutely right when
I chose to be the chaser.
You told Fujiwara something
before the start, didn't you?
What's your strategy?
It's not exactly a strategy. Fujiwara
can win thanks to these conditions.
Then what did you tell him?
An instruction about not giving too much data to our opponent. My mind is already on the next race.
You mean the final battle against Sidewinder?
Yeah, you could say that.
But before that, I have a battle of my own.
He picked up the pace.
Even though he's not a local, he can
see the course in this poor visibility.
This isn't about technique.
He's got good driving sense.
But he won't be able to
continue this pace for very long.
Even that tough Ikeda lost his concentration.
Keep trying as hard as you like.
You'll make a mistake in the second half.
That's when I'll make my move.
If you ask me, I'd say the result was
obvious even before the race began.
But the opponent's car is so well tuned.
I'm a Silvia owner myself,
so I can tell by just looking.
I think the balance of turning, braking, and
acceleration are better than Fujiwara's Eight-Six.
Normally, he'd be at a disadvantage.
What do you mean by "normally"?
Like driving on a circuit on a sunny day?
If that's the case, vehicle
potential makes a difference.
But in conditions like these,
it's all about the driver.
My brother's blind training was inspired
from Fujiwara's natural cluelessness.
Not just visibility, but as all
the conditions deteriorate
the Fujiwara zone gets refined.
So much so that I hate it.
I keep telling you the same
thing over and over, Kenta.
The most fearsome mountain pass driver is
him.
The way this guy's stomping
on the accelerator is scary.
This speed feels twice or even three
times faster because of the poor visibility.
What kind of nerves does he have?
The next turn is a right hand hairpin.
Is he challenging me to a braking
battle even in visibility as bad as this?
No thanks. Nobody can be sure
whether he'd wreck his car or not.
I don't want to be involved.
Even if I fall behind a little during braking, I should be able to recover my loss during acceleration.
I'm not going with you. Go ahead and
disappear from the course alone.
You went in way too fast!
You won't be able to turn like that!
What the hell?!
Is my sense of speed dull because of the fog?
What's important is not to
panic in a situation like this.
If I accelerate precisely while minimizing
wheel spin, the car will narrow the gap by itself.
My car is tuned to do exactly that.
Even if I don't take a risky gamble, if I keep driving so I
won't lose, victory will end up in my hands regardless.
He's fast. What happened?!
This's ridiculous!
Is that a 4WD?!
It disappeared...
It really disappeared from the course!
Alright!
I knew the conditions were dangerous
because I drove the course myself.
But Okuyama isn't a weak driver
who would be affected by the fog.
After all, he's our team's number two driver.
I knew he'd be able to
finish the race safely.
But at the same time, I was sure he
wouldn't be able to win no matter what.
The reason why I let him
race without any advice
is because I thought he'd gain an experience
he'd never be able to have otherwise.
He must be shocked since everything
he's built has crumbled, but
that will definitely help Okuyama grow.
This frustration will drive
him up to the next level.
Oh man, is this what they mean
by getting bewitched by a fox?
Both Ikeda and Okuyama got defeated while
we're still trying to figure out what happened.
This is a big miscalculation for our recon team.
We couldn't even learn half of what
we wanted because of the fog.
Takahashi Ryosuke seems
to be lucky. I don't like that.
He can bring luck to his side
because he's so well prepared.
You look happy, Hojo.
Of course I am.
This festivity will finally reach the climax.
A stage we could never have even wished
for has been prepared for us after all.
Oh, I've been waiting for you, Takumi!
Looks like you keep winning.
I have tons of things
I want to hear from you.
Spiral's car for the
downhill was an S15, right?
What was the car like? Was it tough?
Well, actually the course was covered in fog,
and the surface was partially wet, so
the car looked quite powerful, but the conditions
didn't allow the driver to step on the gas very hard.
You still race, even in the fog?
It's a street racing rule that we race in any
condition so long as both teams agree to participate.
This time, we were lucky because
our opponent accepted our challenge.
You may be right.
It'd be a pain for you guys to drive all
the way from Gunma for another day.
That's true, but what I really meant was
I didn't want the race to be canceled because
I tend to focus better when the conditions are severe.
Just like I said, right, Senpai?
Yeah.
It rained over here that day.
Kenji and I were worried
about the weather in Hakone.
But Itsuki stated that rain would give you an
advantage. He was confident about that.
Ahem!
Still, it feels like you've really
hit the moment of truth.
You've accomplished something great.
The next one is the final battle.
Even the high level Kanagawa
racers are no match for Project D.
Even though we were afraid of a salary cut,
we still asked the boss for a day off.
Both of us are going to
take a vacation that week.
I'm already so excited!
All of the Speed Stars members
will come watch your race.
I believe we'll witness the birth of a legend.
How is it?
Just like you. Your work is perfect.
I can't feel the benefit of the wing on the streets of Akagi,
but I really wanted stability in high speed corners.
All that's left is how well I can
manage this car after a little hiatus.
Ryosuke, do you really have to do this?
I wouldn't say anything if the
opponent was someone else, but
The next one will be the final away race for Project D.
If something happens to you, we can't redo this.
You shouldn't do this.
This isn't like you, Ryosuke.
Sorry, Matsumoto, but this is a fate I can't avoid.
I can't leave that person as he is.
This is something only I can do.
It's difficult to settle the next battle, but don't worry. I'll return no matter what.
If you insist.
I have one condition.
Huh? Are you joking?
No, it's true, Keisuke.
Someone saw Ryosuke and his FC here.
Plus the FC had a huge wing.
A wing?
That's strange.
Was it really my brother?
He said he saw his face
clearly, so I'm sure of it.
An Akagi street racer wouldn't
mistake anyone else for Ryosuke.
I was thinking that I hadn't seen my
brother's car in the garage from time to time.
If that's true, why does he need a wing?
I have a bad feeling.
Hakone's fog is nice.
It hides the dirty side of reality.
When I stand still like this, there's
nothing other than absolute silence
and overwhelming loneliness.
This is the state of nirvana, right, Kaori?
Ever since I lost you, I feel like
I've been standing in the fog.
I'm going to have a race against
Ryosuke where we both bet our lives.
I'll send one of us to your side.
So make a choice.
This time, follow your heart, Kaori.
Even when night falls, the scenery remains unchanged.
Looking back at the path I've taken.
Sadness, happiness, incurable pains.
Realizing that there are too many to count, as I walk alone.
Countless number of memorable scenes.
We lived through the hustle and bustle.
Sometimes we argued, sometimes we understood.
It wasn't always pretty, but I keep the truth to myself
as I take a new step.
Rosy clouds embellish the city.
I quietly ask about my future.
The sky remains silent.
Only illuminating this path before me.
Feel the translucent scenery.
The setting sun plays a melody.