"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante
Nonkina yatsu ni wa rariaato sankai
Manyuaru doori ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebou ze ho!!
In the midnight dream
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai gurai ni wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no now we go
full speed and funky beat
Kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world e to
Umareta bakari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru toko dake no bashitto!
So many people in this world
Toki ni chuushou toka mo nai wake janai kedo
Tsumannai toko wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa tooshi ikiteru
That's our law!
That was close...
"Act 12: The FR Killer!"
That punk bumped me on purpose!
You're gonna pay!
I wonder if an Akina punk can follow me.
Is he crazy?
Don't insult me!
What incredible speed!
Brake lights?!
Braking while cornering at that speed?!
Darn, I can't keep up.
He's unbelievable...
That EG6 may be faster
than Takumi's Eight-Six...
Who's driving it?
Thank you very much!
I was really furious!
So, he was braking while
cornering... at high speed?
I don't think I've ever seen anything like it.
Really?
Everybody does that!
I step on the brake while
cornering all the time.
Uh-oh, I'm going too fast...
I'm scared... step, step...
We're not talking about a beginner...
This EG6 cleared those downhill
turns at an incredible speed.
EG6?
It's a Honda Civic!
Why don't they just call it a Civic, then?
The Civic is very popular among street racers,
even though it's an FF.
It's a non-turbo 1.6 liter like your Eight-Six,
but its VTEC engine has tons of power.
It has been a rival of the Levin
and the Trueno for years.
As an Eight-Six driver,
you should know about the Civic.
As a Levin driver myself...
...I can't let a Civic pass me!
Anyway, I just can't believe
it went in at that speed
and then braked.
Well, that technique is called left foot braking.
Left foot braking?
You usually don't use
this technique with an FR,
but you brake with the left foot
to stabilize the car at
an extremely high speed.
With an FF like an EG6,
you need your right foot on
the gas pedal continuously
to avoid understeering,
so you brake with your left foot
to take the weight off the rear
tires and turn more sharply.
He must be a highly experienced
FF driver to use that technique.
I'm sure he's fast.
He was pretty fast... That punk...
I only avoided crashing
because I'd just practiced
spinning with the emergency brake.
Otherwise, my S13 would've
been in the shop again!
I'm gonna make that EG6 pay!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
I'm home...
Hey, someone called for you earlier.
--Who was it?
--I didn't ask.
A girl... A pretty girl.
She said she would call back.
How could you tell she was
pretty over the phone?
I've developed good intuition over the years.
Cars and women... it's all about
experience and intuition.
--Good luck with both of them.
--Yeah, yeah...
Well, I'm off to a meeting...
Uh... Fujiwara Tofu Shop...
--Hello, Takumi?
--Oh... Mogi...
Were you sleeping?
Remember the other day you were saying...?
This better be real, Takumi!
If this turns out to be a joke... you'll be sorry!
Are you sure she's bringing her friend?
Don't worry...
Mogi said she was bringing her friend.
I wonder if she's cute... or has a nice body...
...or maybe she is beautiful!
I think she is Mogi's junior high school friend.
As long as she is decent-looking...
I shouldn't expect too much...
I can't believe you kept your promise, Takumi!
I'm so lucky to have a good friend like you...
It's nothing, really...
I'll be the best racer at Mount Akina
with a pretty girl in my arms.
Not on my Levin, you darn pigeons!
They should be here by now...
Hey!
Were you waiting long?
--Don't do that, Mogi!
--Hi.
Itsuki, this is my friend Saori.
Saori, this is Takumi and Itsuki.
Nice meeting you.
You, too.
She's... very pretty...
So you are a street racer?
Well, I belong to a team
called the Akina Speed Stars,
and I'm the third or fourth fastest...
I'm well known in Gunma
as "Levin of Mount Akina."
Pretty cool!
What's a street racer?
What, you really don't know?
A street racer is a...
Oh, man! She's far beyond my expectations!
Watch out, Itsuki!
--Want me to drive?
--No, I got it.
Sorry, a street racer's bad habit...
Feeling okay?
I'm fine...
He drives kind of rough...
Hey! Takumi and Natsuki!
Look at us!
Why don't you join us?
They do look good together.
Yeah...
Need a ride home?
Thank you, but Saori and I
have a lot to catch up on.
I had a good time, Itsuki.
Maybe we'll do it again.
--See ya.
--Yeah.
Uh, Saori...
See ya, Saori!!
Yeah!
Not bad... she's not bad at all...
Saori.
I feel life energy surging through me...
Saori!
Watch the road, will you?
Don't worry!
I don't know how to thank you, Takumi.
Yippee!
"Maybe we'll do it again," she said...
Maybe just the two of us next time...
--Hey, light!
--Wha...?
Sorry... I'm sorry...
Thank you very much!
Well, what should I do next?
Work, work, work...
He's in a good mood. Did he meet a girl?
--Maybe...
--He can't have a girlfriend before I do!
By the way, Takumi,
would you like to drive my S13?
It's refreshing to drive
different cars sometimes.
No, thank you.
I'll pass. I mean... you love that car...
Please, Takumi?
I can learn so much from watching you drive it.
Please?
Are you serious about racing
against the Eight-Six of Mount Akina?
You'll see.
All right, let's go.
Come on out, Eight-Six of Mount Akina.
I can hardly wait...
Do I really have to?
Please, Takumi.
Just drive normally...
It'll still be educational for me.
I'll owe you big!
I'm not really good with
other people's cars, so...
I don't think I'll be any help...
He's begging this much, so just this once?
Yeah, Takumi. Just this once.
Okay, just this once, then.
Please don't expect too much.
You will?
Yeah!
All right, Iketani. Just don't faint again...
Don't worry, this is my second time around...
Bring it on, Takumi!
--Here we go, then.
--Yeah!
What should I do first?
Well, how about showing me a braking drift?
Okay.
Wha... hey...
Are you doing it at the first turn?
Aren't we going in a little too fast...?
I hope Iketani's all right.
It's...
"Iketani Passes Out!"
"Wow! I... I saw it!
The agonized cry of his last
moment echoed through Mt. Akina!
The scary downhill!
Iketani, in the third corner...
...passed out!"
...all over again, perhaps.
He can drift effortlessly in a
car he's never driven before...
I never knew my S13 could go this fast!
It's different from my Eight-Six,
but I think I'm getting the hang of it.
But we only went through three turns...
I'm ready for a drift.
A drift? Then what was he doing before?
I think I got it right on that last turn.
It's too advanced for me to understand...
They're back!
Oh, man. You made it this time.
You've conquered it!
So, did you get a good look
at his braking drift, Iketani?
Not really... no idea...
So much for begging him to show you how.
Yeah, but he made it look
so simple that I realized...
...I'm not even close to
understanding his technique!
I feel like a better racer already!
Wha...?
That's the EG6 from yesterday!
That punk!
Hey, you!
I know you're the one who
hit me from behind yesterday.
Who are you?
Don't tell me you forgot this S13!
Oh, you...
That's right! You owe me an apology.
I could've gotten badly hurt.
Are you kidding me? That was your fault.
What?
Your car was going so slow
that I couldn't anticipate it.
I never thought you could
attack a corner that slowly.
I tried to brake, but... bump.
What did you say?!
Calm down, Iketani!
What a jerk!
Stepping all over Iketani's pride...
If you insist, then we'll race under my rules.
If I lose, I'll be on the ground
begging for your forgiveness.
What do you mean, "your" rules?
It's nothing.
We call it the "duct tape death match."
Duct tape death match?
Duct tape the right hand
to the steering wheel...
...and then race. That's all.
Duct tape the right hand
to the steering wheel?
Your shifting hand stays free...
My right hand and the steering wheel...
You can't switch hands...
You can't steer!
Too dangerous...
For you, definitely.
I hear the Speed Stars' Eight-Six
is a downhill specialist.
Maybe this kid can help you out?
Tell this Eight-Six kid
that I'll be waiting here
next Saturday at 10 p.m.
We'll have a duct tape death match...
I'll see you then.
My pride says you gotta be wild and tough
Sou tanin wa kaizai shinai
Never stop, tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peak mezashite, sweep the winding street
Beep beep! Keikokuon wa so cheap!
Sheep-tachi wa michi wo akero
'Cuz I'm never gonna stop, streak my dream
Easy na motivation subete wa simulation
Nigetemitatte doko demo safety zone
Nani ka wo te ni irete nani ka wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout, dare no te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream, yami o harisaite iku
Like a streak to the peak
Sekaijuu no kogekitta yoru o keshiteku
Rage your dream, michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding down, another round never slow down
Konma zero-ichibyou de knockdown
Yoin nokoshikietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haishachi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nougakitachi
Jamakusai kara shikato shitekou
Streaker satte yuku street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream, tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream, ima o ikiteiru
Love fortune: This week your relationship
will develop further.
Did something good happen, Itsuki?
I'm going to have a girlfriend!
Really? Congratulations!
Who is the lucky girl?
--The girl from the double date.
--Saori?!
Wait, the fortune also tells
you not to push too hard,
or you'll find yourself in trouble.
Next on Initial D, "First Date!"
Don't miss it!