"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
Keisuke.
This race must be handled
with the utmost precision.
Okay? I need you to listen closely.
This is advice I have not often given...
You're going first?
Yeah. Unlike Jo here,
I'm not the type to lovingly
observe his opponent.
I'm going for victory in the first race.
My car's a bit heavy, so I don't
want to go drawing things out.
We'll settle this nice and fast.
Do as you like. But Ko,
at the risk of repeating myself,
you have to control your bad
habit of slacking off mid-race.
I don't think we'll lose,
but these opponents don't seem
like they'll be easily beaten.
Worrying too much is bad for your stomach.
Leave this to me. I feel it
all too well... Their aura.
"Steep Curve"
This looks like it'll be hard.
I don't know how well I can do,
but I'll just try it and see.
The way you are now, you should be fine.
According to your simulations,
what's the margin limit I can concede
to him up till the turning point?
Indeed...
About seven seconds.
Seven seconds, huh?
Too much or too little and you will lose.
Don't forget that, Keisuke.
Yeah.
All right, shall we get started?!
"Act 20: The Unmatched GT-R!"
Beginning the countdown!
Starting in five seconds!
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Go!
It's underway, eh? With Ko racing,
I'm sure there's no need to worry.
He always comes through when it's needed.
Still, he can't let his guard down!
No slacking off. Just flee from
your opponent with all you've got!
It looks like it's started.
Yes...
His opponent is the God Foot,
the man they say has a superhuman
mastery of accelerator handling,
Kozo Hoshino.
I assume Keisuke is feeling
some pretty intense pressure.
At any rate, this is no ordinary opponent.
I've been unnerved since the
moment we first met him yesterday.
We have an opponent of our own
to deal with: the God Arm.
Let's give it our all and race
so that we have no regrets.
Three... Two... One.
Hyaaa!
Well, well! For such a big-ass body,
you sure are showing me
some nimble movement.
Yeah, yeah! This is feelin' great! Go!
It looks like it's already started, eh?
Huh? They're doing the uphill first today?
No, that's not it.
They're doing a combined stage,
uphill and downhill.
A combined stage?
Yeah. One race, both hillclimb and downhill.
They'll repeat that until the winner's decided.
Speaking of Kozo Hoshino,
my most lasting impression of him
is from when he was still driving an R32.
I was at a going-away party,
and Hoshino was at the last
corner of the Tsukuba circuit.
I saw him drift the entire thing,
from entry to exit.
I can still see it, like it's
burned onto my retinas.
The GTR's ATTESA E-TS
4WD system is a bit unusual
and as a rule doesn't allow for drifting.
That's because if the E-TS detects tailslide,
it simultaneously initiates front-wheel drive.
Is that so? I don't know that much about 4WD.
In other words, even if you reduce
countersteer and step fully on the gas,
you can't maintain the slide angle
like in a normal rear-wheel drive.
Front-side traction is increased,
and the car cancels out the drift.
Also, because ATTESA E-TS
is designed to assign torque
to the front wheels automatically
according to acceleration,
the more intricate your accelerator handling,
the more difficult it becomes to sustain drift.
But you said his GT-R was drifting, right?
Drifting flawlessly.
Even Mr. Toudou was shocked by it.
He said he had no explanation
for that kind of technique.
Huh? Mr. Toudou said that?
Unthinkable, is it?
Still, to Hoshino it was probably
a little game, just him showing off.
I wonder if that's why Mr. Toudou
said we should come watch this race.
Yeah. No doubt about it, Hoshino
has godlike mastery of pedal work.
That's why they call him the God Foot.
By the way, Mr. Toudou
also said something else...
That we should watch how Project D
faces the giant wall before them.
What kind of race will this turn out to be?
I can't wait to find out.
In the GT-R line alone,
I've gone through R32, 33 and 34...
Four cars already. The R32 had such
an impact on me when it debuted!
But when the bigger R33 came out,
talk about a disappointment.
That one pretty much sucked! One, two...
Hyaa!
I got rid of that R33 right quick
and bought another R32...
...meaning that my fourth car
was this, the R34 GT-R!
All right.
He's keepin' up with me, eh? Well done.
He's so damn fast!
I was full of confidence after having
upped my car's racing capabilities...
But I was naive.
Sure enough, when it comes to
traction, the GT-R is a monster!
When you ride in Mr. Hoshino's
passenger seat, things sure get lively!
Yeah. For him, there's no
such thing as driving quietly.
Sometimes, he does these
"Hyaa!" or "Hngrar!" sorts of yells.
Yeah, yeah! That sure is surprising, huh?
I guess talking like that is
how Mr. Hoshino concentrates.
Muttering to himself and
going into his own world...
We regular guys could never
duplicate something like that.
Yeah. If you're trying to concentrate,
staying quiet is the normal way to do it.
That's exactly it.
When people are absorbed in something,
normally they don't engage in idle chatter.
But I know the real reason...
Hngrar!
Hyaa!
Ko talks so that he doesn't
concentrate too much.
He's the type of guy who gets
more fired up than anyone!
Put simply, it's a cooling
system for his emotions.
This is the method he thought of so that
he wouldn't lose his cool or his objectivity.
I doubt it'll happen, but on
the off chance he stops talking...
...then like a drag machine with
its nitrous system engaged,
he will race wild and unchecked!
Hyaaa!
That's the one thing I want to avoid.
Be sure to play this smart!
According to our age.
Certainly is muggy tonight, isn't it?
Oh, if you'd care for one of these...
--Here.
--Thank you.
Are you all right? You're really sweating.
I guess I'm the age where heat hits you most.
This R34 really is a great car!
It even addresses the R32's one
weak point, stubborn understeer.
It brakes well and it turns well.
There's no other car that's this fun!
If someone's got a bit of money
and doesn't know anything about cars,
he'll drive a Benz or a Ferrari or some crap.
I've got money, but I couldn't care
less about those sorts of cars!
Till the day I die...
...give me a GT-R!
Hraa!
Graa!
"Touge Tunnel Project
To be implemented soon"
Still, you've never given Keisuke advice
the way that you did this time, have you?
Up till now, you've mostly let him act freely.
That should be enough to tell you
our opponent this time is special.
I know that, but...
Under these rules, managing tire performance
during the hillclimb will be key.
Relying on traction against
an opponent in a 4WD GT-R
would likely cause rapid tire deterioration.
But Keisuke has made dramatic progress
in his accelerator handling recently.
That is my point. No matter how
much progress Keisuke has made,
that skill will be of no use
against tonight's opponent.
The man they call God Foot, eh?
That's why I had him restrain
himself for the hillclimb
to wager the race on the downhill.
Yes, I understand that, but still...
...isn't seven seconds a bit too dangerous?
When I heard that off to the side,
I shivered in spite of myself.
I would say the odds of winning
hinge upon seven seconds.
What happens during those
seven seconds is most important.
I am asking of Keisuke a race far
more difficult than any he has yet run.
It is a tactic that acknowledges his
progress in accelerator handling...
And he probably understands my true intent.
I can't believe you'd tell me
something like that, brother.
Can we really take on a guy as fast as this
and give him a margin of seven seconds?
If I can't get that time back during
the downhill, it's game over!
Keeping a margin may be hard, but in
terms of execution, anyone can do it!
Still, my brother wouldn't bother saying
something that could be done that easily.
The problem is...
what those seven seconds hold!
Not yet! No, not yet!
My brother's probably asking
something incredibly difficult of me.
I have to focus my body and spirit...
...and concentrate on the
movement of my right foot.
Hyaa!
--Yeah!
--Awesome! That's Hoshino for you!
He's slowly started to pull ahead of the FD!
Jeez, I guess even Project D's
hillclimb ace is no big deal.
Idiot, Hoshino is just too awesome.
There's no way an FD should be able to
keep up with an R34 on a course like this.
At this rate, Purple Shadow will win
both the hillclimb and the downhill!
So that's your strategy, huh?
That's pretty clever of you.
But you're still young...
If you ask me, there's no need
for you to be that clever just yet.
At his age, I was more of an idiot,
always on the offensive.
Well, it's because of that I've been
able to come this far without losing.
One, two!
Project D's FD is slowly being left behind.
How does this look to you, Sakai?
Will it all be over in the first race?
Not at all. It looks like this hillclimb
is using some nonstandard rules.
Nonstandard rules?
The GT-R with its great traction
will have the uphill advantage,
but on the downhill, the lightweight FD
could have the upper hand.
So he might hold back on the hillclimb,
not placing wear on his tires
until the downhill, which he'll bet the race on.
I get it.
Wait, so that means Project D is the one
that's actively trying to lay a trap?
But it's a big gamble, all or nothing.
Trying this tactic on Kozo Hoshino
of all people will take some courage.
If he doesn't follow as predicted
on the downhill, it's all over.
Yeah.
It's friggin' incredible how he
planned this... Ryosuke Takahashi.
The turnaround to the downhill
will be something to watch.
Kozo Hoshino and Keisuke Takahashi
will engage in an all-out downhill race!
They're both probably well aware...
of where the importance of this race lies.
Just thinking about it is making me tingle.
I'm prepared for the worst.
All I can do is have my right foot
do the best possible job it can!
If my brother says I can keep up
with him, I'll show them that I can!
It won't be long.
We've got word from down below. It looks
like Keisuke is slowly being left behind.
Oh. Well, the GT-R has the
advantage on the hillclimb.
This is probably a terrible feeling for Keisuke.
I'm sure he hasn't experienced this before.
His opponent's car, disappearing without
a trace from his FD's windshield...
Doing your best to control the frustration
at having your opponent disappear
while focusing all your concentration on the
tires' contact with the road is no easy task.
You said it...
It's all right! Keisuke can do it!
I have to concentrate...
Must keep horizontal gravity generated
from corner entry to exit steady.
I have to control the tires' load!
At the corner exit, I'll open it up
full-throttle and make a dash for it!
Keisuke fought his way through
races in the Saitama area
with the aim of improving
his accelerator handling.
As a result, he has seen vast improvement
in his management of tire performance.
The rapidity with which he has absorbed
these techniques has surprised even me.
That is what makes Keisuke Takahashi
an extraordinary driver.
If this race becomes protracted,
the results of that experience should manifest.
There they are!
Yo, there they are!
It's Hoshino's GT-R!
He's running all by himself!
This isn't a race at all!
Hyaa!
Hngraa!
--Awesome!
--So cool!
Don't go lookin' down on my R34!
Go, Keisuke!
Hello? Kenta? How many seconds was it?
Understood. Thanks.
Lag time at the turnaround
point was six seconds.
I see.
Well done, I suppose.
He no doubt held back against
an opponent he couldn't see.
Because now the real gamble begins.
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte