"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
Starting in five seconds.
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Go!
He's fast! He's so incredibly fast!
What do you think they're up to?
The Cappuccino is a minicar.
You think they're just screwing
with us, bringing out a car like that?
Dude, you're clueless, aren't you?
Last year, when the Eight-Six
of Akina made its debut,
all the racers in the Gunma area thought
the same thing when they saw Fujiwara...
Because an Eight-Six is
an old car and lacks power.
But in the end, all of them lost.
Even the Night Kids and we Red Suns.
They've made use of that same advantage.
"Act 11: Rainy Downhill Battle"
Just what hat did you pull that rabbit out of?
When you put it like that, it sounds as
if you realize just how dangerous it is.
I guess.
Not that I should be telling
this to you, the enemy, but...
Even if we beat the Eight-Six using that car,
it'll only make me halfway happy.
To be honest, being able to defeat the
Eight-Six like this, in a place like this...
It's a little painful.
Don't automatically assume he'll lose.
We won't know how it'll turn out until it's over.
No, I know. Sadly, this time
there's no way he can win.
I told you not to assume that, didn't I?
If you look at just car vs. car, the chances
of the Eight-Six winning do look slim. But...
...what's driving that car is a
flesh-and-blood human being.
And in a contest between driver and driver,
there's no telling what will happen.
Are you trying to say our driver's no good?
Sakamoto's skills are solid.
He won't make any slipups.
That's not what I mean.
You don't understand...
...just how incredible he is.
It's not logic. If you were on the
same team as us, you'd understand.
There's genius in this world that can
break the boundaries of convention.
It stings, but I know that it's true.
Anyway, you just watch.
Rain is a drag, huh? It makes
you slip, gets you all wet...
You're one to talk. Takumi's the one who
has it tough, having to race in this rain.
That's right. Doing a downhill
in the rain is kinda scary.
Both of you, Iketani and Kenji?!
Takumi can handle the rain just fine!
Have you forgotten?
That race in the rain at Myogi?!
Yeah, that's true...
What's more, I've experienced
Takumi's godlike skills firsthand!
Takumi losing a race in
the rain just isn't possible!
Which will you choose, leading or following?
When it's raining, going first and having
to set the pace causes added pressure...
Even so, I'd prefer to lead.
We Ferrari racers don't specialize in following,
and I don't want to draw the race out.
If possible, I'd like to end this in the first lap.
Understood. I'm of the same
opinion. We'll choose to lead.
Fujiwara...
I think you'll understand once the race begins,
but that car will be shockingly fast.
You will probably fall behind at corners
and have to catch up on the straightaways.
This will be completely unlike
any race you have yet fought.
Here is my advice...
Try to remember the
hardest race you have run.
Recall the technique used on you
that you found most disagreeable,
for today, you will perform that technique.
To give you a hint...
For example, the methods of
Kyoichi Sudou of Team Emperor.
Something like that would be effective.
Don't forget, having a
completely different mindset
will be the key to winning this battle.
Ryosuke, the way you give Fujiwara advice
is slightly different from before, isn't it?
--It is?
--It's changed.
How can I put this? It used
to be simpler, more concrete.
And concise, a "Do this like this" sort of thing.
But today's was a little difficult, or rather...
It made Fujiwara think for himself
and make his own choice.
That's the kind of advice it's become.
It's an indicator of how much
Fujiwara has improved. Matsumoto...
I seek to provide Keisuke and Fujiwara
with tasks during their D battles.
I had sort of a vague feeling.
I wondered if that was the case.
It's thanks to those tasks that Fujiwara
has been able to advance as much as he as
in such a short period of time.
But this time, I may have gone a little too far.
Considering his opponent, not
everything will go according to plan.
The hurdle I've placed before
Fujiwara may have been too high.
I don't get it. This has never
happened before, not once.
It's hard to do this. Really hard!
What should I do?!
Not being able to take a corner at the
same speed as the car in front of me...
That's the first time this has ever happened!
I still don't really understand...
How much does the Eight-Six weigh?
Nine-fifty... nine-sixty or so, I think.
That's right. It's less than a ton.
But the Cappuccino weighs even less
than that, probably 700-plus kilograms.
That's a difference of 250 kilograms.
You know that the difficulty in controlling
a car is relative to its weight, yes?
You're shackled by the car's inertial mass.
So that 250-kilogram difference
gives the Cappuccino the advantage?
No amount of tuning can beat light weight.
Then this race is...
I'm telling you, don't assume
the outcome before it's happened!
Our guy can't be measured
by normal standards.
In the friction ratio for the contact
sur face between the road and tires,
a lower MU value will greatly affect whether
one under- or overshoots when cornering.
It'd be fine if the car were to
consistently remain neutral,
but that sort of car doesn't exist.
In that case!
Rather than understeer,
which can't be controlled,
one should seek from the start
to create controllable oversteer.
That's how I do things!
In the tough-road world of Ferrari racing,
four-wheel drift is fundamental!
Still, he's done a good job keeping up.
Even when it looks like I
can shake him off, I can't.
Rain takes getting used to.
To be honest, it's scary even for me.
Nobody knows exactly how best
to merge to safely avoid crashing.
That guy knows it's more dangerous
for him, yet he keeps coming after me.
You can keep walking that
razor's edge till the very end!
For this race...
...it was only the day before yesterday
that I received specific information
regarding what tactics
our opponents would use.
To be honest, I thought
perhaps we'd be in trouble.
This mistake is on me.
Mistake? Even you make mistakes?
Frequently. I bluff my way through it,
but inside I'm on pins and needles.
However...
This time, luck is on my side.
An uncertainty that no one could have
calculated may cancel out my mistake.
An uncertainty?
I don't understand it...
The meaning of Ryosuke's advice.
The "methods"of Kyoichi of Team
Emperor? What were they again?
Ryosuke said to catch up on the
straightaways, but that's impossible.
What do I do?!
There's no way to beat an opponent
you can't even catch up to!
The uncertainty was this rain.
So you think the rain will give
Fujiwara the advantage?
But that goes against popular theory.
Rain reduces the MU of the road's surface,
and if the tires' grip weakens uncontrollably,
a major handicap will become even greater.
I think that would be the standard conclusion.
You're overlooking something.
That theory holds true for a midday
race at someplace like a circuit...
...but nighttime on a rainy
mountain pass is a different story.
In conditions such as those, the emphasis
shifts from the car to the driver.
Also, the X factor, or ability beyond that of
mere driving techniques, is called into play.
X factor?
Therein lies our chance.
This rain will change the hurdle I
thought too high to just the right height
and is the uncertainty of which I spoke.
Perhaps this rain is a blessing, made to fall
by the powerful luck that Fujiwara possesses.
I can close the gap a bit on the
latter half of the straightaways.
Does that mean that at least on extended
straightaways, I have the advantage?
This really is a first. Winning in
power but losing at cornering...
It's sort of pitiful. This is stressing me out.
To think, having no choice but to battle it
out on a mountain downhill straightaway!
The way he moves so effortlessly...
I'm getting more and more pissed off!
Whatever it takes, I wanna catch
up and put the pressure on him!
Oh! Kyoichi's "methods"...
Maybe he meant that!
Unreal! Cappuccinos are that fast?!
The Eight-Six is undefeated, but...
Project D's ace downhill racer can't catch up?!
He meant Kyoichi's specialty
technique, no doubt about it.
I'm going to have to close the gap to pull it off.
Just watch, I'll friggin' catch up to you!
Okay, understood. Thank you.
They've just passed the road cut hairpin.
There's a 10-15 meter gap between them.
I don't understand it.
The Eight-Six being able to keep up with
the Cappuccino this far is most unusual.
In my simulations,
this event was an impossibility.
Was the rain not to our advantage after all?
If the race cannot be settled at the
decisive, steeply inclined section,
the gently inclined, mid- to high-speed
section in the latter half shall be worrisome.
I miscalculated.
The capabilities of the Eight-Six's
driver cannot be calculated.
They've upset what was thought
to be a 100% probability of victory.
I get it. The Eight-Six's
whole body is telling me.
The slight sensation of the tires slipping as
they grip wet asphalt... It's almost palpable!
I feel like with this car, I can even know
how much rain is flowing on the asphalt.
I can definitely catch up to him!
I'll have one chance, two at the most,
to set up a counterattack.
There's one thing that's got me anxious.
The first thing that comes to mind about
Sudou from Team Emperor is a counterattack.
Indeed.
I'm worried what sort of judgment Fujiwara
will make with his mind so confused...
...because a counterattack would be a mistake.
Exactly. True to form, you understand.
A counterattack is 100% doomed to failure.
He's gaining on me!
Wataru's Eight-Six couldn't
keep up with this car.
I don't get it! How can he
be this fast in the rain?!
Even I am struggling, searching for grip
on front tires that can't be relied upon.
I can't do any more than this!
It's scaring even me!
This isn't logic... It's instinct.
Rain sure is terrible...
Even an F1 racer with godlike
technique would spin out in the rain
and fly right out of the course.
That's how difficult rain is.
How it falls can change each
and every racing condition,
and there's no telling when it'll stop.
One mistake on this
narrow road, and it's boom.
Even so, you have to pull yourself together
and go on the offensive, or you'll lose.
It's a continuous battle between fear and
motivation. Especially on the downhill.
It takes ten times more out
of you than a normal race.
Dammit! What the hell are you?!
I feel sick. He keeps gaining on me...
What does this mean?!
I think this was how it played out...
The race against Kyoichi at Iroha Slope.
When your opponent has
better cornering speed,
you have to abandon the corner attack.
Slow down, quickly change the car's direction,
then speed up the acceleration timing!
I have to spend just a little
more time stepping on the gas.
There's something I just can't accept.
This "Shame and reputation be damned,
I came to win!" attitude really ticks me off.
Because on the downhill,
being light is an incredible weapon.
But I couldn't stand losing to these guys!
If we friggin' lose, I'm kicking Fujiwara's ass.
That's just like you, Keisuke...
Anyway, there's no mistaking
we're in a tight situation.
My only hope is that there's some
reason Ryosuke wished for this rain.
If we can at least make it to
the midpoint, there may be hope.
If Fujiwara makes it to the bottom,
the roads aren't too steep
and there are long, straight lines.
--Ironic, isn't it?
--You said it.
The downward slope has been
the only thing in his favor
as Fujiwara has gone up against
some powerful enemies, but this time...
...far from being his friend, that slope
will put him through the wringer.
Does this guy not feel fear?!
Up this close, the shower of water
droplets obstructs your headlights.
I hate that, which was the main
reason I chose to race in front!
Driving in the night rain is bad enough,
but with the spray of water I'm sending up
his field of vision should be
hopelessly obstructed, and yet...!
He's right up on me!
Why?! He should be completely
unable to see from that side ditch,
so how can he keep up with me so precisely?!
You son of a bitch, you're not human!
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie