"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Get ready, yo! Now we blow up the horn
In the silver smoke amidst the frozen city
Payback for a dream I've seen so many times
My body is frozen in a
memory that I can't shake
Slam on the accelerator and deceive myself
Broken in the night
My eyes become sharper
All from someone's whim
It seems like the world will end any minute
Break into the night, it's the time
With scared eyes, I'm lost in the night
Embraced by a falling dream
Scared of being alone, missin' my heart
Even hurting myself
Love me so much,
enough that I could fall apart
If only I could throw everything away
And just love you
Then I know I could face the truth
Vroom!
And at the corner I went...
Voosh!
...as I cleared it.
At that moment, I was like the wind.
Nothing beats the pass.
When you have your own cars, go check it out.
My car? It's an Eight-Five,
every racer's dream car!
You probably didn't know that.
"Act 21: Challenge from a Superstar"
This summer was very memorable.
--Why?
--"Why?"
Because I bought a car,
and you debuted in the
racing world like a comet.
Don't tease me like that.
One, two, three, four...
What are you counting?
Four is the number of
races you won this summer.
First, Keisuke Takahashi of the Red Suns' FD.
Second, Nakazato of the Night Kids' R32.
Third, the duct tape death match
with Shingo Shoji's EG6.
Finally, Mako and Sayuki's
Sileighty at Usui Pass.
Four for four.
Your undefeated legend began this summer.
You're no longer just a dummy.
Stop exaggerating.
Don't be embarrassed!
Keep winning, Takumi!
Until I beat you,
and become the fastest in Gunma--
no, in all of Kanto!
They'll be calling me... "Itsuki, Akina's Comet"!
Huh?
Since school ends early today,
let's go do something in the afternoon.
I kind of have to work in the afternoon.
What? You do?
I want to ride in your car again...
...because it's very cute.
If you say so... but it's my dad's car.
You said you wanted to buy a car.
Are you saving up?
I save most of what I make,
but I'm still far from it.
How much do you need?
Around a million yen.
A million...
How much do you have now?
Not even close.
Takumi?
What would you do if I gave you the money?
I wonder...
I bet you'd thank me,
and treat me like a princess.
You'd owe me big,
so you'd have to quit working
and take care of me and love me every day!
--I'm so embarrassed!
--Quit kidding around.
That's too much money
for us to come up with.
I know that!
I was just wondering.
You have no imagination.
That's too far off to imagine.
We now know that Takumi's
technique is the real deal
and will hold up anywhere.
It's more than just technique.
--Thank you very much.
--You need natural talent
to be able to race well on a new course.
He's a genius because he
defeated all those modern cars
with his ten-year-old Eight-Six.
--How gratifying!
--Get a load of you!
You're the one who said he
couldn't compete anywhere else
because he only knew Akina.
I know I did, but...
We all thought that.
Takumi is abnormal.
When I heard the news,
I was sure he'd lose at Usui
against Mako's Sileighty.
Sorry, Iketani.
Don't worry about it.
I've decided to go by
"Iketani the Lonely Driver."
That name sounds familiar.
Welcome.
Flowers?
Are you sure this isn't a mistake?
This is a gas station...
Takumi, this is for you.
Who is it from?
From Ryosuke Takahashi.
What?!
Ryosuke...
...Takahashi.
From the number-one superstar in Gunma...
...to Takumi!
What does it say?
Let me see.
"To Panda Trueno
9/15 10:00 PM, Mt. Akina Peak"
September 15th at 10 PM...
...at the top of Mount Akina.
Is that all it says?
It sounds like...
It's finally here.
A challenge from Ryosuke Takahashi
for a downhill battle.
Wow!
What are you gonna do?
You know he has to accept the challenge.
Takumi already smoked
Ryosuke's brother Keisuke.
That's right. Avoiding a rematch
is more humiliating than losing one.
What's the matter?
Don't you like being with me?
--Of course I do!
--You seem uninterested and preoccupied.
That's normal, I guess.
You seem so far away.
If this isn't fun, we should go.
It is fun!
Sorry, I apologize.
I'll forgive you if you tell me
what you were thinking about.
Well, I don't think you would really get it.
--Bye!
--Okay, I'll tell you!
A battle?
--Yeah.
--Is that like a fistfight?
No. A battle is a car race.
A car race?
I never knew that racing was your hobby.
It's not really my hobby, but I
guess it's kind of become one.
My next opponent is very
good and very well known.
I've been thinking about it since this morning.
I must be feeling the pressure.
You're a good driver, so you'll be okay.
It's not that easy.
If you don't want to race, just ignore him.
It's not that I don't want to.
I may lose to him,
but I don't want to not race him.
That's so like you.
You want to do it deep down, don't you?
You don't show it,
but I know you're very competitive.
I kind of like that about you.
Ready to go?
Why don't we talk a little more before we go?
Sure.
I know why you got in a fight
with that senior in the locker room.
After you quit the team,
your teammate told me why.
You stood up for me, didn't you?
I'm sorry I misunderstood you.
Don't be.
It doesn't matter now.
That's Takumi's Eight-Six.
Who is that girl?
Man, Keiichi Tsuchiya's drift is incredible!
Look.
Look at these pictures.
Takumi? Hey, Takumi!
What is it, Itsuki? Lunchtime?
You idiot!
Sorry, I was just talking to myself.
Takumi's been acting weird?
What's so weird?
He seems out of it.
That's normal.
I know, but he was better during the summer.
But when school started,
he suddenly got even worse than before.
Tired from all the races?
He just started racing this summer.
He may have lost his focus because of school.
I don't think that's it.
It's like something in his head broke.
Is he gonna be able to race like that?
He has a girlfriend, doesn't he?
What are you talking about?
I just thought he might
be daydreaming about her.
Daydreaming?
Just like how you were with Mako...
Kenji... that name is taboo here.
It's all right, Itsuki.
Anyway, I happened to see
Takumi driving with a girl.
Are you serious?!
I just got a glimpse, but she was pretty.
Takumi's girlfriend...
No wonder he's been
ditching me after school lately.
That traitor!
I've never even held a girl's hand!
That's it! That must be the reason!
I'm positive!
Leave it to me!
I'll take him out and interrogate him!
Racers don't need girls, right, Iketani?!
Right!
We are the "Lonely Drivers"!
This is sad.
What's on your mind?
You've been...
...dating Mogi behind my
back lately, haven't you?
Oh, is that all?
"Is that all"?!
It's no secret.
But nothing special to tell, either.
No excuses! Just answer this question...
How far did you go?
Honestly, how far did you guys go?
How far?
Be honest with your best friend!
Itsuki, watch out!
I'll tell you!
Then tell me!
Last Sunday...
Sunday!
...the two of us...
The two of you...!
...went to Akina Lake.
Hey, Itsuki, watch out!
What I mean is...
...which base did you get to, you idiot?
Which base?
Did you kiss her?
--Sure.
--What?!
Hey, Itsuki, stop!
Stop the car!
Yeah, he's daydreaming about her.
Why are you staring at me?
You've been weird lately.
I have?
You never think much,
yet you've been so preoccupied.
I guess so.
He probably can't stop
thinking about Mogi's soft lips.
I've been wondering...
...what's gonna happen to us in the future.
In the future?!
After kissing comes...
How can you even bring up
such a shameful subject
in front of the "Lonely Driver"?!
There's only one thing left to do after kissing!
What's the one thing?
You know--it!
What are you talking about?!
You're not making any sense.
What I mean by the future is...
Never mind. Difficult thoughts
aren't my specialty.
It looks like his daydreaming
can't be easily fixed.
"Welcome to Touge
Altitude: 1434m"
No wonder.
It's Keisuke's FD and Kenta's S14.
Kenta is fast down the hill.
His non-turbo S14 is made for it.
Keisuke took him under his wing
and has been personally training him.
He's our number-two successor.
The battle against the
Night Kids is in two days.
Keisuke shouldn't be wasting time with Kenta.
He must be confident.
I guess Takeshi Nakazato is easy prey.
Keisuke's on fire lately.
Don't you think he's been
driving like Ryosuke lately?
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
Ryosuke must be feeling pretty
confident about his brother.
I heard that's why he's not coming to Myogi.
Can I ask you one thing, Keisuke?
What is it?
Why aren't we challenging the Eight-Six?
We should have him
come to Akagi for revenge.
--Akagi, huh?
--Sure!
There's no way you'll lose
to the Eight-Six on our turf.
If you won't do it...
...I will!
--Forget it, Kenta.
--Why?
You think he'll beat me?
Not on Akagi's downhill.
That's beside the point.
You're a Red Sun now, and don't forget it.
We race on our opponents' courses.
I know we do...
...but I can't take it.
The Eight-Six got the best of us!
If only we could battle fair and square...
Please let me take him!
Be patient!
Don't worry.
When the opportunity arises,
the person who needs to put
an end to it will do just that.
You mean...
...Ryosuke will?
Be patient. First, the Night Kids race.
Just leave everything to us.
He does seem weird.
See?! He confessed.
He is, indeed, daydreaming.
We gotta do something.
We only have one week until the big race.
We're in serious trouble.
"To Panda Trueno
9/15 10:00 PM, Mt. Akina Peak
From Ryosuke Takahashi"
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
This is seriously not good!
What's not good, Itsuki?
--The big race is...
--Forget the race!
He's been daydreaming
about a girl at this crucial time!
--Daydreaming?
--He and Natsuki did this and that and...
...maybe they did "it," too!
--Not that again.
--Huh?
Next on Initial D: "Fierce Uphill Battle!"
Don't miss it!