"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Way to go!
Keisuke managed to shake off
his opponent! It's a perfect win!
Amazing!
A huge gap of 7 seconds.
Today's downhill is scary.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not afraid of my
opponent, but of myself.
Once I start driving, I won't be
able to suppress my fighting spirit.
I've gotta shave down the margin as much as possible.
My attack will be really close to my limit.
I'll be alright within my zone,
but if I screw up, I'm done for.
But I'm not afraid of that,
and that's what scares me.
Omiya...
Don't worry. I should be
able to manage myself well.
I'll show you the best
performance of my career tonight.
Our opponent chose the
lead position for the first run.
I see.
He might have been
inspired by Keisuke's driving.
He might use the same strategy.
In other words, he has absolute
confidence in his mad dash speed.
In turn, we can take advantage of that.
Listen. The steep area in the
second half will be the decisive point.
Try to adapt to his
change in speed flexibly.
And if you feel you can make
a move, do it in this first run.
There's no need to hold back.
I'm Omiya Satoshi.
I'm Fujiwara Takumi.
Don't lose, Fujiwara.
Okay, I'm going to start the countdown!
Act 3  [ Dead Line ]
How do you read this downhill race?
You hit the nail on the head
for the hill climb, Kubo.
I have no idea this time.
It's unpredictable.
Omiya is definitely a first class driver.
Three
Two
One
Go!
There are too many
unknowns about that Eight-Six.
There's something strange about that car.
And also something strange
about that young driver.
I've been in this business for quite a while.
I can tell you he's a rare
breed with a unique style.
Is he fast?
Oh, sure.
That Eight-Six driver is
backed by a certain someone.
Takahashi Ryosuke.
You look like you've been troubled by him.
Do you have some kind of issue with him?
Takahashi Ryosuke.
I do. No, I mean...
There's someone else
who does more than I do.
NB8C Roadster and AE86 Trueno
both have a light and compact body
with a small displacement NA engine.
They take advantage of their
agility to zip along a winding road.
They share the same concept.
Even though they were made years
apart, their potential is very similar.
That's why...
victory will be decided by the driver's instinct.
The instincts of the NB driver,
Omiya Satoshi, and...
the instincts of the Eight-Six
driver, Fujiwara Takumi.
I think the result will be determined by
whose instincts match their car the best.
You make it sound
like both cars are alive.
Maybe so.
The one who doesn't listen to the voice
of their car, even for a moment, will lose.
Project D is a legendary team which swept
the northern Kanto area without any losses.
It'd be wise to carefully observe how they drive from behind.
That's what Kobayakawa thought.
I feel the same way.
But that was the pitfall.
To observe your opponent
means you can't keep your pace.
It feels it's risky to
just watch the Eight-Six.
I just have a hunch.
That's why I chose the lead.
I'll keep my pace without
any obstacles ahead.
in order to win.
I wonder how the downhill will develop.
I don't think we can win very easily.
To be honest, our opponents level is very high.
My race wasn't easy, even though it
may have looked like it from the result.
That guy Fujiwara's facing is especially tough.
He must have perfected street driving.
Can you tell?
I can sense it.
and Fujiwara
senses it as well.
The entire space seems filled,
as if he's always on guard.
The leading NB will hold on, then it
will suddenly accelerate somewhere.
As a local who knows this course best, he can
maintain his pace, which gives him an advantage.
So the decisive point will be?
The steep, rough road
near the end of the course.
That section is disadvantageous to the
Eight-Six because its suspension design is old.
Well, that's true.
But our disadvantage
didn't just begin tonight.
It's been our motto to fight on our
opponents stage since the Red Suns days.
Right.
My brother's calculated knowledge of fighting
those away races has always worked perfectly.
If our opponent is a
specialist on this course
we're a special team organized
to attack enemy territories.
Whoever is faster than the other.
That will be everything in the end.
Nothing is impossible for Project D, as long
as we have the genius of Takahashi Ryosuke.
I truly believe that.
They're close, almost at the corner.
They're gonna dive into the mid section hairpin.
There they are!
Alright!
Go, Omiya!
Throw everything you've got at him!
Leave the Eight-Six in the dust!
They've passed the mid section, fighting tail to nose.
It's developed the same
way up to this point.
I knew my opponent would
accelerate somewhere.
I was frustrated by my opponent, who didn't
make his move according to my predictions.
For some reason, I felt cornered.
The same thing must be
happening to that Eight-Six driver.
In a situation where Omiya maintains his pace,
neither of them can ease up, even for a second.
We're only at the halfway point.
My tension is almost going off the scale.
But I have one more level.
There will be a moment when
my fighting spirit turns on.
Seems like my legs got thicker.
Here... and here.
It must be because of the muscle training.
I can hit my drives farther, which is nice
but my pants size changed, which isn't so nice.
I'm supposed to be on summer vacation.
I wish I could go to the beach once in a while
with Takumi.
That's impossible, I'm too busy.
Takumi must be racing in Kanagawa now.
I want to see him race just once, but
that'll probably scare the hell out of me.
Do your best, Takumi.
Make sure you win.
Good, I'm focused.
From a strategic point of view, I think
braking is most important on the downhill.
Stopping distance increases dramatically on the downhill
versus level ground, so one braking mistake is critical.
Unlike circuits, public streets are dark without
any distance markers before each corner.
So, to determine the precise braking point
you can only rely on your refined intuition.
Landmarks are useless.
I'm constantly surprised by the
potential of the human brain.
Fujiwara's braking sense is exceptional.
That's why he can keep winning on the downhill
against locals who are familiar with their course.
It's not something you can
acquire by just practicing.
He's definitely a natural.
You can figure out your opponent's driving skills by
watching how he brakes as you stay right on his tail.
You're right.
That's not so difficult.
And it's even more true between
two drivers with similar skills.
Conversely, hiding skills can be the key.
You show your true braking skills when
you decide to settle the match.
I was late, only a little, but definitely late.
That hard braking from the long straightaway.
Even if it was just that one time,
I was late in braking.
Incredible entry!
The gap with the Eight-Six is getting wider!
I'm using everything
I've got at 100% capacity.
I'm in a dangerous zone.
They're getting closer.
They're almost at the corner.
Looks quite dangerous.
The cars of that era tend to behave like
that when their suspension is stiffened.
You can say it's very 86 like.
The car's seriously tuned to be the very best in the stages
where the average speed is below 100km/h (62mph).
So there's a meaning to the
choice of using the Eight-Six.
That's something Ryosuke would come up with.
He knows what he's doing based on the fact that
the car doesn't have any aerodynamic parts, but
the level of competition is so high that the cars
will momentarily reach their critical speed even
during the slow speed stage.
People say the GT wing only works on the circuit,
but at their level, it's no longer a decoration.
Aerodynamics might decide
the outcome of this race.
Basically, Mazda's rear wheel drive cars are designed
to have the roll axis a little forward of the mid point.
The FD is no exception, but the Roadster in
particular gives you a better handling feel
thanks to the biased load to the front.
But if you push it harder, it tends to over steer
because of the lack of load to the rear.
It becomes an unavoidable
issue when tuning a Roadster.
There are many different approaches, but you can't
eliminate the car's natural over steering tendency.
I wonder how they dealt with it.
Over steering on the downhill is bad.
Instead, you can drive faster by under steering.
Knowing our opponents, their car
must have been perfectly tuned, but
If something destroys that balance,
Fujiwara will have a chance.
I can't catch him, but
the gap hasn't widened, even though
I'm only tracing his car's line and speed.
It's almost a miracle that you've kept up with me.
From this point on,
I don't need the mirror.
No need to play a guessing game.
I just have to look ahead and keep pushing hard.
I'll just have to check the
rear after crossing the goal line.
That's when I'll ensure my victory.
The Eight-Six's headlights went off!
No way! On this pitch black
mountain pass? What's going on?
The Eight-Six's headlights are off?!
The blind attack, huh?
Ryosuke
During the race until now, Fujiwara must have
intuitively learned that he's at a disadvantage
in the high speed sections.
Fujiwara's god sent talent.
No, he may have heard
the voice of the Eight-Six.
Blind attack, which is Fujiwara's forte, is a two sided
diversion technique of confusing his opponent
as well as hiding his offensive strategy.
But when the opponent is familiar with
the course and remains highly focused.
Right. It doesn't create the desired effect.
However...
Retractable headlights have a lower drag
coefficient value when they're lowered.
Because of less air resistance.
Fujiwara must have wanted to raise his top speed by
reducing the drag, even if only by a very small amount.
Fujiwara's tenacity
His tenacity might create
a breakthrough.
Just before his braking action.
I'm not exactly sure, but most likely.
Right here.
It was too soon, if only by a little.
What the hell happened?
Dammit, I won't lose after coming this far.
I'll keep my space.
Can you keep up?
I messed up the wing.
I've gotta keep the race short.
I'll settle this match on the first run.
The car is unstable.
I don't know what's wrong with the wing,
but the car's lateral balance is off.
I would've been better off if
it had broken off completely.
Damn, no need for excuses. I just have
to motivate myself to raise my limit.
So, today wasn't my day after all.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.