What the hell are they thinking ?!
This straightaway's too short for that !
Hey, that's Takahashi Ryosuke's white FC !
Are they battling ?
An R32 GT-R.
He's better than I thought.
I can keep up with Takahashi Ryosuke.
Young Magazine 35th Anniversary Production
As I thought, you're Takahashi
Ryosuke of the Akagi Red Suns.
And you ?
I'm Nakazato Takeshi of the Myogi Night Kids
Nakazato...
I've heard your name at least.
So, what's a Myogi street racer doing in Akina ?
Look who's talking.
You're an Akagi street racer.
Both of us have the same objective.
I never expected someone like that in Akina.
A driver of a GT-R tuned to 380 HP
is planning to challenge Akina's Eight-Six ?
How did you know the power of my car's engine ?
The battle will be very one-sided, and the outcome is obvious before you even try.
The GT-R will win hands down on
the uphill, thanks to its power, but...
...you can't beat that Eight-Six on the
downhill, no matter how hard you try.
Say what ?!
Don't get me wrong.
I just spoke my mind.
Don't screw around with me.
If you put it that way,
I can't back off no matter what.
I'll beat that Eight-Six and
make you eat your words.
The R32 Skyline GT-R and I will
humiliate Akina's downhill specialist !
You'll understand once you race against it.
New Movie [Initial]
Central Anime
- Racer -
Don't spill it, or you'll squish the tofu.
More than usual ?
You have a big load today.
I thought he had changed a bit,
but maybe it's just my imagination.
GENERAL
This way, please.
Thank you so much.
Takahashi Ryosuke was in Akina, huh ?
He had super precise drift.
But what surprised me more was the GT-R.
The driver showed excellent grip,
and stayed right on the FC's tail.
I don't know who it was, but he's amazing.
Well, drifting is flashy, but some say
it's slower than driving with grip.
Is that so, Iketani ?
But real drifting is fast, and Takumi proved it.
Did you think about it, Takumi ?
Well...
I beg you. I got carried away, and said your
Eight-Six was the Akina Speed Stars' secret weapon.
I already blew my horn.
Same here.
We'll be embarrassed if you don't join.
You have to join, Takumi.
I'm a part of the deal.
I don't mind joining your team,
but it's for street racers, right ?
But I'm not a street racer, so...
What the hell are you talking about ?
Nobody drives faster than you in Akina.
Is that so...?
It is. If you're not a
street racer, what are you ?!
A cup of water is a nice idea.
I thought Takumi's superb driving was because of his
experience in driving Akina's downhill for so long, but...
...I was wrong.
The uphill drive was more important.
The load shift is one of the basics of controlling a car.
If you try not to spill water in a cup,
you'll learn extremely sensitive load shifting.
You're amazing, Bunta.
You've trained him into a
completely new type of driver.
Thank you.
That was quite a circus.
I hate drifters...
...but that Eight-Six was fast.
I need a neck and neck battle
where I can lose myself completely.
You'll be a worthy opponent...
...Akina's Eight-Six.
So hot...
I wish I could take deliveries in an
air-conditioned car, like Iketani and Takumi.
I just don't understand Takumi.
He totally owned Takahashi
Keisuke of the Akagi Red Suns.
But he hasn't changed a bit, and doesn't
even think of himself as a street racer.
I'd be so hyped up, telling everyone
in school how I did this and...
Welcome.
A GT-R ! How awesome !
I'm Nakazato of the Myogi Night Kids.
I was told by the locals that I could
contact the Akina Speed Stars here.
You're a member, aren't you ?
Huh ?
Can you tell me when I should visit
Akina to see that famous Eight-Six ?
A Speed Stars member...
That sounds so cool.
Hey, do you know what I'm talking about ?
Maybe this's the wrong gas station.
No, you got the right station.
In fact, the Eight-Six driver
is a close friend of mine.
Really ?
He and I are the fastest
Eight-Six duo among the members.
Is that right ?
Many Eight-Six drivers are very skilled,
and I hear good things about the Speed Stars.
I'm so honored.
Anyway, I can get a hold of him.
He's my best friend after all.
Thanks.
Make sure you tell him...
...Nakazato of the Night Kids will be waiting on Mt. Akina at 10 pm next Saturday...
...for one downhill match.
Wha...?
W...wait ! Please...
Holy crap...
That was...
...a declaration of challenge !
I'm sorry !
So sorry, really sorry !
I apologize !
What a pain.
It must be the black GT-R we saw on Akina.
It's gotta be.
It makes sense. Nakazato of the Night Kids can stack up against Takahashi Ryosuke.
Takumi, I'm not in a place to be asking this,
but will you accept his challenge ?
Otherwise, I'll be a burden to them.
I don't get it. Why would you be
a burden to them if I don't go ?
People'll speak bad about the
Speed Stars for running away.
Street racers...
When it comes to a car race,
street racers must accept challenges !
If you like to drive a car,
that's enough to be a street racer !
That may be true for street racers,
but I'm not a street racer.
Welcome.
Hey, Takumi...
Iketani, what should we do ?
We'll be in trouble if Takumi doesn't go.
Well, the GT-R would be
too tough, even for Takumi.
Besides, Nakazato of Myogi is a famous street racer just like Akagi's Takahashi brothers.
Given the circumstances,
I can't force him into this.
Dad, is the GT-R really that good ?
Yeah, it is.
Could you beat it on the downhill ?
I could.
It's a piece of cake,
whether it's a GT-R or a Porsche.
You think I can defeat it ?
You want me to lend you my car ?
No, it's okay.
I see.
Thanks for the food.
So a GT-R will be next, huh ?
Nakazato's GT-R is here again today !
Its exit acceleration is incredible !
How much horsepower does it have ?
It's going to race against the Speed Star's Eight-Six tomorrow, right ? That's all they're talking about.
I smell trouble.
The Night Kids' Nakazato is challenging the Eight-Six, which defeated the Red Suns' Takahashi Keisuke.
It's going to be a clash of pride between
the two large factions of Akagi and Myogi.
Akina's nights are gonna
be super exciting this summer.
That Civic that just went by was really fast.
Sure, the GT-R is a monster, but it's not invincible.
Itsuki, I've thought about it since then.
I'm going to ask Takumi to race tonight.
Even if his opponent is a GT-R, the Eight-Six
becomes something else with Takumi behind the wheel.
It turns into an amazing super machine.
I don't think he'll listen.
What ?
He's hated being forced or told
what to do since he was little.
He looks reserved, but he's really stubborn.
He's that type.
I see.
Iketani, I'll go to Mt. Akina tonight,
and apologize to the GT-R driver.
Itsuki...
I'll explain the circumstances,
and kneel down on the ground or whatever.
From the beginning, the
Speed Stars had nothing to do with this.
Alright, we'll go too.
Don't mention this to Takumi.
He must have forgotten about it already.
Speaking of which, where's Takumi ?
Oh, he's in the office.
The Manager had something to discuss with him.
Let me make this clear, Takumi.
You shouldn't do this because
the GT-R is a nasty opponent.
You're only doing this
to save face for Itsuki, right?
If so, you shouldn't.
You're clueless about cars, so you don't know how great the GT-R is, like a class of its own.
It's got the combined advantage of FR and 4WD thanks to the electrically-controlled torque-split 4WD system.
It's also fast on the downhill because of superb stability.
The RB26 twin turbo engine is monstrous.
It was originally designed to make 600 HP for racing,
so you can easily obtain power with a minor modification.
The Eight-Six is totally outclassed.
Besides, your opponent is a famous
street racer. This race is really unfair.
You made a name by defeating the
Akagi Red Suns, so you'd better cherish it.
You gain nothing by participating in
a race you have no chance of winning.
Listen to your elders, okay ?
Thank you for your advice, but...
...I'm not really interested in being a
famous street racer or anything like that.
So you're not going to back down ?
I won't.
If you hype it up like that, I want to
find out how great that car really is.
Manager, I'm not afraid of the GT-R.
He bought it.
I can't remember how many
times I fooled Bunta this way.
They're so alike, right
down to their personality.
This is going to be fun.
Temporarily Closed
for Personal Reasons
-Fujiwara Tofu Shop
Temporarily closed, what the hell ?
I didn't know about this.
We're poor, you can't be slacking off.
Where is the car ?
Dad ?
I can't do anything without the car.
Such a huge gallery.
It looks bigger than the one during the race against Takahashi Keisuke the other day.
I didn't expect this to become such a huge event.
The black GT-R's Nakazato...
A huge group of the Night Kids members came.
This isn't the atmosphere for admitting mistakes.
The Takahashi brothers have come.
Hurry up !
Keisuke is so cool !
Ryosuke, you're so gorgeous !
Takahashi Ryosuke and Keisuke have come, too ?
That makes it even harder to back off.
What should we do ?
Why am I so irritated ?
I want to go so bad.
If you like to drive a car,
that's enough to be a street racer !
If you're a street racer,
be proud of the skills you've got !
I don't know if I like to drive or not, but...
...I am proud of the skills I've learned by myself.
At least, I feel like that, and I want
to test my skills to the limit.
I want to challenge the GT-R
by throwing everything I've got at it.
I've never felt this way.
I'm getting eager to drive.
Dad, please come home.
That's...
That sound.
I'm off, Dad !
His eyes looked different.
The Takahashi brothers have come as expected.
They must be concerned.
I was assured I'd lose.
This's a great opportunity for us to show the gallery that drifting can never be faster than gripping.
Oh man. Here comes
Takeshi's tunnel-minded opinion.
Shut up. You know it's true.
Drift is just a performance to please the gallery.
It's meaningless to be a street
racer if you don't try to drive fast.
I know it because I used to drift.
Once you're done with drifting and start
driving with grip, you'll know it's better.
The time of the drifting FR is over.
I'll put an end to Akina's Eight-Six.
Itsuki, let's go.
We'll be with you.
I don't know what they're
going to do to you, but...
They'll kill me if I say the Eight-Six won't come.
Father, Mother...
God help me, please.
I've never slept with a girl !
I don't wanna die !
Why are you kneeling down
right in the middle of the road ?
Takumi...
Takumi, you came.
Sorry I'm late, Itsuki.
When it comes to a car race,
street racers must accept challenges, right ?
Takumi !
There he is, Takeshi.
So pretentious, showing up at the last moment.
I thought he'd be older.
How did a kid like him acquire such technique ?
Your Eight-Six is gone.
Yuichi ?!
Takumi went to Mt. Akina ?
Yeah, he took off looking really uptight.
I don't know what's going on.
I never expected him to go
to the mountain pass himself.
Like father, like son, after all.
Bunta, he'll be racing against a GT-R.
Did you give him any advice ?
Nothing really.
But...
But what ?
This is the goal.
All marshals are in position.
Nobody's entered the mountain pass.
We can start any time.
Roger that.
Let us know if someone else enters.
Got it.
I'm Nakazato of the Myogi Night Kids.
Your name ?
Fujiwara Takumi.
I'll remember your name.
Start counting down in five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Go !
Takumi, go for it !
I'll let you enjoy the Cinderella Castle Mystery Tour from the best seat in the house, Keisuke.
Nakazato's going easy on the
gas to wait for the Eight-Six.
It's meaningless to
out-accelerate him on a straightaway.
I want a battle.
The real start begins in the corner.
You've gotta be kidding !
There's no way you can stay behind me with that overly showy crab-like driving !
I'm impressed.
Watching his driving this close,
it reminds me that his drift is an art.
Even I can't control my FC like that at the limit.
But wouldn't a non-turbo Eight-Six eventually lose because of the lack of power ?
A turbo is a powerful aid in straightaways, but its
power will make the car unstable at the exit of corners.
It's a double-edge sword.
But once you get the Eight-Six at the right angle, you can step on the gas as you like.
In a technical course, an under-powered car can be faster if you can be aggressive on the accelerator.
Come to think of it, I could barely use the full
throttle of my 350 HP engine on Akina's downhill.
You go boom, and you have to brake right after.
It was also frustrating that I had
to use partial throttle so often.
That's the nature of the FR layout.
Nature of the FR ?
Wait, Brother !
What about the GT-R's 4WD ?!
Its ATTESA E-TS can let you step on the gas without losing control, so you can use the turbo power as much as you like.
This is it.
This feeling of high tension, like
the blood in my entire body is boiling.
This is a battle !
The Eight-Six is falling behind.
Nakazato may be a big talker, but he's good.
He minimizes the under-steer by
transferring the weight skillfully.
It's the type of driving that
makes use of the GT-R's power.
It looks boring, but he doesn't drive wastefully, giving no overtaking opportunities.{It looks boring, but the defense is
tight because the style is efficient.}
You can't be so relaxed, Brother.
It'd be humiliating to allow the
Night Kids to defeat the Eight-Six.
I doubt that will happen.
The first half has many
straightaways and the slopes are mild.
The slope is steep in the second half, and that's where the downhill specialist will show his true potential.
What amazing drift !
That's Akina's Eight-Six.
Incredible.
This must be a dream !
Takahashi Ryosuke's FC ?!
What's going on ?
A three-way match ?
Is this going to determine
who's the fastest in Gunma ?!
Low-speed hairpin curves
are the GT-R's area of specialty.
If you can use the powerful
brakes to slow down like you should...
...the weight will shift to the front regardless.
The biggest weakness of losing
front tire grip can be minimized. {Using the definition of gpush under,h which is to lose the grip during acceleration at the exit of a corner.}
And this is the moment of truth.
This acceleration from the low gear is unmatched, and the stiff body is steady as a rock.
The fastest machine on the circuit
is the fastest on the public roads.
The R badge on the rear right
symbolizes the R's unbeaten legend.
Can you keep up with my R, Eight-Six ?
It's different...
Something's different.
You changed the suspension setting ?
Heavy under-steer when you open the throttle.
Heavy under-steer ?
What're you thinking, Bunta ?
Takumi will have to drift.
If the suspension is...
You don't know anything.
When it comes to the FR, a skilled driver can
maintain full throttle longer because of under-steering.
It's even more true when drifting.
I didn't tell Takumi about it, though...
You didn't ? He must be freaked out by
now because of it's different handling.
It's pointless to tell him because he's not smart enough to change his driving style after thinking it through.
If that's the case...
He may not be smart, but what
he's learned with his body is real.
Minor modifications to the
suspension won't bother him.
Bunta...
Takumi should be able to figure it out.
The Eight-Six is the type of car
that can train the driver after all.
It's different.
It's definitely different.
The car remains stable when
I'm pressing harder on the pedal.
I can start pressing the pedal a bit earlier.
I don't have to hesitate because
the car doesn't skid too much.
I see it, Dad.
This is why you closed the shop.
I don't know how it works, but it feels good.
Amazing.
My eyes can barely keep up.
I lost to that technique.
He started to drop the
inside tire into the gutter.
He must have gotten serious.
He's going nuts.
The Eight-Six is gaining on me !
Ridiculous !
That's impossible !
Very well done.
My presumption about the Eight-Six being an
under-powered classic is gone if you can push it that hard.
It's a wonderful machine with
top-notch combat potential.
I'm so thrilled.
I haven't had an exciting battle
like this since I switched to this car.
In low-speed corners, even though the Eight-Six can almost bite the GT-R's tail during the entry...
...the gap widens at the exit because
of the difference in initial acceleration.
But in high-speed corners,
the Eight-Six can narrow the gap.
The street racers all talk about having to aim at the very inside of the corners, but he's extraordinary.
The bumper almost rubs the guard rails...
...as the car takes the shortest path while
drifting with four wheels at its limit.
In order for the under-powered Eight-Six to
maintain speed he avoids wasteful deceleration.
That's why he uses drift.
He's in a class of his own. This has
nothing to do with vehicle performance.
That bastard must have a few screws loose !
His pressure is tremendous.
Why can't I shake it ?
Dammit !
I'm so glad to be alive !
I wonder where Takumi is at right now ?
Given the incredible speed,
he must have gone down quite far.
If that Eight-Six turns out
to be a worthy opponent...
...the GT-R's weakness will
hit Takeshi just about now.
The GT-R's weakness ? What's that ?
Simply put, the body weight.
Body weight ?
The GT-R's weakness is under-steering
because of its super heavy front section.
Even if you try to mitigate it
with tuning or driving technique...
...you can't change the basic characteristics.
If you continue a forceful steering manner as you use the ABS on the hard downhill...
...the front tires and brakes will lose their grip.
By the time you reach the bottom, you'll be
fighting under-steering at the entrance of corners.
Even with a well-tuned brake system.
The response from the front has become dull.
It's slightly under-steering.
The stress to the front
tires was greater than expected.
This is gonna be tough.
But I must not lose !
They're here !
The Eight-Six is right on its tail !
Nakazato's the fastest in Myogi,
but he's being pressed hard !
I saw you overtake Takahashi
Keisuke in these five hairpin curves.
You only have to keep the inside closed. I'll never open the inside no matter what.
What the...?
From the outside ?!
Don't screw around with me, you brat !
Did you see that ?
That was insane.
It drifted through this narrow road.
From the outside again ?
It's so annoying !
The GT-R's motion is unstable.
Nakazato must be losing concentration.
Keisuke, the Eight-Six's going
to overtake, so don't miss it !
I see.
Because I'm trying to block the inside too much, I'm not
braking hard enough and I'm not taking the ideal cornering line.{Because I forced myself into staying close to the inside, I took an abnormal path, which resulted in a loose entry.}
I can enter the corners a little faster if I leave just enough space that's too narrow for him to pass.
He's taking the outer line,
which means he won't take the inside !
It's gone. Where...where is it?
The outer line was a feint motion !
He changed his line while full braking ?!
That was a brilliant move, but...
...starting from side-by-side, I can still pull
ahead using full acceleration in second gear.
I'll show you the true potential of the RB26 !
It lost...?
The GT-R lost...
No, that's not it.
I'm the one who lost.
The GT-R didn't lose to the Eight-Six.
It's a shock, but somehow it feels good.
I did everything I could.
There're plenty of great drivers out there.
And there's quite a few of them
driving the mountain passes.{a lot of
them in
That was fun, wasn't it, Keisuke ?
That was great.
It pressured the GT-R really
hard during braking on the downhill.
The Eight-Six must have
high-performance ABS.
What're you talking about ?
You think the Eight-Six has ABS ?
The driver's right foot is superior
to machine-controlled ABS.
I haven't been this excited in a long time.
I have to rewrite a big chunk of my paper.
That Eight-Six is a really worthy target to defeat.
Brother...
T...Takumi...
...won ?!
Are you serious ?
I'm checking now.
Apparently, it's true.
It can't be true.
No way.
Looks like you are the one
who was humiliated, Takeshi.
You can't act tough for quite a while.
When I defeat the Eight-Six, then I, Shoji Shingo, will become the leader of the Night Kids.
Just wait, Eight-Six. I'll send you to the junk yard by fighting under emotional, yet dangerous rules.
Eat one.
Thank you.
Hot...
This is awkward.
I've begun to look at you differently.
Huh ? What do you mean ?
Right now, you're the usual Takumi.
But once you get in the Eight-Six and are
thrust into the night mountain pass...
...you become an admirable
hero of Akina's street racers.
Huh ? Really ?
That's what this is all about ?
You make me feel embarrassed, Itsuki.
Although you're just an airhead
munching on a sweet bun right now.
"Airhead," you say ?
I feel awkward, too.
But if someone becomes happy because of what I do, that makes me really happy.
I see. I didn't know you were the
type who'd do things for others.
Driving is slowly becoming fun.
Iketani's car is repaired.
That's good.
Let's go to Akina tonight.
Sure.
You look happy.
Of course.
I finally got my baby back.
The S13 Silvia, that is.
When did it...?!
It tapped my bumper.
You want me to move because I'm too slow ?
Screw you !
T...Takumi...
Itsuki, Iketani, are you alright ?
I'm fine, more or less.
Apologize ?
You've gotta be kidding.
Don't screw around with us !
You hit us on purpose !
You could have injured us really bad !
Like I said before, it was your fault.
I didn't expect your corner entry to be so slow.
No one could react fast
enough to avoid a little bonk.
Say what ?
He's rubbing our nose in it.
If you insist, I will kneel down and apologize only if
you can defeat us in a downhill battle under our rules.
I don't mind if that Eight-Six
driver over there is my opponent.
You're good at the downhill, right ?
What're you going to do ?
So, are you Speed Stars boys in or not ?
If you lose, you'll kneel
down and apologize, right ?
He's only provoking you, Takumi.
You don't know what he might do.
I won't lose to a guy like him, Iketani.
Wait, you said something about rules.
It's really not a big deal.
We call it the gum tape death match.
You tape your right hand
to the steering wheel and race.
That's all.
Stop. Don't do this, Takumi.
This's insane. It's so risky.
You know what this means ?
You can't steer as much !
If you can't do that how are you
going to clear the corners ?!
But the conditions will be equal.
He must have practiced !
That's why he brought up a rule like this !
This's just too risky, even for you !
Please don't, Takumi !
I won't quit, Iketani.
I don't know why, but I don't want
to lose to that guy no matter what.
Takumi...
You can go first, Eight-Six boy.
Go !
They're off.
We've gotta go, too !
Impossible !
We'll never catch them !
I'm not thinking about catching them !
If Takumi crashes, I want to
help him as soon as possible !
There's no need for two downhill specialists.
This EG6 Civic driver Shoji Shingo of the Myogi
Night Kids is the fastest downhill driver in Gunma.
Let's see how many corners you can clear.
You're done.
Damn, how did he recover from that ?
But it's only a matter of time.
No matter how good the driver is, you must apply a
counter-steer to stop the over-steering of an FR car.
Right, but the Civic is an FF, so...
...you can stop over-steering with the accelerator,
so you can dive into corners more aggressively.
And you can mitigate under-steering
by pulling the parking brake.
Under this rule, you'll crash
unless you drive an FF car.
If someone can avoid an accident
in an FR car, he must be a monster.
I feel so uneasy after every corner because
I might see a wrecked Eight-Six at any moment.
I feel like he's gonna be alright.
It's Takumi, after all.
Why ? Why can he turn ?
The gum tape death match is not
easy for a first timer to manage.
See ? I can pass you
any time if I want to.
Why don't you feel the heat ?
Attack harder and crash.
I can go...
...faster than usual.
I can go faster if I depend less on the steering.
What the hell ?
No matter how much pressure
I put on him, he remains stable.
In fact, he's getting faster.
I don't give a damn !
Victory is all that matters in a battle...
...regardless of how !
Damn, what a lucky ass brat.
Well then, I'll just pull away right here !
This is it. The sound of the engine
revving all the way up to the red zone.
I just can't get enough
of this intoxicating feeling !
You did that on purpose.
I will not lose to a scumbag
like you, no matter what !
No way !
How can he keep up ?!
I'm driving at my ultimate speed !
What's going on with that Eight-Six ?
He's not using the steering...
...but turning by only shifting the weight !
What the hell was that ?!
How did he pass me in a place like that ?!
If I lose the very gum
tape death match I set up...
...I'll be a laughingstock among my team members, and never be able to redeem myself.
I have to save my rep even
if that means I have to resort to a tie.
The end of this battle is a double crash !
My EG6...
Ouch. You really blew it.
Hey, are you alright ? Are you hurt ?
I think my right arm is broken because
of the kickback from the steering wheel.
Hop in. I'll take you to the hospital.
It's faster than calling an ambulance.
I can't owe you that much.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It hurts, right ?
We'll take care of the mess here.
We're used to things like this.
Don't be a stranger.
Crashes happen to anyone.
We are locals, so we know
the emergency hospital.
As he says.
Thanks, I owe you one.
So Takumi won.
He's incredible, isn't he ?
I ended up facing a really annoying a-hole,
and I snapped during the race.
After that, I don't remember what happened.
When we lose ourselves, both you
and I don't know when to stop.
But I'd never damage the car.
So, did you win ?
Yeah.
I see.
Like Itsuki and Iketani say, street racers
love cars and take good care of them, but I...
I'm sorry.
It's worn out real bad.
I might as well replace it while
the car's in the body shop.
It's hot again today.
You're incredible.
No street racer will challenge
you to a downhill battle in Akina.
I don't think so.
There're plenty of good drivers in
Gunma, because its skill level is high.
I don't think Takahashi Ryosuke
of the Red Suns can remain quiet.
Takahashi Ryosuke, huh ?
Speaking of which, he's fast.
When I was fighting the GT-R,
a white RX7 was right on my tail.
I was occupied chasing the GT-R at the time...
...but looking back on it, he concerns me.
I know for sure. He's really fast,
faster than anyone we've ever seen.
I see. Probably so.
Hey, Takumi, what would you do if
a great racer like him challenged you ?
You won't accept, right ?
If that happens...
...I'll take a shot.
I finally found you !
Mogi...?
Why are you here ?
You only mentioned "gas station," so I've been looking for your work place for a long time.
Why ?
Because I wanted to see you at work.
Itsuki, who is she ?
A classmate, but um...
Your bellybutton's showing.
That's fine.
This's how it's supposed to look.
Hello. I have a flower delivery,
and need your signature.
It's addressed to Mr. Panda Trueno.
Panda Trueno...?
Takumi, that must be you.
Me ?
A bouquet for Takumi ?
From who ?
There. A letter.
Open it quickly.
From who ? Who is it ?
So who sent it ?
August 27th at 10PM
Will be waiting at the peak of Mt. Akina
Takahashi Ryosuke
Even when my ears are covered, I hear the heartbeat getting...
Fujiwara Takumi:
Nakazato Takeshi:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Takahashi Ryosuke
Shoji Shingo:
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Mogi Natsuki:
Tachibana Yuichi:
Kenji:
Mamoru:
Shigeru:
Man L:
Man G:
Fujiwara Bunta:
Miyano Mamoru
Suwabe Junichi
Nakamura Yuichi
Ono Daisuke
Sakaguchi Shuhei
Shiraishi Minoru
Tsuchida Hiroshi
Uchida Maaya
Shimura Tomoyuki
Katsu Anri
Goto Mitsuhiro
Nozawa Satoshi
Hamayanen (8.6 second bazooka)
Tanaka Shingle (8.6 second bazooka)
Hirata Hiroaki
...faster and faster.
Try to find the right answer, but there's no such thing.
Hey daddy, tell me... I wonder why those people fight.
For their name ? For their cash, or for their pride ?
Those piercingly honest eyes of yours.
I'm going down. (I'm going down.)
But everybody's saying, "We're right all the time."
`cuz they want to stick to absolute justice.
They're never turning back. Never want to be denied.
But it's falling down. (It's falling down)
Patching up the open wounds with the past.
Remembering the pain that never fades away.
I draw my blade.
It's not about becoming a hero to save the world.
Instead, until my voice wears thin...
...I want to sing of the future when the crybaby next to me only smiles.
I continue to fight.
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to ? Dumb ass !
"Don't get carried away," says a snot-nose brat.
Gutsy, for now, and goes "Should I kick `eem asses?"
With a faint voice. "Whacha say, huh ?"
When I close my eyes, I see your tears burnt into mine.
I swear to myself. I'll never back down.
Translation
Hiro-kun
Song Translations
Lily-chan
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
It's not about becoming a hero to save the world.
Instead, until my voice wears thin...
...I want to sing of the future when the crybaby next to me only smiles.
Someday, I want our future to be...
...the place where we can laugh away our tough times.
In the pouring rain, I long for your heart to be as open as the sunny sky.
I continue to fight.
Preview
Ultimate Battle !!
New Movie [Initial D]
-Dream-{Phonetically, mugen means limitless, semantically the characters mean dream and expression}