"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
"Steep Curve"
What do you think about today's race?
What kind of outlook should we have?
Personally, I'm scared.
About Keisuke's race today.
Huh? You're scared? Is this
course's downhill that difficult?
No, that's not what I meant.
How can I put this?
Even if a car's settings
are tuned for the hillclimb,
once you go up, you'll
have to come down, right?
Well, yeah.
In other words, Keisuke's run the
downhill as many times as the hillclimb,
so his downhill techniques
have steadily gotten better, too.
Then the same goes for you, right?
No, because our power differential is too great.
On the uphill, there's no way the
Eight-Six could keep up with his FD...
But the FD is incredibly fast,
even on the downhill.
I don't think there's much
of a difference between us.
You're not serious!
I get that general idea
from watching him practice.
As the team downhiller, it's sort of unsettling.
What I'm scared of is being
shown Keisuke's true power
when he takes the downhill with full intent.
He's left me behind? No. I can feel him.
He's up ahead!
"Act 21: Dogfight"
So he preserved his tires during the hillclimb
to bet everything on the downhill, huh?
That's a pretty smart idea. Not bad.
Like it or not, I'm gonna have to get serious!
Oops.
I was about to fall silent there.
Hyaa!
In a street race, a gap of
six seconds isn't that great.
If that FD can't catch up to Ko on
the downhill, that's when we win.
But if he does catch up...
If there's no clear winner,
we just go to the next round, right?
That's incorrect. If this isn't
settled in the first race,
it would be a tremendous
disadvantage for Ko...
...because in the second round,
the FD would go first.
You know what that means. Both the
pursuer and the pursued will feel
the pressure of being unable
to see their opponent.
Even if distance opens up between them,
it will be a dead heat where
every millisecond counts.
One, two!
Awesome! He shortcutted
over the roadside gutter!
Still, he'd go that far with something
in the GT-R's weight class?
Because for Hoshino, there is no second round.
No matter what, he has to finish
this race in the first round.
Here comes the FD!
This one's taking a shortcut too,
like it's only natural.
They have the same way of thinking, is that it?
All things said, this is one intense race.
Not being able to see your opponent
means you can't drop your
guard even for a second.
A race where you're going neck
and neck would be a lot less stress.
I see him! All right.
Four seconds... No, maybe less.
I've definitely gained on him
since the turnaround point.
Rather than some old God Foot dude...
...the winner of the downhill will be me!
He's come this far, huh?
He's better than I thought.
But I know he's comin' to close the gap.
Now it's a game of tag,
to outrun him till the goal line!
From the beginning, that's the
kind of, uh, race this has been.
Hngrar!
Coming up is what will decide this race!
This heat will probably
take its toll on Ko, as well.
Ooh, this is tough.
A handful, all right, a handful.
This youngster from Gunma is something else.
Even on the downhill, he's gettin'
closer and closer to my R34.
All right! I'm definitely closing the gap on him.
This really is fun. It's been a
long time since I've felt like this.
One, two, three!
"Touge Tunnel Project
To be implemented soon"
I swear... Now it's getting to
where it's hard for me to breathe.
We've never faced this kind
of development before.
I think the six-second time lag
at the turnaround point
might have made him push forward
into a very dangerous zone.
Even if things progress according
to the scenario I have scripted,
his chances of winning are fifty-fifty.
His opponent is of the highest caliber.
Dammit! Tire traction is less than half, eh?
I've used the front tires for all they're worth.
The weight of the car's frame
is finally takin' its toll.
He's come up a hair's breadth from me.
That margin I had is now all but gone?!
Fine!
Just one more...
Then I'm comin' in with a deathwish!
Hey! You bastard!
They've gotten close!
They're about to tear around the last corner!
It's no good! He can't lose him.
Ko...
So it's no good, huh?
Yes! Keisuke made it to the second round.
No way. It can't be...
The Hoshino...
...couldn't hold onto that big of a lead?
Mr. Joshima!
I'll say this for the sake of Ko's reputation:
his opponent is running
a truly incredible race.
Without a doubt, their driver is of a
level far above what we'd expected.
He may be our enemy,
but all I can say is, "Well done."
That was a brutal and most incredible race.
What?! This isn't the time
to go openly admiring them!
The opponent will be
leading in the second round...
You said it yourself, didn't you?
Now the conditions of the race
will be overwhelmingly against us!
Yes, well... True enough, I did say that.
That's if one were to think
of this in the "normal" way.
But the driver that is Kozo Hoshino
is about to enter his true element.
All right, we're moving into the second round!
Starting in five seconds! Four!
Three! Two! One!
Go!
The first round was to my liking,
one of smart progression.
However, this strategy has one small hole in it.
How will our opponent react to that?
This second round will be turbulent...
Make no mistake!
Give it a rest, old man. I already
know you've got good traction.
Hey, what gives? Is that all it's got,
that rotary rocket of yours?!
I know from the first round that I lose
when coming out of corners on the hillclimb.
No matter how much he rides me,
I just have to not let him pass.
If I can keep outrunning him like this till
the turnaround point, this race is mine.
I won't be beaten on the downhill!
It looks like they've started a second round.
Looks like it.
Sure enough, I guess that lightweight FD
was pretty fast on the downhill.
This will make things tough for Purple Shadow.
They're both big-framed cars, so pulling
ahead on the hillclimb will be hard.
So Project D's strategy
will decide the race, eh?
He's a bright one, all right, Ryosuke Takahashi.
Still...
Something bothers me.
What's that?
Ryosuke Takahashi is certainly a cunning foe...
But I don't think Kozo Hoshino could have
completely failed to see this coming.
After all, it was Hoshino that
chose to lead in the first round.
If he loses, then for a driver
called the "God Foot,"
wouldn't that be far too little planning?
Well...
I think Hoshino has some sort of
plan in mind. I can't help but feel that.
If it's some sort of loophole in the rules...
then what on earth could it be?
Hyaa!
Forget it. I don't know what
kind of power that thing packs,
but there's absolutely no way
I'd let you pass me now!
That's the shape of it, eh?
I've got the general picture.
What is this? This mood like
people are expecting something...
Gimme a break. There's no
reason anything'll happen.
As a racer with experience
at running mountain passes,
I can at least say that for sure!
There's no way he could pull
ahead on a course like this!
Soon they'll be here at the turnaround
point, the yellow FD still in the lead.
They'll circle around this
pylon and head back down.
In that instant, Keisuke's
victory will be certain!
The top is just ahead. We'll be up there soon.
I can do it. This race is mine!
They're here! There they are! They're comin' in!
Okay!
They're comin' in side-by-side!
What are you doing?!
Hoshino's out in front!
It can't be. Don't tell me...
He was waiting for the instant when
the turn toward the downhill begins?!
What a crazy thing to do! That GT-R
came charging in without hesitation.
If Keisuke hadn't moved, it would've
been a terrible head-on crash!
Screw you! You'd do something like this?!
No, that's not right. They may
have looked about the same,
but our opponent entered the spin
turn a split-second earlier.
That's where the lead
position was taken from us.
I timed it so we'd be side-by-side
when we came out of the corner.
That was quite satisfactory, if I say so myself.
He got me. Now all I can do is overtake him!
It looks like Keisuke had the tables
turned on him at the turnaround point.
As I thought. Sure enough,
he did not pass up his opportunity.
This puts us at an overwhelming disadvantage.
All we can do now is bet on Keisuke's
natural ability to spring into action.
The rougher and more
heated this race becomes,
the higher the probability.
The more turbulent this is,
the greater our chances.
The one thing that worries
me is Ko falling silent.
Don't get too heated.
Drifting, huh? If that's how you want to play it...
What?!
Hoshino pulled ahead at the turnaround point!
Yeah!
I knew there was no way he'd lose!
Oh. So that was Hoshino's plan?
There they are!
Drift vs. drift?!
The GT-R is a 4WD, right?!
This thing's gettin' more and more heated!
What's goin' on with Hoshino?
What on earth is going on?
It could be that this is
according to Hoshino's plan.
Without a doubt, his tires have lost their grip,
making it easier to understeer
on downhill corners.
If he fishtailed the rear section at corner entry,
he could control the front-end push.
At first glance it appears utterly reckless,
but there's sound reasoning behind it.
Also...
If the GT-R drifts its big rear section
on already narrow streets,
it takes up that much more space,
effectively blocking the way...
...creating a barricade that
stretches the width of the road.
I hadn't planned on gettin' so flashy,
but if my opponent is gonna take
things this far, I can't back down now!
This is a different world, beyond reason.
And I won't let anyone criticize!
I just don't understand it.
Mr. Joshima, they're drifting.
Both Mr. Hoshino's GT-R and the pursuing FD...
Isn't the sensible thing to do to race
with a little more care for their tires?
Well, sometimes the only ones who
understand are the people holding the wheel.
Sure enough, they're cut from the same cloth.
I guess we just keep quiet and watch these
two fools engage in their battle of wills.
They're both up on the main stage now...
There is a logical reason for
Kozo Hoshino's repeated use of drift.
However, there is no such
reason supporting Keisuke's.
Put simply, it is the willfulness of one
who drives a rear-wheel vehicle.
Keisuke has responded with
competitive spirit rather than reasoning...
Fight drift with drift.
There is one aspect in which Kozo Hoshino
and Keisuke closely resemble each other.
Keisuke's actions make
no disguise of his feelings,
which in this case fuels
Hoshino's fighting spirit.
That is what suddenly made
this a battle of drifting.
My tires!
Ko is probably enjoying this
more than he can stand.
But Ko, this turn of events
will count more against
the GT-R, with its heavy frame.
Drawing this out would be
disadvantageous in terms of tires...
He should've known that from the start.
They're not too far off now. I'm sure
Keisuke has no intention of quitting.
We still don't know what will happen
until that goal line is crossed!
Dammit! It's overshooting all on its own!
--All right!
--Yes!
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie