"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let's look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let's go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
It's the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let's look for explosive thrills, it's the time!
"Act 9: The New Eight-Six"
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
It's so cold!
Dad, shouldn't we pull out the electric heater?
Laziness makes you cold, so stay busy.
You sound just like my P.E. teacher.
What?
You fixed it already?
Does it really work?
Of course it works.
I put in a new engine.
You can use it for deliveries again.
I have something to tell you, Takumi.
I had to use your hard-earned
money to fix this car...
...so it's half yours from now on.
What?!
But I'm the one who broke
the car! Are you sure?
A mistake didn't cause it,
so it wasn't your fault.
I used up the savings not only
from your part-time job,
but also from your morning deliveries.
You're entitled to feel attached to it.
I see.
Anyway, I've already made up my mind.
So go on and finish the deliveries.
Okay.
It feels weird.
Your eye level is lower
because of the bucket seat.
After a while, you won't notice it.
The steering is heavier.
So is the clutch.
When you put the clutch in...
...that's when you first notice the weird feeling.
Good luck with the Mercedes guy.
The Mercedes guy... The Mercedes guy...
The Mercedes guy...
How did he find out?
Of all people...
...how does he know about this?
This is awful. It's just too awful!
If this is a dream, please let me wake up!
It's so hard to control!
What the heck?!
What?! Your Eight-Six is fixed already?
Really?
Have you taken it on a test drive?
--How was it?
--How?
It did work.
--Oh, man!
--We know that!
That's not what we meant!
I bet they'll go nuts...
...because this new engine is unbelievable!
What's the new engine like?
Is it fast?
Oh, boy...
You'll be disappointed if I tell you this.
It may be slower than the old one.
It lacks power.
♪ I'm a lonely driver... ♪
♪ The king of the pass... ♪
Hey! That's a cool Eight-Six!
I haven't seen that car before.
Hey, Takumi!
Why do you say that the
new engine lacks power?
It just feels slower.
It can't be slower.
Your dad said it was a premium engine.
He said that?
I don't think so.
It's hard to control.
But it's hard to control because it has
so much more power, right?
I know it's a good engine.
Boss, do you know what kind of engine it is?
What?
Have you driven it?!
No, I, uh, haven't driven it.
I don't know what's going on, actually.
What's going on, Bunta?
That engine has less power?
Wow! It has a roll bar and a bucket seat!
This is so cool!
If I had an Eight-Six, it would be like this!
Hey! It has a boost meter, too!
That means this Eight-Six is...
...a turbo!
This is the best!
I so want this Levin! I want it!
Hey!
What are you doing with my car?
Well, you know, I was just...
...admiring your car.
Admiring it?
It's just a domestic car!
Tell me the truth!
Were you messing with it because
it doesn't have a Gunma plate?
Are you kidding, or what?!
Why would I do that?!
You don't need to yell at me! What's with you?!
For your information, I just love Eight-Sixes!
Don't insult me! Gunma people
don't mess with other people's cars.
What a rude girl!
Kazumi!
I found the hotel where our aunt works.
--What's the matter?
--Nothing.
Gunma stinks!
What? You just got here.
You'll be here for a while,
so try to be a little more patient, okay?
Your impatience worries me a little, you know?
It's only temporary, but you'll
be dealing with customers.
Don't make our aunt look bad.
I won't.
Don't get upset with rude customers.
Then promise me that you won't stop by Akagi
for a spin on your way back home.
I won't.
Not on a crowded Sunday.
You can't lie to me.
I know you're planning to race
Akagi's white FC someday.
That FC...
I couldn't say.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
About the new engine...
Takumi said it was slower than the old one.
Yeah.
Did you set it up that way?
Why would I do such a laborious thing?
I don't get it, then!
But it makes sense.
What Takumi said is right.
What?
You really don't get it, Yuichi?
It's so simple.
What is?
Just think about it.
I'm busy, so I'm hanging up.
Hey, wait! Bunta?!
What's with him?!
It's been days!
Darn! I still can't control it!
I'm gonna be late for work!
It's that rude girl.
"Taiyaki
Fresh Baked and Delicious"
I'll take six.
Five in the bag, and I'll eat one now.
Okay. That'll be 660 yen.
Careful, it's hot.
Delicious!
Oh, no! I'm ten yen short.
I'm sorry, but can I give you a 10,000 yen bill?
That's too big.
--I don't have change for that.
--Really?
Oh, no...
Take it.
Thank you! I'll pay you back later.
That's okay. It's only ten yen.
I want to! I wouldn't feel good otherwise.
Where can I find you?
I work at the gas station down the street.
I started a temp job at
the hotel where I'm staying.
My aunt works there.
I'm running an errand for her.
Sorry about the other day.
--You're nice.
--Well...
I was actually happy,
because people rarely
compliment my brother's old Levin.
It's your brother's?
I don't know anyone in Gunma,
so I was feeling bored...
...and kind of lonely.
Let's be friends.
I'm Kazumi Akiyama.
Uh, I'm Itsuki Takeuchi.
See you soon, Itsuki.
This sensation...
Could it be...
...that?!
Akina's Eight-Six is back in action?
Kenta thinks he saw it drive by.
He saw the "Fujiwara Tofu Shop" sign.
I wonder if he put in a new engine.
We should find out.
Yeah.
There!
That engine sound...
Big brother, wasn't that...?
Yeah. He isn't used to it yet...
...but that car's been
revived as a scary monster.
It took you a long time. Anything happen?
No.
After the deliveries,
I drove the pass a few times.
I used a lot of gas.
Sorry.
I don't mind.
--Dad?
--Yeah?
Cornering with this car is tough.
What I could do before
isn't as easy with this car.
It's upsetting me.
I've been trying different things,
but it's not going very well.
Good attitude.
He's trying to compensate with his technique
instead of changing the suspension settings.
Go ahead and struggle for a while.
Trial and error is an important process.
In time, this car will improve your
technique without your even knowing.
This car will be a tool for you
to move up to the next level.
Oh, there you are!
Hey! Kazumi!
I'm here to pay you back.
Here.
Now we're even.
Yeah.
--You really saved me yesterday!
--Oh, yeah?
Hey, who is that?
See you at 7:30!
Who is that cutie, Itsuki?
She's, uh, a friend.
A friend?!
You said we racers don't need girls!
What happened to "Lonely Driver Itsuki"?
Don't just laugh it off!
What?
No way. It's a Levin!
Is this really your car?
It sure is.
Oh, me?
I graduated from high school this spring,
so I'm a year older than you.
What did you do after you graduated?
I got a job, sort of.
But I didn't like it there.
My brother often tells me
that I'm a little impatient.
The one with the Eight-Six?
Yeah. You may think it's odd,
but we were always together,
even when he went racing.
They say he's the fastest
downhill racer in Saitama.
Wataru's downhill is--
My big brother's name is Wataru.
They say Wataru's downhill is sharp.
He's starting to use me
as an excuse to come to Gunma.
He may be racing at some pass right now.
I'm sorry.
It's our policy not to race in Akagi.
Is it because I drive an Eight-Six?
No, it's because it's too easy.
Racers in Gunma know that the
Red Suns don't race on their own turf.
It's nothing personal.
I'll tell you one thing.
We take Eight-Six racers seriously.
Gunma's Eight-Six is a downhill specialist.
He has never lost a race.
What?
Against any type of car.
Any type of car?
Right.
Then you're qualified to
determine if I'm faster than he is.
--What?
--It's okay, Kenta.
We don't race here.
I don't know who you are,
but come back in ten years if
you want to talk trash to Keisuke.
Fine, then.
I hate to do this, but you've left me no choice.
If you're that desperate,
I'll play with you a little!
That's more like it.
Please teach that rude jerk a lesson!
That sound... it's a turbo!
He followed me out of the corner.
That car's power isn't ordinary.
Is it really an Eight-Six?
I don't know how powerful it is,
but that much power will impede his control.
That car is like a loose cannon,
but he's controlling it!
I just can't keep up!
Darn!
I don't know as much as my brother,
but this guy is very skilled.
I shouldn't mess around.
Get serious... or I'll pass you!
Man, this doesn't look good.
Luckily, we weren't going too fast.
Yeah.
I should put a warning reflector up.
I'd hate for another car to crash into us.
Yeah.
Whenever I turned around
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
The warm wind
Comes back quietly and tenderly
And as I gaze at the sky alone
You smile down upon me
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory
Hearing the rumors,
Wataru approaches Takumi!
What will happen?
Next on Initial D: Second Stage...
"The Eight-Six Turbo!"
Don't miss it!