"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
Furihodokitakute, hazusu mune no safety
Yureru omoi o tsukamaete, sou, kisu o shite
Sou, itsumo pressure,
gyuugyuu ni yurareta densha
Yodonda meshita hitogomi kara mitero ze tte
Itsuka, hora denkousekka
Tobidashi ano checker flag
te ni ireru, sou shinjite
Dakitai yume ga mieru deshou
Kono ude ni kanjitai, your soul
This moment I can feel, zenchou tourai o shiru
Kono mama iku ze, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
"Skyline"
Really?!
We did it! Keisuke won!
--Yeaah!
--Yes.
The distance was a little hard to tell.
Shall we go for a third round?
Nah. I clearly lost.
Plus, my tires are finished.
I'm real sorry about before. I couldn't
hold on and ran into ya on the inside.
Once I was in the drift, the car wouldn't
respond to my more delicate handling.
Still, that felt great. It's been a long time!
I could forget everything but battling
it out with the steering wheel!
Good job.
Give it your all out there, Jo.
These guys are better than we thought.
Yes, I know.
Sure is hot tonight...
And it looks like it's going to get hotter.
"Act 22: The Sorcerer of the Single-Handed Steer"
--Good night.
--Good night, sir!
--It's so hot!
--It really is hot today, huh?
At this rate, the Project D team will
have it rough out on the road, huh?
'Cause it gets this hot even at night.
Let's go hang out somewhere
that's nice and air conditioned.
Yeah.
Back from the dead!
Uh-huh. So, where's Takumi headed to
in the middle of this scorching heat?
Ibaraki.
According to Kenji, he's facing
a really tough opponent.
Speak of the devil. It's Kenji!
Hey!
I see this wretched heat isn't
keeping you busy at all.
You're one to talk. You two fools are
lollygagging around here as well.
Lollygagging?
That's, like, so ohmigod, right?
--Right?
--I know!
--I guess.
--And then, like, Ryoko was all...
Aah, why are we three the only group of guys?
Even though there should be the same
number of girls as guys out there...
Eew, you perv!
Yeah. What's more, it's the
same group as always...
They call summer the season of youth...
Should we three guys be spending it
lollygagging in a place like this?
No, we shouldn't! But what's the alternative?!
No need for you to get upset, is there?
--Where do you want to go next?
--Somewhere we can be alone.
For real?!
Dammit! This is makin' my blood boil!
Now, now. Iketani, Kenji.
For a racer, women are just...
They sure would be nice.
Right about now, Takumi's racing intently...
Should we really be doing something like this?
We don't have any excuse, do we?
No, we don't.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Yessir!
Please choose your starting
position for the first race.
Maybe I'll come from behind...
I'll follow for the first race.
Understood. Fujiwara!
You lead for the first race!
I'm Toshiya Joshima. A pleasure.
Takumi Fujiwara.
You mind if I ask you something?
Uh, please do.
I'd like to know why someone
your age decided on an Eight-Six.
I'm extremely curious to hear the reason.
Well, it's not as if I actually chose this car...
It was originally my father's.
Your father's?
Yes.
It's been at our house since I was a kid.
This was all we had, so it's
the only car I ever drove.
I'm attached to it, and drove it a lot
illegally before I got my license.
Interesting.
So, your father taught you driving
techniques before you had your license?
Yeah... That's about how it worked.
I'd like to meet your father. I have
a feeling we could be friends.
You'll allow me to do my
best as your opponent.
By all means.
Ryosuke, we can start anytime.
I see.
--Listen closely, Fujiwara.
--Okay.
I'll be clear. This is the fiercest opponent
you've yet faced. He has no weaknesses.
At present, there is only one
piece of advice I can give:
Endure.
Even if you can't win, you should be able
to make it so that you aren't beaten.
I will give you additional
advice when the time is right.
As much as possible, look at the
course and not the other driver.
He is a ghost.
Don't forget.
Begin it, Fumihiro.
Okay.
All right, beginning the countdown!
Five! Four! Three!
--Two! One!
--Ghost?
Go!
Got it.
The first downhill race has started.
I'm counting on you, Jo.
By the honor of the man they call the God Arm,
please make this a one-win, one-loss draw.
Keisuke.
Do you think Fujiwara will be all right?
Worryin' about it won't
change anything, will it?
This is his race now.
According to Mr. Toudou,
this guy Toshiya Joshima has settled
into a particular sort of technique.
Call it a habit or whatever,
but he'll keep his left hand on the
gearshift and steer only with the right.
What kind of merit would that have?
Me, I've gotta use both hands
to steer or it doesn't feel right.
Wait a minute. Steering with just one hand...
Wouldn't there be corners where there's
not enough steering angle to turn?
Actually, aren't most corners
on a mountain pass like that?!
That's why Toshiya Joshima,
the sorcerer of steering,
is called the God Arm.
He's fast! Unbelievably so!
As I thought, he's quite good.
Oh. It's probably drift.
It would take incredibly high skill,
but if he used a zero-counter drift from
the minimum possible steering angle...
That's not it. Toshiya Joshima does not drift.
It's not drift and it's not grip...
Apparently, his racing
is something in-between.
Huh? In-between drift and grip?
So it's neither of the two?
"Steep Curve"
Everyone seems to think Jo's one-handed
steer is some off-the-wall technique,
but it's grounded in solid principles.
What it boils down to is, how do you
turn along a slight steering angle?
Jo has spent more than 20 years
pursuin' that question.
He's combined various techniques,
and after all that trial and error,
he got to where he is now.
He'll emphatically say it's not drift
and it's not grip, but if ya ask me...
...it's the perfect drift.
The really high-level techniques
are the ones that're hard to see,
and just look sort of plain.
Tires do their best work
when the G-forces kick in and you're
not sure if they'll grip or slide out.
Yeah...
I think he makes his car slide just
enough that you can't tell by looking.
From a logical standpoint,
that sort of makes sense.
I get it. So that's what it means
to be in between drift and grip?
Mr. Toudou knows full well.
The Toudou School and Purple Shadow
have been rivals for many years.
Back when we were active in the scene,
we used to have racing meets
all the time on the circuits.
To think that the top members of Purple
Shadow would actually do a street race...
If we'd let this chance slip by us,
we'd never get a second one.
The God Foot Kozo Hoshino...
...and the God Arm Toshiya Joshima are two
men whose racing we should watch closely,
I'd say this means.
Fumihiro, do you remember
Shingo Shoji of the Night Kids,
whose specialty was the
duct tape death match?
Shoji... Oh, I think he was the guy
who'd fasten his right hand to
the steering wheel with duct tape.
This would let him turn only within
a set range of steering angles.
In other words, his turns had to
rely on accelerator handling.
It could be that Toshiya Joshima's
single-handed steer
is an extension of that technique...
Or rather, its ultimate,
most thoroughly perfected form.
But why bother? Aside from having his
left hand able to perform all shifting,
what's the benefit?
The answer to that is in the realm of
sensitivity unique to Toshiya Joshima.
While undoubtedly an
unorthodox driving style,
some of the WRC's top drivers
have utilized a single-handed steer.
It's exactly the same! This feeling...
A pressure, a kind of
overwhelming tingling sensation.
It's just like that of a certain bastard
of an old man who drives an Impreza...
It's so alike it makes me sick!
"Touge Tunnel Project
To be implemented soon"
What I think about how it's going?
Yes.
That's neither here nor there.
This won't be a race that'll be
decided in one or two rounds.
Oh, really?
The course itself isn't that long, and
there aren't many proper straightaways.
It's going to have to be
something of a drawn-out race.
But if...
If there's anything that could
decide this race quickly...
It would be Fujiwara losing.
Put another way, unless he digs in for the
long haul, he'll have no chance of winning.
That's the kind of race
you should think of this as.
The key will be the second round,
when the opponent goes first.
If Fujiwara can hang in there,
tough it out somehow...
This will become one
tangled marathon of a race.
Anyone with a bit of knowledge
would think that about the first round.
No matter how heated things
look like they're getting,
they're still just trading light jabs.
--Awesome!
--So fast!
They're both fast! Joshima of Purple
Shadow and Project D's Eight-Six!
I've never seen such fast cornering before!
It's awesome... An all-out downhill battle!
The first round will be over soon.
Dammit! He did nothing but pressure me,
and I couldn't do anything!
This first round went as planned,
with me getting a good, long look at you.
There they are.
They're right on top of each other!
There's no gap at all!
Beginning the countdown!
Five... Four... Three...
Two... One...
Go!
It looks like the second round's begun.
Yeah.
This second round is the critical stage, huh?
And we're following this time.
Fujiwara's tenacity when coming
from behind really is second-to-none...
He hasn't lost once from behind,
no matter who he's faced.
Still, Keisuke said "if"
Fujiwara can hang in there.
Meaning, he must be facing
an incredible opponent!
The S2000 really is a difficult car to master,
but its racing capabilities are second-to-none.
Mr. Toudou says it's even faster
at cornering than an NSX.
Having a driver like Toshiya
Joshima behind the wheel
means there's no way it
could lose to an Eight-Six.
Yeah, I wonder...
Maybe he won't even have to do anything
special, just draw out the car's potential,
and that will be enough to catapult it into
a zone where the Eight-Six can't keep up.
I'd like to believe that's how
the second round will be.
But what's "normal" in a situation
like this isn't normal at all...
Because both drivers are
anything but ordinary.
Especially the driver of that Eight-Six, huh?
He has a genius-like ability you'd
have to race him to understand.
What's more, it's perfectly suited
for that car, the Eight-Six.
In a sense... he was born for the
purpose of becoming that car's driver!
Its engine is not just an NA,
it is an F20 capable of
producing 125 hp per liter.
The F20 is a VTEC unit that boasts enough
power output to put racing engines to shame
and most assuredly poses a
threat to Fujiwara. However,
the S2000's true value lies
in its handling capabilities.
Its mid-front mounted engine
achieves optimal 50:50
front-to-rear weight distribution,
and its rigid High X-Bone Frame is such that
one forgets the car's open-body structure.
In addition to its compact and lightweight
in-wheel, double wishbone suspension,
it boasts heightened racing
capabilities exhaustively refined
through traditional means rather than
a modern electronic control system,
such that it can even beat high-tech cars
fitted with turbochargers or 4WD.
However, as a car, it is limited to
the smallest percentage of drivers.
In other words, you have to be extremely
talented in order to make full use of it?
Experiencing the "limited domain"
that is the S2000 is, one could say,
the privilege of a handful of
drivers blessed with great skill.
And "God Arm"Toshiya
Joshima is one such driver.
Fujiwara's gone head-to-head with
a really troublesome opponent...
I'm pretty interested in this second round.
We'll get the general idea of what
kind of script Jo's thought up for this.
You say "script," but...
Mr. Joshima is in front, so why not just
lose his opponent and be done with it?
Nah. You wouldn't think it,
but he's actually a bit perverse.
The more talented his opponent, the more
that little devil of his comes out.
If Jo put his mind to it
and went on the offensive,
I bet he could outdistance any opponent.
Whatever else, he knows
this course inside and out.
Not even a pro racer could
beat us in that respect.
This is tough. I'm trying my hardest,
but he's still a good distance ahead.
I'll say this for the sake of Jo's reputation.
If there's no winner in this second round,
I think the script he's planned
is to win not when he's leading,
but when he's following.
What?! Even for Mr. Joshima,
that would be impossible!
This course has no straight
angles and is all corners,
so overtaking someone would be...
Nah, I bet that's probably
what he intends to do.
'Cause he's perverse.
I didn't notice when I was in front...
...but his lines are different!
There are points where his line
doesn't match what I'd thought best.
His timing when he reaches
the in-line is earlier or later...
It's different from normal theory!
But here, is his way the right choice?
If not... I can't explain this speed!
Ryosuke... What you told
Fujiwara is really bothering me.
As much as possible, look at the
course and not the other driver.
Your opponent is a ghost.
Fujiwara's greatest weapon is his
ability to be behind an opponent
and "absorb" his speed, so why...?
And what did he mean by "ghost"?
I don't get it. How can he be
so fast using a line like that?
Senjou ni saita rose,
for the reason they don't know
Mae ni shika susumenai caterpillar
ga kyou mo fumitsubushita
Yo, hates and pain, nikushimi dake fuyashite
Hates and pain, sonna sesou, live eizou
Dakishimete ite ne, motto tsuyoi te de
Fuan na yoru ni anata no koe
(For the reason they don't know)
Sekai wa itsuka chi o nagashite ite
(All around the world)
Sonna news o wasuresasete yo, wakaritakunai
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte
Sakusou suru jouhou wa
mass media-tachi ni mou hora
Ressei ga noukou na
taikyoku no urei o tsutaedasu
Risei wa kanensei,
yokushiryoku o kaiteru nenrei, yeah
Dokomade senrei uketsuzukeru zenshin zenrei
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Tayorinai kowaresou na fune koideru nara
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Aa semete mou sukoshi,
uso demo ii, yasashiku utatte