"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Blastin' off to the wicked show,
splitting the air with that sputterin' noise
Let's go, ride that thing
to the throwdown party
Determination that never
backs down, the dogfight
I wanna feel the thrill of the
screams in the phat red zone
A brief flash, like a comet
The brightness lasts a second, but I don't care
Someday, I wanna tell of that
glimpse of precious scenery
Yes, right now it's a purely instinctual dogfight
If it's a thrilling dream
you're after, it's right here
A wind that shatters the heat haze, backfire
C'mon, throw away yesterday,
right now it's a rocket dance (Dogfight!)
If the wish you can't scream aloud hurts,
then hurry and come here
You're big time gambler
Foolishness is a beautiful contour
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Tha loud sound is everywhere
Sideswipe, a 5G heavyweight
Runnin' right to the line, a hair's breadth
between offense and defense
Ba-ba-baaam!
Yo, I can step on the gas for
an easy victory, I still got it
Hey, Takumi!
You have the day off today?
--Yeah.
--Takumi!
I finally did it!
Did what?
The turbo, man, the turbo!
I told you before, right?! That I was
gonna add a turbo to the Levin!
Oh...
It's at the shop right now.
Aah, I can't wait till the day I get it back!
So Itsuki's Eight-Five will get an upgrade,
going from a slug to a plain old snail, huh?
What do you think you're saying, Iketani?
I'll have you know they're expecting
it'll go to about 180 horsepower!
In which case, it could even keep
up with your S13 on the uphill!
It'll have that much output?
A turbo sure is incredible.
Anyway, Takumi...
I heard from Kenji. You even beat
those guys from the Toudou School.
Yeah, somehow.
And it seems that Keisuke Takahashi
also won the uphill timed race!
The Toudou School couldn't do a thing, huh?
Project D sure is incredible.
I wonder if my Eight-Five turbo will
get me scouted for Project D, too.
Not gonna happen!
Tomo!
I heard you all lost.
I wanna hear the details.
"Act 5: The Starting Line to Victory"
Well, I think this incident will
be a good lesson for them.
This kind of motivation is important, too.
As long as you keep racing, you're gonna
run into different kinds of walls.
For both Sakai and Daiki, this was
an encounter with one such wall.
It's only the guys who suffer through it
who can climb that wall and move onward.
When you hit a wall you can't climb,
that's when you've reached
your limits as a driver.
But Tomoyuki...
You should still be able to climb any
number of the walls you're hitting now.
This is embarrassing.
You could tell, could you, Sir?
If I couldn't tell that much, I wouldn't
be fit to run the Toudou School.
My "wall" is pretty intense.
I've been made keenly aware that
in racing, having funds is everything.
After losing on the straightaway,
I pushed myself too far,
making stupid mistakes
or getting into trouble.
The team's morale is getting worse
and with this economy, the sponsors
aren't lining up. The future looks grim.
This may be one wall I'm
powerless against on my own.
I really don't know what I should do.
That's where you're wrong, Tomoyuki.
You've forgotten something very important.
This is a problem I can guarantee lies with you.
--Don't you get it?
--Sir...
Why don't you give street racing a try?
Are you being serious?
You're the one who said not to do anything
stupid out on the street once turning pro!
Sometimes you hafta be an idiot.
Just think of it like you'll be pullin' a fast
one on those street-racin' amateurs!
You'll probably find the answer
you're lookin' for now...
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
"Homemade Taste for Health and Beauty"
"Chilled Tofu with Dinner"
How is it?
It's got pretty good balance.
I did a light run there and back,
and compared to when the
engine was first changed out,
you can charge downhill and it feels good.
The suspension's a little tricky,
but it's come a long way.
I bet this has made it easier to run races, too.
No, it friggin' hasn't. The guys
we race keep getting better.
I feel like there's no way
I can keep on winning...
Of course not. It's about time
you try losin' for a change.
You can learn a lot from losin'.
"Try losing"? How can you say it like that?
We're winning these as a team,
so I can't just go losing, now can I?
Talk all you want, but no one
can perform above his means.
A car's got a basic limit
it can't go faster than, too.
Yeah, but still...
It'd probably be a load off your mind
if you thought about it that way.
Still, this car...
I said we could share it, but it feels
like you've completely taken it from me.
It's not even fun for me to work on it anymore.
Maybe I'll buy one, a different one.
A-Are you serious?
I'll ask Masashi. If a bargain comes up,
I'll have him send it my way.
What do you want to buy? What make?
It's a secret.
Big brother, I'm coming in.
Okay.
You said we got a rematch
challenge from the Toudou School?
From one of its graduates.
--A graduate?
--Yes.
We're accepting, right?
"Akechidaira
Panorama Restaurant House"
--Is this Ryosuke?
--Yes.
This is Kyoichi Sudou.
Kyoichi? This is a surprise.
You got a rematch challenge from a
graduate of the Toudou School, right?
You'd be better off not accepting it.
I know you're not the type of guy to listen
when told not to do something, but listen up.
Your challenger this time is a pro racer!
His name's Tomoyuki Tachi,
and he's in a league all his own, even
compared to other Toudou School students.
Even the mighty Project D can't
be 100% assured of winning.
If there's no way that this
can be avoided... Ryosuke.
You do it!
As long as the course is the street, and as
long as there's even a sliver of a chance,
you need to race this yourself.
Incredible. The Toudou & Co. demo
cars are fast enough as it is,
but having Tomo behind the steering wheel...
I got goose bumps just watching.
Just once, I'd like to be in
the passenger seat next to him.
It's like he's in a whole other zone we
could race our entire lives and never reach.
Seeing this, I could care less whether
it's a revenge match against Project D,
I just definitely have to watch his next race!
An all-out street race with
pro race driver Tomoyuki Tachi...
There'll never be a second chance to see it!
How is it?
Very nice. I have no complaints.
Any problems down the road will
be because of human emotion...
Or rather, driver's preference.
I'll make it fit your preference.
What do you want?
Really? But...
...is it necessary to go that far
when the car already has such
incredible racing capabilities?
Even though you said the
challengers are amateurs...
It may be just a street race,
but if you don't give your all,
there's no point in doin' it.
Listen, Tomoyuki...
Don't think about needless details,
and just treat this as if it were a real race.
Show me the best job
you're capable of right now.
Understood. If you're going
to be that adamant about it,
I have a small request to
make about the underbody.
Please retune it so that the rear comes
out a little more when entering corners.
The way I drive now,
that will trim my race time.
Okay, understood. No problem.
It sure does give off a different
impression, doesn't it?
Just with one new hood...
Based on Ryosuke's advice, I've tried
to make the Eight-Six more lightweight.
Going forward, we plan to try
several such small modifications.
Everyone, gather round.
The meeting will now begin.
This is footage of the race
course shot just today.
If you watch this, I think you'll understand.
This particular stage is a mix,
half uphill and half downhill.
In that case, who runs it, me or Fujiwara?
We will decide that once we reach the course.
Both cars will do a practice run, and I will
review the results to make my decision.
What the hell? It's gonna be me,
of course! I'm the ace driver!
This is important, so I'll say it up front:
our opponent is from the Toudou School.
What's more, he's an established pro racer.
A pro?! No way!
No matter how you look at it,
this is a bad idea, Ryosuke.
Our guys will run right into his traps!
That's right! This is playing dirty!
There will be no way of knowing
unless we challenge him.
I've thought it over,
and decided that we shall do it.
We shall never run away from any opponent.
That is the motto of Project D!
Let me do it, brother.
If the stage is a mix of uphill and downhill,
then with its level of power, the FD should
have the advantage over the Eight-Six.
That's right!
Keisuke. Do not make me
say the same thing twice.
As I said, I will decide who races
once we arrive at the course!
Tomo.
Ah. Daiki.
Project D will start their practice runs tonight.
What will you do? Would you
like to go take a look later?
They'll be racing till close to dawn,
tuning their cars while running the course--
It's like they're playing racecar.
They're doing the same thing we
normally do when racing a circuit, eh?
To be honest, I don't really
know what Mr. Toudou is thinking.
I think he knows I'm stressed
and is probably trying to give
me a chance to snap out of it.
The thing is, there's no reason for me
to look forward to some street race.
I'm only doing this because I
think it's best to do what he says.
And since I've decided to do it, I won't pull
any punches, even against an amateur.
You all just watch closely and see
how big a difference there is
between pros and amateurs!
This is a tough course that
incorporates all different types.
Cars' condition, drivers' techniques...
This course will require the best of both.
As always, run five races at 80%.
This is not the Toudou School's course,
but they should already
have raced it before us.
Concentrate, and head out!
Keisuke certainly is taking this seriously.
Yes, he is.
I say we take our time with it.
I don't know whether we'll race or not,
but we should at least
get everything done right.
--Okay.
--As always...
...our real enemy is the course.
Here I go.
Ryosuke...
This isn't like you, heading out
alone to scout out the course.
What's more, taking the FC with you...
There is no special meaning in
my having brought my own car.
The important thing was simply to grab
the steering wheel and know the course.
--However, it...
--What is it?
On the contrary, it has
made me more confused.
Fumihiro, you give the orders in my stead.
The same routine as always,
so there should be no problems.
What?! And what are you going to do?
Sleep.
H-Hey!
I've been absorbed with
a clinical pathology report
and have just remembered I've worked
until the early hours for three days now.
I thought my head was
operating rather sluggishly.
Do not wake me.
I get it.
Not only are there steep ups and downs,
there are so many variables to this
course that it's hard to keep balanced.
I guess that's what my brother meant
when he said this was a tough course.
I wonder how my skills will
stack up against a pro racer.
This is my best chance to test it out!
How on earth is this going to turn out?
I'm really worried about this...
There it is again.
That old Fumihiro anxiousness.
That's not it. This time,
something is really strange.
And I've known him for a long time.
But...
He would never use the Eight-Six
on this course, would he?
Yeah. That's what I'm thinking.
What are you planning, Ryosuke?
No... It couldn't be!
It's finished.
All done, Keisuke.
Okay.
"Italian Fair"
My back hurts!
You can't get a good night's
sleep in a car, can you?
Ryosuke's pretty incredible
about that, isn't he?
He can sleep soundly and not wake up at all!
Our great leader...
That's nothing to make fun of, Matsumoto!
I swear! Only just yesterday, he let
us know just how important he is.
An organization can't perform
smoothly if its "brain" isn't functioning.
Our spirits are low and
we're operating disjointedly.
And he should know it.
No matter how you look at it,
this time around, it's strange.
What do you mean?
This is just between you and me, Matsumoto.
I think Ryosuke can't come up with
a simulation that will let us win.
After exploring any and all possibilities,
if he still can't find a way we can win...
That's Ryosuke for you.
Configuring the cars should
have taken till morning,
but Ryosuke was somehow able
to do it last night in two hours.
I wondered what was going on
for a while there, but...
Ryosuke sure is incredible!
They're here! The Toudou School!
Bring me a flashlight!
And a jack!
Looks like the boss man
finally showed his face.
I immediately knew which
one was today's driver!
Me, too.
He's different, isn't he?
Keisuke, Fujiwara. Come here a moment.
After reviewing yesterday's data,
I've made my decision.
Today, the Eight-Six will ride.
You, Fujiwara.
Hold on a minute, brother!
I had a better time in the practice runs!
I know that.
Then unless you explain, I can't
accept it. Why the Eight-Six?!
I will explain later. There's
something I must do now, quickly.
Fujiwara.
Get in my car's passenger seat.
I shall lecture you as we ride.
Brother... this isn't right!
Keisuke, don't let it get to you.
What Ryosuke does,
he does for an important reason.
--I know that!
--Keisuke!
And knowing that just
makes it more disgraceful!
A-Awesome!
Just once, I'd like to wear something like that!
Idiot. These are like battle fatigues.
Once you put these on, playtime is over.
You fight, with the pride of a professional.
Tomo.
Even one of our demo cars
will lose to an FD on a straightaway.
Don't let your guard down.
I already have a counter-strategy in mind.
That's why I had the car tuned to my specs.
Just leave the rest to me.
Are the Eight-Six's preparations complete?
It's already done warming up.
It's good to go anytime.
Very well, let's start. Fumihiro.
Got it.
All right, let's begin.
There's plenty of road width,
so we'd like to start
with a simultaneous, side-by-side dash.
Fine. I leave it all up to you.
Understood. Okay, line up your cars!
Hey, what the hell? For real, the Eight-Six?!
Didn't see this one coming, eh?
What's the meaning of this?
They don't disappoint,
those guys from Gunma.
We were 100% sure they'd come with the FD,
meaning they've avoided all our preparations.
To think they'd use some
underpowered Eight-Six...
This is quite the insult to us, and to Tomoyuki.
Still, that makes it all the more interesting.
All right! Starting the countdown!
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
All right! His front section's
pulled halfway ahead!
Which will it be?
Which one will enter the corner first?!
Hey, the coming of a new generation
Calling now for the arrival of a new era
How long are you going to
pretend you've forgotten?
(Tension that seems like it'll
rip my heart) This heartache...
Within those eyes,
something that can't be held back...
(Yeah, this image that won't let me go)
...stares intently at the night
Yes, the two who didn't even know how
to reach out and touch someone's
heart are already, from here...
(Hey, the coming of a new generation,
Check it, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Strike the sleeping dream awake
(Skillz enough to rend the night!)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
A risky tune that rocks the times
Blast my desire
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Calling now for the arrival of a new era,
break what you wanna break)