"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
No oncoming traffic.
You can go all out!
All right! You're doing great, Mako!
Yeah...
What's the matter?
Is something on your mind?
Mako?
It's nothing.
Okay, we're going for another run, Sayuki.
Ah, the weather's awesome.
Yeah, seriously.
It makes me feel like driving somewhere instead of working.
And if we could have a cute girl in our passenger seats...
Woah!
Why are you acting surprised?
How long were you standing there, Kenji-senpai?
What? Am I not supposed to be here?
Well, it's not a problem or anything.
You must be bored.
It's Takumi.
Yo.
Hello.
D doesn't have a race this week, right?
Yeah.
So you're bored too?
Well, it's not like I'm bored, but...
I don't have work today or anything, so...
No problem, no problem.
You came here 'cause you have nowhere better to go, right?
Bullseye.
So how's your job at the shipping company?
Have you gotten used to it?
Yeah, but I've been busy because I'm involved with D.
Hey, tell us about your battle the other day!
What're your feelings about your first victory as a member of Project D?
Well... um...
how should I put it?
It was a relief.
A relief?
What, that's it?
You're not gonna say something like,
"I knew victory was mine at that point"?
I mean,
I just drove like Ryosuke-san told me to.
But I was happy that I won,
even though it was a close battle.
They praised me and said I did well.
Racing outside the prefecture must be a lot of pressure.
It'd be embarrassing if you challenged someone, traveled to their site, and lost.
But I don't even think about things like that when I'm racing.
Instead of things like wanting to win or how I can't afford to lose,
I think more about driving better than I did the last time.
I see.
I haven't even driven on the mountain pass,
much less been in a battle recently...
Say, Takumi, could you lend me some time tonight if you're not busy?
Sure.
I don't have anything going on.
I'm gonna try pushing myself on the mountain pass.
I want you to sit next to me and teach me.
All right?
That's a great idea!
Let's all get together on Akina again and have a blast!
Sure!
Yeah.
I understand.
It really makes me happy.
But...
please let me think about it for a little bit.
It's been awhile since the four of us came up here.
Yeah, I've only been driving on Akina for deliveries these days.
It must be nerve-wracking to drive on a new course for your battles.
Of course.
Here at Akina, we know about the minute details of the course,
but things are completely different when it's your first time on a new course.
Even though it's unavoidable as a member of Project D, it's gotta be scary.
Yeah.
Hey, let's get started soon, Iketani-senpai!
Kenji-senpai and I will stick right behind you in my 85.
If you're too slow, I'm gonna pass you.
Now you've said it.
All right, Takumi, please get in.
Sure.
I'm counting on you.
If something comes to mind, please let me know, no matter how small the detail.
I understand.
Well then, let's see what kind of driving he'll show us.
This is exciting.
Here I go!
He's started!
Don't get left behind.
I know.
Go!
It's the first corner.
A-all right...
Not bad!
H-how was that just now, Takumi?
Both your line selection and timing weren't too bad.
Oh yeah?
His acceleration out of the corner is pretty good!
That's surprising.
All right,
this feels good!
He's good.
Not bad, Iketani!
How's that?
I'm in a groove today.
The upcoming S-curve is gonna be a problem though.
Iketani-senpai tends to push it too far when he gets cocky.
Next up is the S-curve!
Yeah!
Here goes,
the S-curve!
Iketani-senpai,
you're pushing it too much!
O-oh my God!
Oh man,
he's done it.
Well, we knew this would happen.
Thank God, no scratches anywhere.
You should at least change your right rear tire though.
You're right.
I'll change it when I get back.
Man, I still need a lot of practice.
But I guess I couldn't get as good as Takumi, even if I did practice.
It's just like you to be so wishy-washy.
W-what's that supposed to mean?
And you know,
it's about time you got over that other thing too.
What's this all of a sudden?
What am I supposed to get over?
I'll take this opportunity to be blunt.
Forget about Mako-chan.
M-Mako-chan? What about her?
At this rate, you're gonna be single for the rest of your life.
You might lose out when a new opportunity comes your way,
because you're still dragging on about Mako-chan.
Hmm, that's very possible.
Don't exaggerate things like that.
That's bad luck.
I'm not exaggerating.
Watching you seriously worries me.
It's none of your business.
First of all, I don't wanna hear it from another single man.
N-no! Iketani-senpai.
It'll be the end once you say that to Kenji-senpai!
I...
I want a girlfriend too!
But you see...
You can't help what you don't have!
Are you two supposed to be a pair of comedians?
You might have a point.
Either way, you...
What is it?
Isn't your mind still filled with Mako-chan?
Why don't you try contacting her again?
That's impossible. Out of the question.
I wouldn't be in a bind if I could do that.
I've tried many times. I just wuss out at the last second.
Once you miss your chance,
it's over.
No kidding.
I've lost track of how many times I wanted to call Kazumi-chan.
You gradually lose your opportunities to make a move as time goes by...
It's already been half a year since then.
What's the problem with half a year?
It's too late.
There's no way a cute girl like that would stay single for long.
You don't know that.
Mako-chan isn't the same as those typical light-hearted girls.
She wouldn't like it if I called her!
Anyway, it's too late.
I'm convinced of that much.
He's really holding it back.
I guess he needs some fated encounter to break him out.
A day hasn't gone by when I haven't thought of Mako-chan.
I've always thought that I need to apologize about that day.
But you know what, Moon? That's what's so hard about this...
Huh?
Hey, a shooting star!
Man, a memorial service? What a drag.
It's kinda busy.
Is it because it's a holiday?
Say, Koichirou.
Huh?
Is there a rest area coming up?
What?
Can't be helped I guess...
Hurry up, Mom!
We don't have a lot of time.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Sheesh.
The rest of the world is on vacation, huh.
There are couples everywhere I look!
So where do you wanna go after that?
Well, anywhere's fine!
I want to go on a drive with a girl like that too.
To think that the person sitting in the passenger's seat for my roadtrip is my mom...
It's depressing to the megaton-level.
What is it, Mom?
Stare...
Just as I thought! It's Iketani!
S-Sayuki-chan!
I thought it was someone else because you were dressed like that.
Hey Mako! It was Iketani after all!
What are you doing? Come over here already!
Mako-chan?
Hello.
I-it's been awhile.
Hey, what are you getting flustered for?
You sure are a weird man.
W-well...
But man, this brings back memories. How's everyone doing?
Y-yeah...
Takumi-kun's sure amazing!
I've been making sure to check Project D's home page.
Is this reality?
Is that really Mako-chan in front of me?
At 8pm...
I'll be waiting for you under the billboard...
that I first met you at.
Would you like to meet there
and spend the night together somewhere quiet, where we can be alone?
Mako-chan is...
Mako-chan is right in front of my eyes...
Hey now, Iketani,
have you been listening to me at all?
Huh?
What's the matter with you, spacing out like that?
Oh sorry, Sayuki-chan.
I just remembered that there was something I just had to tell Mako-chan.
Huh?!
I... need to apologize to you, Mako-chan.
I'm really sorry
for not making it to our meeting on time.
On that day, the highway was really backed up.
No, it wasn't just that.
It's also because I left late.
Either way, it was past 10
by the time I got to our meeting spot.
What? You can't be serious...
I waited there until 10pm exactly.
No!
You must be joking.
Mako-chan, you waited two hours for someone like me?!
Yes.
So back then...
Could it be that I missed her...
by just a minute or two?!
I really must've been out of luck.
No,
if I hadn't hesitated back then and left sooner...
Koichirou, what are you doing?
Gah!
Mom?!
It's nothing at all!
Hey, we'll be late if we don't get going.
Your aunts will nag us.
I know that!
I'll be right there, so you don't need to come over here. You're embarrassing me!
God dammit!
Why do things always go like this?
My head's starting to spin,
but I'm not gonna back down!
Mako-chan,
I have other things I want to tell you,
but I don't have time today.
Um...
so...
I...
Me too.
I have something I want to tell you too, Iketani-san.
Please give me a call when you get the time.
I'll be waiting.
M-Mako-chan...
I got it! I'll be sure to contact you.
W-well then...
Yeah. See you again.
Hey, what's the matter, Koichirou?
Who's that girl?
Oh, Koichirou...
Hey...
I don't remember how I got back to the car.
My mind was blown for the next 30 minutes.
I have no doubts about it.
This was surely destiny.
What?!
You met Mako-chan?
Is that true, Iketani-senpai?
That's right.
Really, really, really for real.
I can't believe such a coincidence could happen.
I ran right into her at a rest area on the highway.
I see...
I'm convinced for sure this time.
This is my "last chance" that's been given to me by my revered ancestors.
D'oh!
Why is it your ancestors?
Iketani-senpai, I thought your word of choice was "God"?
Not this time, because I was on my way to a memorial service.
This guy has a surprisingly religious side to him.
I can tell that time is being rewound at an incredible pace inside me right now.
It's as if I'm in a time machine!
Huh.
It's as if I can almost go back to under that Kamameshi restaurant billboard.
Thank you, revered ancestors.
I... will never repeat the same mistake!
That's right.
Good luck!
Yeah!
My difficulties of the past six months have drilled into me the importance of acting with courage.
I'll score for sure this time.
I'm going to make a move on Mako-chan!
An aura!
He's emitting an aura!!
I'm not sure what's going on, but you're impressing me.
You've sure grown.
I can't believe you're the same indecisive Iketani.
Yeah, really.
Things really worked out.
I'm happy for you, Iketani.
Good luck this time.
I think you definitely have a shot.
Make sure you get your beloved Mako-chan!
Whoa.
He sure seems confident.
Why?
Why am I hesitating at the last moment?
I can't decide. What am I supposed to do?
Mako.
There's a car coming up.
Okay.
Did you see that?
They were women.
Oh?
Female racers, huh?
Not bad...
but you should be able to go faster.
Okay.
I'll go for another run.
Here they come, here they come.
Hey, missies!
Hey!
You're looking pretty good.
Say, won't you give us a tip or two?
Hey now, you're gonna totally ignore us?
Hah! Acting so stuck up...
you two probably came up here looking for men.
They must be full of themselves just because they can drive a little.
Drive? They're just women in the end.
So what if we're female?
Oh, now she's heating up.
Getting looked down on just for being female pisses us off like nothing else.
How scary!
So, you wanna race us?
A single downhill run.
What do you think, Mako?
If we don't accept, they'll say we ran away because we're women.
That's the way! Let's do it.
Yeah.
We'll go with the leader-chaser format.
Leave the other in the dust or overtake to win.
You guys can lead.
All right.
Let's have them cry like babies.
Let's go then!
Do those women really think that they can beat me?
What should we do when we win?
Maybe we can get some...
Good,
we'll let them run for a little bit.
We'll take it to them at the exit of corner C-121 like usual.
Okay.
They're better than we thought.
Yeah,
but...
they're not anyone I'd lose to.
Hey, start trying a little.
They're sticking right to us!
This is impossible.
What's going on?
Amazing.
You're amazing, Mako.
You're definitely faster than when we raced against Takumi-kun.
Your entry speed into corners,
braking, choice of lines...
they're all perfect.
We don't need to wait until C-121.
I'm passing him on the next corner!
N-no way!
Hey!
Unbelievable!
You've become independent, Mako...
Well then, Kenji, Itsuki,
I'll be on my way.
What?
Already?
You sure are leaving early.
Weren't you meeting her at night?
I can't be careful enough.
After all, it wouldn't be funny if I was late again today.
Even so, don't you think you're going too soon?
It's fine.
Mako-chan waited two hours for me.
If you think about that, getting there two hours early is nothing.
Well, you have a point when you put it that way.
Either way, I'm off.
I can't fail if I'm a step ahead on every move.
Good luck!
Hurrah! Hurrah!
Iketani-senpai!
So he's gone?
Iketani-senpai's unbelievably invested in this.
Yeah,
his last mistake must really have smarted.
I wonder what'll happen...
It makes me nervous.
From what I've heard from Iketani, I think he's got a pretty good chance...
It sounds like Mako-chan was waiting all this time for him to contact her too.
In that case, I think something big's about to happen!
Iketani had a serious crush on Mako-chan, after all...
It'd be like a dream for him if a girl like that became his girlfriend.
The thought of it makes me jealous.
And what about you, Kenji-senpai?
Well to be honest, I used to be really jealous too.
Mako-chan's pretty, after all.
Yeah, really.
That's to be expected of any man!
But you know,
I truly feel like cheering him on now.
I get the feeling that I'll get an earful of bragging on a daily basis,
but I'll take it for his sake.
You're bringing tears to my eye! Now that's a manly friendship!
I just can't turn my back on him.
I worry more about him than about myself.
That's true.
I want Iketani-senpai to find happiness too.
Hey now,
stop cheering for Iketani...
and go find a girlfriend or two for yourselves already.
Youth is short.
Please don't remind me...
My heart is aching.
Kazumi-chan...
And I have no one...
I'm surprisingly calm.
Even though I'm about to confess my feelings to a girl for the first time in my life...
"Please date me."
I just need to say that one sentence.
I have no expectations.
I'm just going to throw my everything at her.
When I think about my half year of constant regret,
I have no doubts holding me back!
Oh boy...
The highway was empty, so I really did get here two hours early.
Oh well.
Now I'll be 100% on time.
When I think about the six months leading up to today,
two hours is nothing.
Excuse me...
Huh?
I saw that you've been sitting there
and don't seem to be in a hurry.
Do you think you could listen to what I have to say?
What?!
Your tour bus left while you were eating some kamameshi?!
That's right.
So I have a favor to ask of you.
I'm very sorry for the trouble, but could you drive me to my hotel in Karuizawa?
I'd really rather not...
I know it's a lot of trouble,
but I'm not familiar with this area and I don't know my left from my right.
I was really starting to get lonely.
Won't you?
As I expected...
Oh man...
I'm starting to feel sorry for him.
I could make it to Karuizawa and back in an hour.
All right,
I'll take you there, gramps.
Huh?
Really?
Oh, thank you.
Please, please, you're a good person!
Okay, hurry and get in.
Okay.
Are you traveling by yourself, gramps?
That's right.
At my age, traveling is about the only fun in your life.
I see...
Spring, summer, fall, winter:
they all have their own flavors.
Now that he mentions it, it's spring already.
The seasons sure go by quickly.
Oh yeah, where in Karuizawa is your hotel, gramps?
Well...
I think I had a pamphlet.
Oh, here it is.
I'd like for you to take me here.
What? Kitakaru Grand Hotel?
Wait a minute, gramps,
although it is Karuizawa, this is in North Karuizawa!
It is Karuizawa, no?
North Karuizawa is in Gunma Prefecture.
It's far away! I can't do that.
I can't say no to that face!
Crap, what a nightmare.
Two hours is barely enough for North Karuizawa...
Please give me a call when you get the time.
I'll be waiting.
M-Mako-chan...
I got it! I'll be sure to contact you.
W-well then...
Yeah.
See you again.
No, but if I give it my best, I'll be able to get back on time.
Gramps, I'm gonna step on it.
Please hang on!
He's not here yet.
I got here first again.
I'm such an idiot!
Half a year ago,
I messed everything up by being two hours late.
Today, I messed up by being two hours early.
This is too much, revered ancestors!
If only I was Takumi at a time like this...
Shit!
Either way, I need to hurry.
If I speed, I should only be about 30 minutes late.
I've trained my driving technique for a time like this!
I... I've done it...
I hit a rock on the shoulder of the road...
and burst a tire.
This is the worst!
I don't have a spare!
You should at least change your right rear tire though.
That's right!
I changed my tire back then and...
Shit!
And at a time like this!
Oh yeah, I need to call her at least...
Why is my battery out?!
I can't waste time here!
Mako-chan, I'm so sorry!
Mako-chan!
I wonder what happened to Iketani-san...?
He's not even calling.
I wonder...
if he forgot?
There's not even a public phone in the mountains like this.
Ouch...
shit.
My heart's about to burst.
I need to find a phone!
A racer is racing down the mountain pass on his own feet...
This isn't even funny!
Hello?
Iketani-san!
I'm so glad to hear from you. Where are you now?
Huh? You have a flat?
I'm really sorry, Mako-chan.
Not only was I late, I had to have you come get me...
I'm really pathetic.
No, please don't worry about it.
We got to meet in the end.
Yeah.
Anyway,
what was it that you wanted to tell me the other day, Iketani-san?
Huh?
That's...
well...
Crap.
I've totally lost my momentum because of how pathetic this situation is.
O-oh yeah,
you said you had something to say too, Mako-chan.
What was it about?
So,
I know it's rather sudden...
but I'm moving to Tokyo.
Huh?
Tokyo?
There was a promotion where a certain publishing company would sponsor an amateur to drive in races for a year...
and that person's experiences would be published in a magazine.
Okay.
I applied for the heck of it,
and for whatever reason...
You got accepted?
That's amazing!
You're going to be a racer!
Although it's just a race series sponsored by car makers with only minimal modifications allowed to vehicles...
That's still amazing!
Yeah,
I hear that a huge sum of money is needed for someone to race for a full year.
I couldn't possibly pay for it myself.
I'm sure.
I really wasn't sure,
but I don't think a chance like this will come my way ever again.
I just had to talk to you about this, Iketani-san.
I think it's all thanks to you...
that I've been able to keep driving this long, Iketani-san.
W-what are you talking about, Mako-chan?
That's not true at all.
No, I don't think I would've had this opportunity
if I hadn't met you, Iketani-san.
Oh man...
Either way, I'm glad to hear that.
Congratulations, Mako-chan.
I can't believe that someone I know is going to become a racer!
I'll brag about you to all my friends when you become famous!
When you do, please give me your first autograph.
Oh no, what are you talking about?
No, I'm serious.
I'm impressed.
You're great, Mako-chan!
She's actually happy about it.
Well yeah,
why wouldn't she be.
Oh, I've been doing all the talking,
but I want to hear what you have to say too, Iketani-san.
W-well,
what I had to say was...
This isn't good.
Compared to what you just told me, it's nothing at all.
That's not true, please tell me!
No, it really was nothing.
See, I wanted to properly apologize for what happened last year.
And it looks like I have your understanding already.
So it's all right.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I actually want to tell her, "Don't go."
But...
But... I can't do it.
Iketani-san...
Mako-chan...
Well, I need to call a tow truck to fix up my car and drive it home.
I'm sorry, but do you think you can drop me off somewhere near a phone?
Okay?
What?!
So you came back without confessing your feelings?
I mean,
how could I say it under those circumstances?
You might say that, but your feelings will never reach her if you don't tell her!
It's okay.
Since Mako-chan's leaving for Tokyo to start racing, confessing my feelings will only trouble her.
But man...
It might make me feel good,
but that's only self-satisfaction.
This was the right choice when you think about the other person's feelings.
Telling her, "Give it your best," and cheering her on is the best I can do.
You're too nice...
Maybe.
That's pretty cold of Iketani.
I thought he had feelings for you too.
I really don't get men.
It's okay, Sayuki.
Now I can move on.
Really?
To be honest, I was worried.
Life in Tokyo seems tough.
I wasn't confident that a wimp like me could become a racer.
I was hesitant until the last minute,
so much so that I could've been swayed had someone told me not to go.
But now I'm embarrassed that I even thought that.
I'm sure Iketani-san was cold to me because he saw through all that.
He gave me a push on the back saying,
"Go give it a try with confidence,"
so that I won't leave any unnecessary regrets over here.
That's what I'd like to think.
That might be true.
He does have an admirable side to him like that.
I get a feeling that's true.
Iketani,
do you really...
have no regrets?
Nope.
It's tough,
but I have no regrets.
This is how it was supposed to be.
Mako...
Good luck!
I certify your talents.
Yeah,
I'll go as far as I can.
I won't hesitate anymore.
So this is the end for Impact Blue.
It's a little sad.
I need to practice more.
I blew my tire at a time like that because my skills are still lacking.
Will you go practice with me, Kenji?
Yeah.
Takumi told me this before,
but I guess I push it too far when I get pumped up.
Next up is the S-curve.
All right!
This is the last run for Impact Blue.
Please take a good look, Sayuki.
Yeah,
give me a refreshing run,
Impact Blue's shooting star.
You still have some work to do. You're ballooning out too far to the outside.
Okay.
But this is great.
When I'm driving like this, I can forget everything.
I might not be as fast as Takumi,
but I must be a racer at heart too.
Street racers...
don't need girlfriends!