"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Information, it's an era
where it travels in a second
But you don't know what
choice you should take
"Money can't buy my love"?
Guys who say that crap
get the lariat three times
Following the manual you just hold each other
You don't realize there is no love
Before you suffocate, shout Ho!!
In the midnight dream
You can't even take a breath
in the sleepless city
Never showing weakness but laughing
Safety is in lies, truth is empty
On the edge of danger,
I wanna shout and break out!
Now we gotta start let's get move!!
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
Frightened by the wide world
We've just begun, now we go
full speed and funky beat
We will shine around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! Here we go unknown world
We newborn travelers
The unfamiliar walk is still charming
The place you want to go is under your feet!
So many people in this world
It's not as if there isn't
backstabbing once in a while
Let's warp past these boring things
And go straight to our reason for living
That's our law!
Please, Takumi!
I couldn't tell this to the others,
but I knew I had to tell you
to make you understand.
I don't like this. She makes me mad.
Takumi, don't be angry at Mako.
She's a good girl.
I don't know why you have to defend her.
I don't get it. You don't owe her anything.
I'm begging you, Takumi.
Hey, Takumi?
You've never been to other passes, have you?
Could you race here?
I wouldn't know until I tried it.
I'll race her.
Really? I'd be so grateful!
I don't know what you and that
girl expect out of this, but...
Takumi...
I'll go to Usui with my Eight-Six.
"Act 17: Sudden-Death Death Match"
Are you serious, Kenji?!
I can't believe Takumi decided to battle it out
with Usui's Sileighty!
Me, neither.
It's not like him to go to
another pass and battle it out.
How did Iketani talk him into it?
I'm not really sure.
Iketani doesn't want to talk about it in detail.
We talked about what would happen
if Takumi raced at another pass, remember?
Yeah.
I can kind of understand Iketani
wanting to see that happen...
But he doesn't have to race
the Sileighty right off the bat.
Is Takumi racing in Usui?
That's right, boss!
And the Sileighty is that good, huh?
She's better than good!
She drifted left and right, and faked
some moves on that narrow road!
Takumi was there, too,
so he knows how good she is.
He'll win, though!
I almost envy your simplicity.
That attendant said that
no local had ever beaten her.
Maybe this time,
it's not about winning or losing for Takumi.
I'm out of cigarettes.
I guess I'll go for a little spin.
What the...?!
My Eight-Six turned into an Eight-Five.
"I borrowed the car.
I left you a replacement.
- Takumi"
Your dad must be freaking right about now!
His Eight-Six turned into my Eight-Five.
Iketani, I want to ask you something.
What?
Which side are you on this time?
Which side?
I just coordinated this race, that's all.
Am I supposed to believe that?
What about Takumi?
Aren't you sacrificing your friend
to look good in front of Mako?
--That's not true.
--Oh, yeah?
Then do you really think
Takumi can win this race?
Do you? What's your answer?!
I, uh...
He has no chance.
He only knows Akina Pass, and is racing
at difficult Usui Pass for the first time.
I know his technique is incredible,
but that's not the answer to everything, is it?
He's never even driven the pass!
Even Takumi can't handle a new
course without any practice.
You must've realized that much.
I, uh...
Men go crazy for women they like.
To make this summer memorable,
I would like to race
Akina's Eight-Six at Usui Pass.
But don't sell out your friend for a woman!
Have you forgotten that Takumi and
his Eight-Six saved your ass once?
The Eight-Six of Mount Akina is our pride.
Let's stop this nonsense...
...or our friendship is over!
You're right, Kenji.
I'm sorry.
I should've come to you
with this a long time ago,
but I kept it to myself.
I still don't get why you're quitting racing.
It was so much fun when we
started racing two years ago.
We've always wanted to
become the fastest here.
It's still fun, though, isn't it?
I can't explain it...
...but I'm just not as intense as before.
I don't know why.
I just feel like it's time to move on.
I've done enough...
I don't know.
I still don't get it.
I want to have a boyfriend
and a normal relationship, like you do.
You can race and still have a boyfriend.
You can't.
I don't think you can understand how I feel.
You have someone you like, don't you?
I must confess that I've
had someone in mind...
I was just messing with you. I didn't know.
You couldn't have known.
He's not from here,
and I was just admiring him from afar.
Oh, my!
You must be the ultimate innocent, shy girl.
And you're 20.
I liked it that way.
I was satisfied with just admiring him.
You gotta learn to be more realistic than that.
Sorry.
But I do want to test what you and I
have built in the last two years...
...in this final race.
You want a final exam.
It sounds good to me.
He's a perfect opponent for you.
Yeah.
But I'll tell you this...
As long as we race at Usui Pass,
we have to win, no matter who we race.
I can't accept anything less.
I know.
We have to win, no matter what.
Even if it's against the Eight-Six.
Absolutely.
Well, there's no use racing if you're not into it.
Iketani and I will let them know.
You guys turn around here.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Takumi.
He means it, Takumi.
Kenji, I'm not going back.
Takumi...
I'm going because...
...I do want to race her.
I'm not going back.
Takumi...
But Takumi, you saw what Mako is capable of.
She's too much for you.
--Even you can't beat her.
--I know.
This isn't about winning or losing.
Don't say that!
The Eight-Six of Mount Akina is famous now!
Have some pride.
I'm not good at that sort of thing.
I happened to win some local races,
and the rumors exaggerated my abilities.
I would feel better if
rumors like that went away.
--Hey...
--Come on!
I'm going.
I just want to attack this
new pass as well as I can.
I should apologize for my harsh words earlier.
How could we say anything
to him after that, really?
Yeah.
Well, he's one of a kind for sure.
He's strange.
It's hard to tell if he's special...
...or simply "off."
The tires look good.
The pressure is ideal for this road.
I don't think it's necessary
to make any more adjustments.
If you say so, Sayuki.
I know you know,
but in this kind of race,
avoid wide-angle drifts.
And it's crucial to know when
to drift and when not to drift,
especially with Usui's continuous turns.
I'm with you, so believe in
your technique and go for it.
You won't lose to anyone!
I won't let you down.
Together, we're one winning team.
--Yeah.
--I'm fired up, Sayuki!
I've never felt this good before.
I'm excited to see how the race will turn out...
...and how good he really is.
So, how are you gonna win this race, Takumi?
Do you have a plan? Tell me!
Not really.
What?!
Can't you think of something?
I refuse to see you lose.
How about this?
Usui Pass is narrow
and has no straight lines...
...so jump the gun and get ahead!
What the...?
And you can block her the rest
of the way to the finish line!
I can't do that, 'cuz it's unfair.
But if she gets ahead of you, it's over.
That's true...
Man, we need to come up with a plan!
Her car has four wheels just like yours...
What?!
Are you really the driver of
the Eight-Six of Mount Akina?
Unbelievable.
How old are you, anyway?
I'm eighteen.
Eighteen? A high school kid?
You've gotta be kidding me...
Twenty isn't much older than eighteen.
And they're girls.
Now we really can't lose to him, right, Mako?
Let's talk about the race.
I don't think it's a good idea
to start side by side here,
because whoever has a better start
has a definite advantage.
I'd hate to argue over who
cheated and jumped the gun.
There goes my plan!
Then how?
How about a "cat and mouse" race?
It's a chase race.
If the mouse gets away, it's over.
If not, we keep switching
positions until someone wins.
It's a "sudden-death death match."
--Well?
--That's fine.
Since we're the locals here,
you get to choose whether you
want to be the cat or the mouse.
--Well...
--Hold on a sec!
Come here, Takumi.
With this rule, you should go in front first.
It won't end with one race,
but at least you get one practice.
It's better to lose in the second race.
He'll go in front first.
I'll win in the second race, then.
I don't mean to ignore your good advice,
but I don't think I like that.
What are you saying, Takumi?!
--I'll chase her first.
--What?!
--Wha...?!
--Think it over, Takumi!
This is my race, so let me decide.
But...!
--I'll chase.
--What?
You'll chase?
Is he trying to insult us, or is he an idiot?
It's okay. I'll smoke him!
Who is it? I'm busy.
Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hey, Bunta?
It's only you.
I'm busy right now.
I thought I should tell you
something about Takumi...
Should we start the race?
He went to Usui for a race? So?
"So?" Is that all you can say?
Aren't you worried?
Not really. He's my son, you know?
We'll go slowly, so just follow us.
After the first turn, we'll go full speed.
That's the beginning of the race.
Is that all you have to say?
That's all.
I'm busy, so don't call me about nonsense.
Hey, Bunta?!
I was an idiot, Takumi.
I realize that now.
I know...
...that the only reason you
agreed to try this losing race
was to save my ego.
I'm regretting it now.
You're Akina's racer.
You're our pride.
This is a huge mistake.
I don't wanna see you lose
because of my stupidity.
He won't lose, Iketani!
Reality isn't that simple, you know.
It's my fault.
Iketani...
I chose to be the cat for a reason.
What?
I'm not sure if I'll win,
but I'm not here to lose.
So, you do have a plan?
It's not really a plan...
More like an inspiration.
--What is it, Takumi?
--Tell us!
No matter how fast she is,
she can't fly.
Yeah?
She's driving on four wheels, too.
Four wheels...?
Then I should be able to turn these corners
as fast and as well as she can,
don't you think?
You're right!
Theoretically, it's true.
That's crazy talk!
We're going!
Let's go, Mako!
Let's finish him quickly!
Okay, Sayuki. I'll show you the best race ever!
Wow!
They're going full throttle already!
Takumi's first "away" race has finally started.
Takumi is at a serious
disadvantage in this race, though.
I'm not worried...
...because I know he'll win!
There was a time when I
wandered aimlessly, tired of love
I lost sight of myself and gave in to desire
But destiny is ever-changing
And charmed by innocent eyes
Bloom like a red rose,
I hold you ever so tightly
All I can say is that I believe
my feelings are true
Let's enjoy our happiness...
Into our shining future
We'll prove countless times...
Our passion will last for eternity!
Bloom like a red rose,
I embrace you ever so tightly
Even if I lose everything that I have,
I will never let you go
Bloom, my beautiful...
...and miraculous flower
Mako, we can't lose on our own turf!
--We're street racers!
--Yeah.
What will you do if Mako quits racing, Sayuki?
--I'll still be racing!
--Sayuki...
--So, you won't retire?
--I'll be racing after men!
--Huh?
--Where are all the good men?
Where are they...?
See ya, Sayuki.
Next on Initial D...
"Hot Winds & Furious Driving!"
Don't miss it!