"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Remember? Let's look for
the CD that we used to listen to
For we've been nervous with
each other for some time now
Speed awakens the melody
of our forgotten past
A conscience-driven targeted
hit that shakes the earth
Blazin' beat
Shower me with a strong love that hurts
Embrace the echo in the crying wind
Naked mind and desire
Wanting is not a crime
Leave your worries behind and trust me
Blazin' beat! Yo! Let's go wild
and throw away our morals
Break loose impulsively
It's the weekend, everybody gather around!
M.O.V.E., move, break ahead
of the pack and go crazy
Let's look for explosive thrills, it's the time!
"Act 13: Changing Seasons"
It's rare for a race to last this long.
It's a battle of endurance.
It's physically and mentally demanding
to maintain extreme intensity
while dealing with the
continuous lateral G-force.
Especially when the course is this tricky.
Others would've given up already.
Stamina will be a major factor.
All we know is...
...that whoever loses focus first will lose.
If Kazumi moves back to Saitama,
I may never see her again.
So what am I supposed to do?
I should at least tell her the truth...
Not that it'll change anything.
I should tell her that I love her.
What?
Um, I, uh...
It's the third round!
Both of them are so intense.
They're getting me fired up.
The Levin looks different from the first round.
He's good.
What is this?!
His style has changed.
He's so fast that I can't relax at all.
I was being cautious at first.
The theory for passes says not to go 100%
before determining the road conditions.
But this round is a different story!
I don't want to lose now.
I'll chase him to the end!
My Eight-Six is finally listening to me.
I've never wanted to win a race this badly.
Is it because he drives an Eight-Six?
I just want to win with my new Eight-Six!
No!
That was close.
I need to keep my focus,
or I'll lose more than just this race.
I wonder if I'm getting tired.
I've started to wobble a little.
Could it be the tires? Not now!
The rear traction is slipping.
The rear tires are losing their grip.
This isn't good.
I can't adjust the tires.
I've come this far...
...but maybe this is it.
I may lose!
I know I'm losing speed.
So why isn't he pulling away from me?
Could it be...? It's the only explanation!
He's having the same problem.
His tires are losing their grip, too!
Takumi!
This is the fourth round.
It's become a crazy endurance race.
Your rear tires must be slipping, too.
The power increase puts
more stress on the tires.
Our powerful cars have been running
at the same pace all this time.
It's only logical that we'd
have the same tire problem.
He's good!
It's obvious from behind.
The worse the conditions get,
the better he seems to get.
But he's only human.
He's not invincible!
This is a test of endurance!
Actually, these slippery tires
make it easier for me to see
my car's ultimate capabilities.
It feels natural.
It's running the way I want it to.
I'm all fired up!
This is my new Eight-Six!
Basically, I step on the accelerator to swing.
It's the same as before.
But I can clearly see a major difference
when drifting at full speed.
Dad, I know how to control this car now!
Uh... what round is this?
I've started to space out a little.
I'm getting tired,
but I'm sure he is, too.
At this stage of the race,
it's mentally more exhausting to follow
than it is to lead.
A little difference in speed won't
be enough to take the lead.
You can only lose by falling behind.
So, you can't lose when you're leading.
The next corner is that mudslide.
He won't have enough space to sneak by.
I should be safe.
I'll keep this up for as long as it takes
until you lose focus and make an error.
What?!
There's less mud on the road!
Don't be reckless!
It's impossible to pass me here!
He's crazy!
I won.
Darn! I didn't notice that
the mud was pushed aside,
which created enough
space for him to get by me.
Regardless...
...he was able to gauge
that narrow space accurately.
He's way out of my league.
They've slowed down.
The race is over.
Will it be the Trueno or the Levin?
The Trueno!
Takumi won!
--He did it!
--He pulled it off!
--All right!
They're finally back!
Big brother!
Takumi.
Thanks for waiting.
I got back safely, but I'm exhausted.
Get in, Kazumi. We're leaving.
Kazumi!
Well, goodbye, Itsuki.
I couldn't say goodbye...
...because I didn't want it to be goodbye.
--Takumi?
--Yeah?
How did the race go?
Well.
I managed to win.
I see. You're amazing, really.
It was a complete loss for me.
Even though you brought me there
so that I could be with Kazumi...
...I just couldn't tell her how I felt.
I've been thinking about her
constantly since yesterday.
Falling in love with her
made me realize something.
Loving someone is really a painful thing.
Loving someone is serious business.
When it doesn't work out,
your chest aches so much.
Laugh at me if you want.
Why would I laugh?
You know the feeling?
Yeah.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
--You're back late.
--Yeah.
You only have an hour until your deliveries.
I know.
Wake me up when it's time.
Sure.
I never knew that our car was that good.
Hey, Dad?
Maybe you can teach me
about engines and stuff
when you have time.
What happened all of a sudden?
I realized which essential
element I was lacking.
Takumi, Itsuki is acting weird.
You'll find out eventually
anyway, so I'll tell you.
I see. That's really unfortunate.
I thought they'd make it.
He's back to being the "Lonely Driver."
Itsuki?
What?!
Kazumi!
Didn't you go back to Saitama?
It was all so sudden.
I came back to get my stuff.
Oh, yeah?
But that's not all I left here.
We left in a hurry,
so I couldn't say goodbye to you properly.
Kazumi?
Are you free now? Just for an hour?
I have some time.
He had to leave early...
...for personal reasons.
Again?
Bittersweet youth...
She's the most important
thing to him right now.
That reminds me.
Takumi, I heard that your girlfriend
--started a part-time job.
--What?
How are things with you two?
Mogi got a job...?
Autumn is almost over.
I'll never forget this autumn in Akina.
I'll think of it every time
the leaves change colors.
I'll never forget the people I met in Gunma...
...especially this outspoken
but compassionate boy
who encouraged me to live.
He's a year younger than I am,
and is like the little brother I never had.
I won't forget him.
Thank you very much!
Welcome! For here or to go?
Whenever I turned around
"Shibusawa Station"
There was always that
unchanging smile of yours
It was there on days when
I was too tired to go on
And even on days with a little happiness in them
My hands aren't enough
To hold on to all the love you gave me
Goodbye, Kazumi.
I couldn't tell you this...
The warm wind
...but I loved you.
Comes back quietly and tenderly
It blows through with a radiant light
Just like it did that day
Big brother... have you formed
the All Gunma Team yet?
The grave sin of betrayal
I've picked the candidates.
The strength of believing in each other
Now it's up to them to join the team.
The countless days and nights
I can't keep losing like this!
Let's tuck them away in our hearts
I'll get my revenge on the Emperors...
...and Akina's Eight-Six!
On the road of meetings and partings
We keep on walking while our hearts get hurt
You are still waving to me from the radiant light
Just like you did that day
You are my everlasting memory