"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
This is just between us...
But all you guys are sorta in trouble.
That guy that lost the race
just now has sort of flipped out.
He's called up a bunch of his friends,
really bad characters.
So, in other words...
You're telling me to lose on purpose?
Nah, I didn't say that.
All I said was not to race too hard.
I'm sayin' this to be kind.
Think about it.
They're close now. They're just up ahead.
The approach to this point is one
of this course's difficult areas, huh?
You've gotta maintain speed,
coming downhill at a slow turn
and then making a sudden left.
There's no way to make any
kind of direct braking path.
How the "best downhiller in Gunma"
tackles it will be something to watch for.
What's more, he's in an Eight-Six with no ABS.
This is bad! The Eight-Six's
braking point is too late!
I've never seen anyone go chargin'
in full-throttle that far before!
Awesome! He caught right up to him!
Shit!
"Act 17: The Saitama Area's Final Battle"
Okay. Understood.
It seems Fujiwara's braking technique
is surprising the onlookers.
Well, of course.
He's practiced over and over, learning to
choose the last possible braking point.
It's a piece of cake for him now.
The Eight-Six has been tuned not
for flat terrain but for the downhill,
wherein braking is executed with the
front section pointing slightly downward.
Utilizing the Eight-Six's light weight,
and dependent upon the skills of the driver,
its braking performance can
surpass even that of ABS.
In extended out-of-corner acceleration,
the Evo-Six will probably
pull ahead of the Eight-Six...
...but through cornering work
utilizing its light weight,
the Eight-Six should be able to close that gap.
Quit keepin' up with me!
You're startin' to piss me off.
If this is how you wanna play it,
whatever happens is on your head!
Whatever. I should be able to lose him
once I enter the final, high-speed section.
I'm in a completely different speed range...
from some stupid Eight-Six!
Keisuke.
Actually, before the race started, Fujiwara
said something that's been bothering me...
He really said that?
Yes. It's probably just a scare tactic,
but it got me a little concerned,
so I thought I'd tell you, Keisuke.
I wouldn't put it past those guys to do that.
Give me a break! Just how
rotten are these guys?!
We should hurry and call our guys, too!
All it would take would be
a word from you, Keisuke!
No, Kenta.
Huh?
It could be just a bluff.
Don't get all worked up over it.
But Keisuke! If it's for real, there'll be
nothing we can do about it! They...
They already outnumber us.
I know.
I know that, which is why I'm telling
you not to get worked up about it.
I can keep up... A little poorly,
but I don't feel like I'll lose.
So the real problem is the driver.
That one time, the person
who pulled out in front of me...
...was my father.
This guy's braking doesn't
hold a candle to Pops'.
Oh! Now I get it. That's the weak point!
Still, being told something like that has
probably gotten Fujiwara a little rattled.
In terms of diversionary tactics, I think
it's quite effective for a race like this.
I think so, too.
I told him to forget everything that doesn't
matter and concentrate on the race, but...
It's not as easy as that, is it?
It's a whole different kind of
pinch for Fujiwara this time.
No.
Fujiwara is not that fragile.
Ryosuke...
He's right. Anyone who's raced
Fujiwara even once would understand.
He normally seems harmless,
but once he starts racing...
...his concentration shoots to pro-racing levels.
His weak point is...
...braking!
Shit! For some weak-ass Eight-Six
to be able to run this fast...!
I don't know what kind of trick he's
pulled, but this is pissing me off!
It'll be trouble if he comes
chargin' in half-assed.
I've gotta safely make it
outta this low-speed section!
His line has changed...
He's checking my cornering speed
and keeping his guard up!
Theoretically speaking...
If the Evo-Six were to begin
maneuvering defensively,
it would enter corners tighter.
Should its driver fail to consider offensive
tactics coming from the outside...
...that is where Fujiwara would strike.
There's wide open space on the outside!
All right!
They're here? Okay, understood.
It's still the middle of the race,
so have them wait down
there till it's over. Yeah.
Those are some pretty scary guys,
so make sure you don't step out of line.
It looks like they're here.
You don't say...
The driver of that Evo-Six is by no means slow.
His defining characteristic is, put simply,
that his racing makes clever use
of high-tech electronic devices.
As for braking, he makes masterful
use of the benefits afforded by ABS.
With no special skill,
he can employ high-level braking
that makes full use of the tires' grip.
However, his senses may or may not be such
that he can adapt to changes in his situation.
If he can, countering the braking point
at which he approaches
each corner will be difficult.
Whether Fujiwara can do that will
determine the outcome of this race.
Bad move!
This bastard just won't quit!
Just a little farther.
After we pass just one more...
...it's the high-speed area where
I can open it up full-throttle!
What the...?! My front tires have lost their grip!
Yes!
Dammit! It's oil! I went too far into the in-line!
I passed right over some leftover oil!
We're not at the goal yet! I...
I just have to get back in front of him!
With this thing's racing capabilities,
I can turn the tables in the power section!
Just you watch!
I've got a two-liter turbo engine,
the fastest on the street racing scene!
There's no way it'll lose to
some wimpy 1.6-liter engine!
The last part of the course is a
mid-speed section with wide roads.
It is here that the speed
range is raised a notch.
Then the Evo-Six is sure to--
You never learn, Kenta.
Huh? But...
The more their speed increases, the harder
it becomes to accurately gauge braking...
...and the risk factor increases exponentially.
Isn't that right, big brother?
On the downhill, the importance of technique
over power increases in high-speed areas.
Dammit! It's no good!
That asshole's takin' the
corner without braking!
I... I don't believe it. That racing's incredible...
Okay. Understood.
Apparently, five or six suspicious-looking cars
are headed this way, coming up toward us.
What do we do, Ryosuke?
The situation would seem to
preclude our scheduled timed race...
Let's get things ready so we can
pull out at a moment's notice.
The safety of all our team
members is top priority.
Fumihiro, if worse comes to worst,
Keisuke and I will remain behind to buy time.
You look for an opportunity
to take the others and flee.
But I... Ryosuke...
I thought there was a risk of this occurring
during one of our expeditionary races.
We have prepared for the worst.
It's just like he said, Fumihiro.
I'm used to this sort of thing. Don't worry.
I'll find a way to get through this.
All right. In a time like this,
you're our only hope, Keisuke.
Keisuke! I'll stay with you!
You go along with the others.
But...
Don't let Ryosuke get hurt.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah. Just leave it to me.
Ryosuke, I'll...
Don't you worry, Fujiwara.
There they are.
Everyone! Get into Vans #1 and #2!
We're gonna watch us a fun little show.
We'll get to see that uppity bastard
in the FD cryin' like a girl.
Yeah.
With a chance like this, we should
join in too, and blow off a little steam.
After all, we didn't make
a single yen off of this.
Shit! All the effort we put into this,
and it amounted to nothing.
Let's do it!
After all, our guy's an ex-motorcycle
gang leader, a real son of a bitch!
Those other guys are gonna get pounded!
This guy sure looks like a badass...
Supposedly, he's the former leader of some
famous huge gang in northern Kanto!
Don't move from there, brother.
It's you, huh?
It was so dark I couldn't tell
it was you at all, Keisuke.
It's been too long, sir.
These guys are friends of yours?
You're not keeping very
good company, are you?
Uh, well, I wouldn't go so far
as to call them "friends."
They just asked me for a favor...
Bastards! They've done something
rude to you, haven't they?
I guess. But it's over with,
so no need to worry about it now.
More to the point, your cars
are in the way. Move them.
I'm very sorry, I'll do it right now.
Did you hear him or what?!
Yessir!
What gives, Keisuke? You know him?
Uh, well, I guess he's an old acquaintance
from when I was young and careless...
My little brother back when
I was still a troublemaker.
"Little brother"?
Well, in any case, that was a big help, Keisuke.
For a while there, I wondered
what would happen to us...
But now we can go home
without a scratch on us or our cars.
You certainly are incredible, Keisuke.
You've really made me look bad.
Do you not even know who
Keisuke Takahashi is, bitch?!
On top of that, Project D is so damn cool,
everybody in the Gunma
area knows about 'em.
Shitbird, did you forget that I'm from Gunma?!
"Gunma"
I-I-I didn't know! Please forgive me!
We didn't know anythin' at all!
We're not even involved so,
uh, please forgive us.
You're friggin' dreamin', cupcake!
In a bit, I'm gonna teach all you guys a lesson.
Just wait, dammit!!
As Keisuke's FD is incapable
of functioning normally,
I'd like to cancel the timed race.
Is that all right?
Yes, it's just fine!
All right, we're moving out!
Everyone, let's go!
Yes! We've completely
dominated the Saitama area!
Somehow, this latest race gave me a hint.
The way to beat it... is this!
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie