"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Tobidase wicked show, kuuki biribiri saku noise
Shibaite norikonase, abarenbou no party
Zettai hikanai kihaku, the dogfight
Buttoi red zone no himei ni shibiretai
Hakanai senkou, like a ryuusei
Isshun no kagayaki demo kamawanai
Kaimamita kichou na fuukei itsuka kataritai
Sou, ima wa honnou no mama dogfight
Shibiretai yume nara koko ni aru
Kagerou yaburu kaze, backfire
Kinou nado sutetekina,
ima kara rocket dance (Dogfight!)
Sakebenai negai ga itamu nara sugu ni oide
You're big time gambler
Orokasa wa utsukushii kyokusen
Crazy game
(Break it! Break it! Strike it! Shake it!)
Baby, this is your ecstasy
Ha ha! Souon mo everywhere
Yokonaguri, 5G hodo no heavyweight
Giri de soukou, miri no koubou
Za-za-zan!
Rakushou de funde ikeru ze, madamada
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Go!
--The Eight-Six has the lead!
--Awesome!
Sure enough, in a simultaneous dash,
an FR probably has the advantage over an FF.
That'd be because of the difference
in their drive systems, huh?
I assume this is according to plan,
what's just happened.
Indeed.
That Eight-Six has some
rather impressive acceleration,
but I'm suspicious as to whether
Tomoyuki stepped all the way on the gas.
From here to the first corner
it's a battle of just a few seconds,
but it could greatly affect
the course of the entire race.
"Act 6: Blind Attack"
Really, is that true?
Okay. Understood.
You ain't gonna believe
what's happened, Kyoichi.
Those Project D guys used the Eight-Six!
I mean, this course has got
an uphill and a downhill,
so I thought for sure they'd use the FD.
Why, Ryosuke? Why did you ignore my
warning and insist on using the Eight-Six?
This race isn't going to be
some walk in the park!
Going on the offensive from the beginning
certainly led to an advantageous start...
...but it is not as simple as that.
The area from this starting point to the
first corner is one of all-out acceleration,
and it divulged plenty of
information to our opponent.
Accelerating from zero clearly
reveals a car's potential.
If one were to remain slightly
behind and observe closely,
the Eight-Six's racing capabilities
would be plain to see...
Not absolute engine power, but
everything from gear configuration
to output characteristics
relating to RPM acceleration.
Having once shown all our cards,
the chances of a tactical
victory over a pro racer are nil.
If tactics are no good, why bother racing?
What about driving techniques?
Even Fujiwara would be unable to defeat
a pro racer using such techniques.
Furthermore, his car's capabilities
would provide no advantage.
As far as I can tell, there are no
shortcomings with our opponent's EK-9.
Power-wise, it is either on par with
or above Fujiwara's Eight-Six.
What?! Then...
From the start, you thought this was a
race we couldn't possibly win? Ryosuke!
Don't leap to conclusions, Fumihiro.
That's not what I am saying.
There is just one thing...
...in which Fujiwara is second to none,
even when compared to a pro driver.
It is that upon which I am betting, and it
is why I chose Fujiwara and not Keisuke.
There is no such thing as a race
that Project D simply cannot win.
We fight with the pride of street specialists!
The strategy for this course can be
roughly divided into four sections.
Right after the start is a narrow
stretch of area with no center line.
If you're going to bet the race on anything,
it will be the next section after that.
With the right amount of road width,
someone like Tomo could
lay down a trap anywhere.
From the second section onward,
the course widens up and
there's more room to navigate.
Doing one complete circuit
is what will win the race,
but when they return to this starting point,
the thing to watch for is
the distance between them.
This road is narrow and has poor visibility,
but from here it will suddenly change.
Coming up is the new second section, where
construction to widen the road has finished.
It looks good, but the road surface is terrible.
Joint lines in the asphalt are
bumpy and will toss you around.
It looks like it's got a lot of power,
but that Eight-Six has old suspension.
I wonder how far it will even be able to go.
So it can stay in complete control even
when tossed around by bumpy roads, eh?
Well, not too bad. The Eight-Six
has some pretty solid suspension,
but it's not enough to hide
that it's having a hard time.
I don't get it.
Just what is the point of this race?
The answer I'm looking for
couldn't be in a place like this!
Keisuke.
Okay, dammit. Fine!
It seems they've entered the second section.
Ah. Understood.
Keisuke. Where have you been
and what have you been doing?
I was in my FD pouting. But I started
feeling like an idiot, so I came out.
You want to ask my reasoning. Don't you?
We've passed the high-point corner.
Coming up is the tight, downhill third section.
I wonder how far this
Eight-Six will tag along...
It won't be able to keep up for long.
I have experience with this, as a pro!
This is ridiculous. Any more
time than this is just a waste.
Even before I started, I knew the answer
I was looking for wouldn't be here.
I should just step up and end this thing now.
If I get out in front of that Eight-Six...
...it's all over!
I can't move forward unless I
can think things out for myself.
In my FD with the engine off,
I cooled down a bit and worked
through some reasons of my own.
And before long, I had it.
When I heard we were going up against
a pro racer, I got too worked up over it.
I thought about it too much, to where
even I thought it was getting dangerous...
...and honestly, I was
scared I'd get into a wreck.
If I'd raced in that state, the outcome
would not have been good.
You thought that too, right?
It was a consideration, yes. But the
real factor is somewhat different.
Frankly, speed all boils down to experience.
Pro racers always keep in mind
to try to trim their lap time,
so they have a time awareness
that no hillside racer could possibly reach,
no matter how much he practices.
The number of training runs and the
quality of racing is completely different.
As part of D's activities,
and in order to perfect my
theories on street racing,
I am attempting two completely different
approaches in pursuit of the same goal.
It is for this reason that D has two drivers.
If there's such a thing as a talent for driving,
it means bein' able to improve a little
faster than a guy who hasn't got it.
There's no such thing as an instinctive
"gift" that could outdo accumulated effort.
At least, I've never seen
somethin' like that, not once.
One driver will employ an orthodox style,
applying motor sports techniques
cultivated on the circuit
toward street racing...
And the other driver...
...will be a pure street specialist,
a product of the streets!
His will be an irregular style,
the result of high-speed racing on
only one stage: the mountain pass.
Do you understand, Keisuke?
Our opponent this time
is of the orthodox style.
An exceptional one at that.
This does not mean that
you are inferior to Fujiwara.
Do you understand Daiki, Sakai?
Winning or losing boils down to experience.
And if that's the reason you guys lost,
it's the same reason that
Tomo definitely won't!
It's about the nature of the racing.
Therein lies the only chance
of beating a pro racer.
I get it. You thought about all that
when making your choice, huh?
But if you'd just told us that in the beginning,
we could've gotten things done
without getting all confused.
I apologize for that.
But the ones who are truly confused...
...are our opponents.
They're headin' into the four
consecutive winding hairpins!
He passed me here?!
What the heck?! He passed
Akina's Eight-Six like it was nothin'!
The disappearing line, eh?
Disappearing line?
The line at which you disappear from the
field of vision of the car in front of you.
It looks like you're just following the in-line,
but actually it's a high-level overtaking
technique often used in circuit races.
You enter the blind spot in your
opponent's rearview mirror
and, while trimming to as
short a distance as possible,
bleed over into your opponent's line.
If it's timed just right, even another pro
racer would have no way to prevent it.
He pulled it off perfectly, like it was nothing.
In the four consecutive hairpins,
the road widens out
and there are any number of lines
you could take to make your approach.
That makes it close to the same
conditions as the circuit...
Meaning that as a racing driver,
he'll be right in his element.
Dammit! He's so fast!
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
Bunta, you here?
Masashi?
About our discussion before, is there
a particular model year you'd like?
Not really. But I don't want some splashy
thing that's got wings on it or something.
Yeah, I figured.
Anyway, I've already asked a
dealer acquaintance of mine,
so you should go for a test
drive and make your choice.
Yeah.
"Sushi"
Still, it really doesn't suit you.
I mean, you in a four-wheel drive...
Just before this bridge, I'm going to set
a new speed record for this course!
Once we cross the bridge is the
fourth section, a tough uphill!
I'll speed ahead and it will be the end!
He did so-so for an amateur...
After we cross this bridge comes the uphill.
If my car doesn't have enough power,
I won't be able to keep up.
Come on, Eight-Six!
I'm counting on your engine!
What?!
He's staying right on my tail.
This is a bit unusual.
For an FD, which is fast on the straightaway,
matching the gear ratio to the point on this
course where you can achieve top speed
will work against you once you reach here.
The low-speed corners of the hillclimb
section won't match that gear ratio.
If your opponent drives a turbo,
he'll be able to adjust, but...
I never thought they'd use the Eight-Six.
It's a crime! Their leader's
a smart one, all right.
It wasn't apparent on the downhill,
but on the hillclimb it's all too clear.
That Eight-Six behind me has
a better gear configuration.
Corners that I'm taking in
second gear, he's taking in first.
But more importantly...
...ever since I overtook the Eight-Six,
his concentration has
definitely been on the rise.
He's done a good job keeping up with me.
I feel like I'm watching a younger me.
At this rate, he definitely won't
free up any space. What do I do?!
I should make it so he can't see me!
If I disappear from his field of vision,
the way he did to me earlier...
All I can do is try!
Now!
He's gone!
The Eight-Six has disappeared
from my mirrors!
That's not the sound of my car.
That's where he is?!
What?!
He got me.
He used the disappearing line
I just showed him, eh?
This is the first time a car I've passed has
then passed me, and on a mountain road.
I'm starting to get it.
What Mr. Toudou wanted to show me...
But I'm not going to pull any punches!
--They're here!
--The Eight-Six is in front?!
We're coming up to the fourth winding hairpin.
I'll show you. In box car racing,
there's this kind of bashing, too!
I'm not pushing him hard enough to spin him.
I just want to throw him
off balance for a moment.
Sorry, chump. This sort of thing happens
every day in the pro racing world!
Ryosuke, please tell me.
When you let Fujiwara sit in
the passenger seat of your FC,
what kind of advice did you give him?
I gave him no advice.
I simply showed him...
...the strategy for the course I
had made based on my own run.
He races now with an intuitive understanding
of how his racing differs from mine.
S-So then...
Fujiwara took the strategy you'd
made after you ran the course first
and that's what he's racing with?
We're almost to the goal.
If he gets away from me here,
there's no way I'll get a second chance.
That again?
I won't fall for the same trick twice!
The Eight-Six isn't coming!
What the heck?! The Eight-Six
is racin' with his headlights off!
Huh?! The Eight-Six's headlights are off?
There he is! He's keeping up!
He's not in my mirrors,
but he's definitely behind me!
This is crazy!
Who goes racing around a mountain road
in the pitch dark with his headlights off?!
I can't look at his tail lights...
Look only at the road lit up
by the car in front of me!
I just have to concentrate only
on burning the image into my mind
and superimposing the line
that Ryosuke showed me.
This is too much. To think I'd get shown
up like this... You're pretty incredible.
But in this last section, there's no
point where you can pull out ahead.
Victory is mine!
They say the Eight-Six's headlights are off!
Incredible. I didn't teach him that.
It's his own original move.
This is the thing about Fujiwara
upon which I was betting.
When he's cornered and the situation
becomes grim, he awakens... evolves!
The goal is just ahead. I've won for sure.
I won't give up! If there's any opening,
I'm definitely taking it!
Um...
Why did you yield the line?
Just before the last corner.
Oh, there.
There's no big reason.
There was something in the road.
I reflexively avoided it.
Well, this is how it goes
when luck's not on your side.
Plus, there was the slope of
the uphill toward the goal...
There was?
Ah. I guess you wouldn't have seen it, huh?
Um, I...
You won.
If there is a Lady Luck out there,
then you had what it takes today to move her.
Today, I lose.
Thank you very much. I understand
now what you were trying to tell me.
Tomo...
To keep your motivation as a pro high,
you need to have a starting
point you can go back to.
Next time I'm hurt and suffering,
I know now where to return to.
I feel refreshed right now.
Is that so?
Hey sanjou, new generation
Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou
Itsu made wasureta furi o shiteiru no?
(Chigiresou na heart no tension) Mune no uzuki
Sono hitomi no oku, osaekirenai mono
(Sou matowaritsuku kono image) yoru o niramu
Sou dare no kokoro ni te o
nobashite fureru subemo
shiranakatta futari, mou koko kara
(Hey sanjou new generation,
Hora, This will blast your love)
Blast my desire, break off the barrier
Nemutta yume o tatakiokoshite
(Kirisaku you na skill)
Blast my desire, stronger than fire
Jidai o furuwasete risky tune
Blast my desire
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
be what you wanna be)
Blast my desire
Blast my desire, whoa whoa whoa yeah
(Atarashii jidai tourai o ima teishou,
break what you wanna break)