"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Initial D
Raise up your hands high.
(Everybody now raise your hands)
Take hold, there's a brand new tomorrow.
(You don't stop)
It's a beautiful eternal dream
where you learn about yourself.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
If you think you're lucky just to be alive
go for the highest stake in the gamble.
Same mission creates similar lives.
But your passion for your dream will make a difference.
You can never use the escalator.
But you can build up your strength, yeah yeah.
You must eventually climb the stairs.
Customize them the way you like.
Intense days go by.
(But you know)
Just laugh it off, because it's a game worth competing.
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands forever.
(Everybody now raise your hands up)
Run, sleepless challenger.
(You don't stop)
It's a quest of the never ending dream
where you now search for the reason to live.
(Let's go)
Oh
Oh, raise up your hands now.
After graduating from high school, Fujiwara Takumi
joined the Project D team organized by Takahashi Ryosuke,
and won victories as a downhill specialist in
out of prefecture races in Tochigi, Saitama and Ibaraki,
along with the hill climber Takahashi Keisuke.
However, Takumi's race against his last opponent,
Joshima Toshiya of Purple Shadow, ended on a bitter note
with him winning in the overall results, but losing the battle.
I really do feel awkward with just one hand.
I won't be able to respond fast
enough if something happens.
One hand steering only works
when you're absolutely confident in your driving
while anticipating the future with 100% accuracy,
even when pushing yourself to the limit.
It's exactly like Ryosuke said.
Without having 100% confidence
in controlling everything
you can't fight a battle like this.
Tofu Shop
I'm done with the delivery.
Good job.
I'm taking a nap
before going to work.
Where are you going next?
There's no race this week because
the Eight-Six has to be repaired.
The last battle will be
in Ibaraki next weekend.
After that, we'll head to Kanagawa.
Going that far is gonna be a pain.
You're finally going to face real difficulties.
Act 1  [ Fateful Encounter ]
Takumi.
Yo, Takumi.
What's up?
Hi, Iketani, and you too, Kenji.
I feel sorry for you,
since it's still hot at night.
Hey, don't treat me like Kenji.
I'm working, but he's just goofing off.
What's with you?
Can't you put it a little differently, Iketani?
Right.
Kenji has no date to spend time with.
Shut up!
Street racers don't need girls!
How many times have I said that?
Hey, when will your Eight-Six be ready?
You're doing more mods again, aren't you?
This time, the main issue is the suspension, and the tire size is being changed, too.
And strengthening the chassis
plus the reduction of weight.
You're leaving the looks completely unchanged, but modding what's inside, huh?
I wonder what kind
of car it's going to be?
It's awesome?
Totally awesome?
After all, you are Project D's undefeated downhill ace, with an uninterrupted series of victories.
Oh, that's right, Takumi.
Do you go on trips with Takahashi Keisuke,
other than Project D's expeditionary races?
Huh?
Um, no, I don't.
What made you ask that, Kenji?
A friend of my friend apparently raved about meeting Project D's double aces last weekend, on a mountain pass in Saitama.
What?
I never went somewhere like that.
I thought so.
It didn't sound right.
Then what the heck's going on?
Mistaken for someone else?
Higashi-Chichibu
Heel and toe!
How was that, Takumi?
Someday, I'll emerge as
a downhiller with my Levin.
That's my dream.
Reality is harsh.
What?
What do you mean?
I'm not talking about you.
You know I drive around town for
deliveries during the daytime, right?
When I see middle and high school kids
having fun, that thought pops into my head.
Uh huh.
I've come to think that
summer break is incredible.
You can play around every day.
Now that I've got a job,
I feel such a stark difference.
I see.
We had summer break last year.
One year makes a huge difference, doesn't it?
It makes me sad to think that we'll never have
such a summer break again for the rest of our lives.
Hey, do you miss...
Natsuki?
The reason I said
I have to stay here...
is because I want to join
a new team and learn a lot.
I think that will bring
me closer to my dream.
You wanted to go to Tokyo, didn't you?
Then you have to go, no matter what.
If you don't do what you want because
you let a temporary emotion take control
you'll eventually come
to regret it in the future.
Well, I guess I did for
a while, but I'm over it.
I don't feel lonely.
She went to Tokyo to pursue her dream.
Is that so?
I'm honestly rooting for her
as she chases her dream.
Do you come to this mountain pass often?
This is the second time, I guess.
It's boring to only drive on Akina.
What?!
Seriously?!
I wonder what's going on.
They're getting excited for some reason.
I heard Project D's
double aces are coming.
Really?
Awesome!
Let's go see
Yeah
How could that be possible?
No idea.
A panda Trueno and a yellow FD?
W-what the?
T-shirts with logos
And dressed the same way?
I've never seen anything like that.
Excuse me, but aren't you
Takahashi and Fujiwara of Project D?
Hold on.
I'm sorry, but I can't answer
yes or no to that question.
You see, we didn't come
here for an official visit.
In other words, this is supposed to be a secret, we don't want to create a buzz.
Right, Keisuke?
He's acting so casual with Keisuke.
Besides, that Keisuke is too short.
Hey, is it okay for you to let
them do whatever they want?
It's obvious they're imposters.
Okay or not, I don't want to get involved.
They're too embarrassing to watch.
Excuse me.
Do you mind if I take a picture with you?
Yay
They're popular with girls.
Screw it.
I can't stand this.
Now I'm gonna be in trouble.
Hey imposter!
Who the hell are you?
Hey, that's what I want to ask you.
What?
What do you mean?
I know you're not with Project D.
What makes you say that
we're not with Project D?
I have proof, which is...
this guy next to me.
He's the real Fujiwara Takumi.
Say what?
It sounds so fake.
We have proof.
Hey, Takumi, show them your license.
Um...
I left it in the car.
What the?!
You moron!
How come you're not carrying
such an important thing?!
Oh, I get it.
You guys are imposters.
Looks like you've got
a Levin, which is so bogus.
Say what?!
Bogus?
Fujiwara Takumi drives a panda Trueno
like that.
He's right, you're a fake!
You're an imposter!
What was that?
That's rude
I knew it.
I had a bad feeling that
something like this would happen.
The real Trueno is being repaired
The suspension was damaged when the car hit
a curb during the last downhill battle in Ibaraki.
Well? Surprised?
Only the real person knows that.
Hey, keep your mouth
shut if you don't know.
With all due respect, I, Fujiwara Takumi,
am famous for my precise vehicle control.
I'd never hit a curb and
damage my car during a battle.
What the hell is with him?
I'll forget what I saw today.
so don't ever pretend to be us again.
Let's go, Keisuke.
Don't mess around with us.
Hey, wait
What?
You met the imposters?!
Yes.
It's just as I thought,
there are imposters out there.
Excuse me.
I want to see Mr. Fujiwara Takumi.
I've been told that I could contact
Mr. Fujiwara of Project D if I came here.
Are you Mr. Fujiwara of Project D?
Yes, I am.
Personally, I don't have a grudge
against you, but that was for Tomoko.
You should know what I'm talking about.
Who is this Tomoko girl?
I have no idea.
Acting like you know nothing?
You're such a coward.
Now, now.
Just calm down.
I don't know what's going on,
but we should talk this out.
You guys are his friends, right?
I can't trust you, and I have no
intention of talking to you either.
Hey, don't be so stubborn.
In any case, he tricked my best
friend and now she's miserable.
I admit that my friend was
careless for pursuing you
but she's a good, honest person.
I can't stand a guy who'd take advantage of his fame to play around with a girl's heart.
That's dishonest and horrible.
That's all I wanted to say.
Good bye.
Oh, come on.
Are you sure this is the
guy who hit on your friend?
How can I be?
This is ridiculous, right, Iketani?
I know.
It must be that imposter.
Imposter?
Right.
There's is an imposter,
who's chubby and ugly.
It sounds so fake.
I can't believe a story like that.
Regardless, double check
and see if it's really him.
You can find out whether he's the same person or not by just snapping a picture and mailing it to your friend.
If you insist.
She's not responding.
I wonder if she's out of the area.
I'll send her a mail, though.
What a bummer.
I have to go now.
I've got to catch the train.
This's exactly what
I was worried about.
Those imposters have a lot
of nerve hitting on girls.
I don't know what's going on.
How can this be happening to me?
You'd better let Takahashi
Ryosuke know about this, Takumi.
Hello?
Oh, Fujiwara, what's up?
There are imposters?
Yeah, I heard a little about
that from another source.
Yes, and...
What? Really?
If it's that bad, we can't
leave them alone, can we?
I understand.
I'll get right on it.
Don't worry.
If we use our network
it shouldn't take too long to catch these rats.
Leave this to me.
Anyhow, that was a real
disaster for you, wasn't it?
Just forget about it.
It's just a misunderstanding.
I know that, but I feel down.
That girl was really
mad at me, wasn't she?
I've never met a girl before
who gave me a dirty look.
I was more shocked by
her glare than the slap.
Personally, I don't have any grudge
against you, but that was for Tomoko.
You should know what I'm talking about.
What's wrong with me?
I feel so antsy, but
I don't know what to do.
I don't get it.
Hello, Tomoko
This is Mika.
Did you see the picture?
Wha?
Totally different face!
No way?
Take a look at it carefully.
You know, he might
look different in a photo.
He doesn't?
Totally different person?!
Okay.
No, not okay.
Oh crap, I...
I gave a full swing slap
to the totally wrong guy.
Thank you for coming.
Another hot day.
You really think so?
It's totally possible.
I'm sure of it.
What are you talking about?
Well, it's about the girl from yesterday.
He says her and Takumi
would make a nice couple.
Think about it.
Their first meeting was so dramatic.
My instincts tell me that there
was a spark between them.
Now that you mention it, Takumi was still upset about the incident later.
You see, you see?
Of course he was.
Anyone would be.
She threw a slap all of a sudden, and left.
SLLAAAP, just like that.
That could be the end.
I don't think this is over.
It's just a hunch.
Hi, is this Ryosuke?
It's me.
The Eight-Six is ready, and
I'm going to take it to him.
Okay.
I was going to call
you about that matter.
I found the tag number of the imposter's car.
Huh? Already?
I don't have the time, so I'll
let Keisuke take care of this.
I told him not to get too rough, but can you
watch over him while following up on the matter?
Okay, you can count on me.
Also, it's a little early, but I'll recon the Kanagawa area with Kenta tomorrow.
I see.
The time has come.
Project D is getting closer
to entering its final stage.
I feel fulfilled.
The real challenge begins now.
I'll go over courses
more carefully than usual.
Okay.
We have one last race in Ibaraki.
That next hurdle isn't very high.
Once it's over, Kanagawa, also known as
the holy ground of street racing, will be next.
The battles will be unimaginably tough
but once we overcome the challenge, the true
meaning of "D" in Project D will become apparent.
Are you Mr. Fujiwara of Project D?
Who the hell are you?
I'm just a noob.
My name is Akiyama Wataru.
Hey, chill out.
I just wanna have a friendly talk.
I'm not picking a fight or anything.
See?
We're both Eight-Six drivers.
I, um... how do I put it?
As an Eight-Six driver, I'm very interested in the driving of the famous Fujiwara Takumi.
I wonder if you'd show me
your incredible driving technique.
No, I'm not supposed to do that.
Just one flashy drift, please.
My request is that you burst out sideways
from the top of that bridge over there, then.
I can't.
Ryosuke won't allow that.
The exit is a 90 degree bend, so if you can clear the
corner with only accelerator work, the crowd will go nuts.
On the line cornering, you see?
Don't screw around with me!
It's not as easy as you think.
There's no such god like driver
who can do it on the first try.
You're right.
Normally, it's impossible.
Here he comes.
But I guess the world is big, and there's one
moron who can pull it off without any practice.
Only one.
Alright, listen guys.
You'd better pay attention and watch what's gonna happen very carefully.
You don't get to see it this close very often.
This is real drifting.
Shit, a panda Trueno!
So fast.
He's much better than before.
What was that?
Could it be the real one?
It must be.
No other Eight-Six could do that.
I just remembered
some urgent business.
Let's go, Keisuke.
Okay.
What a coincidence.
Your name is Keisuke, huh?
Mine, too.
It's been a while, Wataru.
Yeah, it looks like you're doing alright.
He was the real!
Now, what should we do with them?
What gets me most is that
they used Project D's name.
The team's fame is like a medal of honor.
We managed to build it with the entire team's dedication.
We're sorry!
Please forgive us!
The second problem
is that my impostor is so incredibly ugly.
That deserves a few broken bones.
Sorry that I'm so ugly.
Dang.
Just kidding.
We won't resort to violence or anything,
but make sure you never do this again.
We can get your name and
address from the tag number.
Don't underestimate our information network.
I'll never do it again.
Being in Project D was my dream.
Oh, Fujiwara, you have something
you wanted to tell them, right?
Um...
you picked up a girl
named Tomoko, didn't you?
I got in trouble because of that.
Make sure you contact her, and
clear up this misunderstanding
since it's been a real pain for me.
I will!
I'm very sorry!
Make sure you do it.
Okay.
As you'd expect from a local, he's pretty good for what his car is capable of.
I wonder how far Project D will go.
We'll show them we're out of their league.
The Kanagawa area is known as
the holy ground of street racing.
Following the brake light of the front car.
A shimmering light up ahead in the dark street.
It's the silence like a silent film.
The light was all I could depend on.
I felt like I could catch it,
if I passed through this tree lined street.
Get up! I just can't understand.
I couldn't find what I'd been looking for.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
At this place.
Please turn over the flyleaf.
I lost my way.
Fogged up windows, and
messed up navigation.
As the stoplight turns red
a light in the side mirror blinds my eyes.
I gradually close the window
to stop the cold wind from blowing in.
Get up! I just can't understand.
We must choose one of the paths that lie ahead.
Yeah, it starts at this moment.
Because you're with me.
Please turn over the flyleaf.