"This story is fiction.
All names of characters, places and
organizations in the story are fictional.
Follow the traffic rules and drive safely."
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Now listen y'all, what you
waitin' for is the Noizy Tribe
We're back!
I want to shake myself free,
release the safety on my heart
Grab hold of your wavering
emotions, yes, kiss me
Yeah, always pressure,
like a train that's been jolted, creaking
I'm telling you, just watch me
from that sluggish crowd
'Cause someday, check it,
I'll be zoomin' fast as lightning
I'll dash out and get that
checkered flag, believe it
You can see a dream you
want to embrace, can't you?
I want to feel it in these arms, your soul
This moment I can feel, know the omen's arrival
I'm headin' out like this, I'm the Noizy Tribe
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can feel, you can feel,
you can feel in my love (C'mon!)
Come with me, come and cry with me
Got to be, got to be,
now you got to be free (Yeah!)
Noizy Tribe, you're my Noizy Tribe
You can break, you can break,
you can break 'cause you're Noizy Tribe
Here come the Noizy Tribe, we're back!
Welcome!
Hey, Takumi!
Is Itsuki here?
Itsuki?
Uh, well, he took the day off today.
He did?
The truth is... And this is
kind of hard to say, but...
He had sort of a rough time last night.
That really happened?!
Yeah. For Itsuki to take a day off,
it must've been quite a shock.
I never thought something like that would...
It happens a lot in love triangles.
Itsuki ended up losing out,
but he got pretty close there.
You have to be able to accept
the other person unconditionally.
Itsuki still has a ways to go in that department.
Hey, that sounds like you
when you were seeing Mako.
You're not exactly one to talk.
I told you not to mention that!
The pain of it is still too great...
Hey, you should give Itsuki
a call later and cheer him up.
I don't mind doing it, but I'm not
really good at that sort of thing.
The best thing is to just
leave him be for a while.
Listen, when Itsuki comes
back to work tomorrow,
this topic is completely off limits.
Understood?
--Yessir.
--Understood.
High octane. Fill 'er up.
Yes, sir. Thanks very much!
Hello. Thank you for the other day.
Hey. This is perfect timing.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
There is?
"Act 15: 4WD Complex"
I can't control how things turned out,
but I did a bad thing to Itsuki yesterday.
I'd like you to tell him for me.
He should hurry up and forget Kazumi's
ugly ass and find himself a good woman.
This is how the power
of a supercharger feels...
It's completely different from my Eight-Six.
This thing easily clocks
over 200 on a chassis dynamo,
but on a high-speed stage like Akina,
it's not so good on extended uphills.
It sure feels good on Chichibu's
narrow mountain roads, though.
So now that you've beaten
the Northwest Area coalition,
you're undefeated in Saitama, huh?
Still, there is just one
bothersome group left standing...
They're a little full of themselves.
In terms of skill, they probably
won't give you too hard a time.
Um...
I've wanted to ask you this...
Do you feel there's some kind of limit
with the Eight-Six's power
or racing capabilities?
Well, yeah. Of course there is.
That's why I added the turbo,
then the supercharger,
and am always fiddling with it.
That last race I did in the rain,
just how old the car's basic design is
hit me really hard, like a body blow.
Even you think the same thing, huh?
If so, that's unexpected. I think
you're in a class all your own.
Even in this day and age, you're winning
race after race, undefeated, in an Eight-Six!
No... Actually, I haven't
told anyone this yet, but...
Recently, somebody beat me.
I can't believe it.
Your Eight-Six, beaten on
your own home turf...
--What kind of car?
--An Impreza.
A four-wheel drive, huh?
It's been driving me crazy ever since.
It's like I've developed
some kind of 4WD complex.
You say that,
but you've beaten Lancer Evos before, right?
Don't you think it's best not to give 4WD
any kind of special consideration?
I'm trying to convince myself that, but...
In any case, the impact of it was far too strong.
That's why I was wondering
what you thought about it.
Well...
I'm running up against the
Eight-Six's limits too, and I don't like it.
To be honest, it's not just 4WDs.
It's FFs and FRs...
I'm scared of all the new cars.
All of them?
But I've used that complex as a
way to spring back even harder.
I'm refining my techniques,
and using my skills to cover
the difference in car functionality.
Look, let me tell you something.
This is actually the perfect chance to
get rid of this weird hang-up of yours.
I think your next opponent will be a 4WD.
Up till last year,
you could keep on winning, having nothing
to do with theory or even being in the know,
but once you've reached a certain level,
you're bound to run into its limitations.
For example, you don't
really know what 4WD is,
but you race your hardest
against it and end up winning.
In a way, it's a fool's victory. But I think
that's also your greatest strength.
What's being demanded of you now is that
you understand the characteristics of 4WD,
and that you negate your enemy's
strengths and attack his weaknesses.
In other words, you win smart.
I think this next race will
be a good chance for you.
Why not think in your own way,
and try drawing up an attack
plan for tackling a 4WD?
An attack plan for a 4WD...
Still, it'd be boring if you
started getting too clever.
It's letting that "fool's power" of yours
run wild that makes you you.
"Fujiwara Tofu Shop"
A 4WD's strengths and weaknesses, huh?
Sure enough, like Wataru said,
last year I just raced my hardest,
not knowing anything.
Now I know all too well what 4WD is about...
But it's not as simple as that.
This thing...
Does it even have anything that
could be called a weakness?
Well, what did you wanna talk about?
This is just between us, but...
If we win this next race,
it'll mean some money.
They're famous, right? Project D.
Think about it: What if our Lancer Evos win?
Being the shop that worked on those cars
has more advertising potential
than you can imagine.
If you really promoted it on the Internet,
I bet there'd be a huge increase in customers.
Okay, I follow. So how much
are we talking about?
If we win both races, 500,000 yen.
One race, 250,000.
If it's a draw, let's say 50,000 yen.
Are you serious?
M'yeah.
But winning ain't gonna be easy.
I'd never planned on running a "clean" race.
If a little underhandedness
can get results, so be it.
And that's your specialty, right?
Underhandedness.
Not that I wanna hear that from you, but yeah.
"Corporate Reforestation"
--They're here!
--Here we go!
Just like Wataru said... 4WDs.
They've got Lancer Evos, huh?
Ryosuke, come here a minute.
These guys say they want to split the
practice time and get some racing in, too.
We've never done it that way
before, so... What should we do?
I don't understand why we have to split
the time. Can't we practice together?
The thing is, we don't
like that idea. Sorry, but...
We don't wanna race with guys when
we don't even know how good they are.
Goin' out too far on a corner and... Hmph!
Smashin' headlong into an oncomin'
car ain't my idea of a good time.
You're saying you don't
trust our driving abilities?
--You stay out of this, Keisuke.
--But...
Hey! All I'm askin' is you be fair
and give us half the time till mornin', right?
What's with the friggin' attitude?!
If you got a problem,
then just forget the whole thing.
It ain't like there's some big reason
we gotta go out of our way to race ya.
Let's do it.
Ryosuke...
Big brother!
Let's get going.
What a joke.
What the hell's he talking about, "fair"?
This is their home course,
the one they always run.
The truth is, they just don't
want us to practice, right?
We've never met anyone like them before,
have we? They really piss me off.
Up till now, sure they've come up
with their own strategies,
but everyone we've raced
has fought a fair, clean fight.
Well, if they think cutting
our practice time in half
will give them an advantage,
they couldn't be more wrong.
Come tomorrow, we'll be giving them a
lesson in the true power of Project D!
Depending on how you look at it,
this could be a good experience
for Fujiwara as well, right?
He'll have to come up with
a strategy for the course
and get his car ready in half the time.
Which would be fine, if that's all this is.
I have a very bad feeling about this.
A bad feeling?
There's something we haven't seen yet.
Don't let your guard down, Fumihiro.
Burn both the road surface and
course topography into memory.
For crying out loud. Finally!
We get to go now, huh?
You guys keep standing around and
it'll be morning. Let's get a move on!
Ready and standing by. Shall we go, Keisuke?
Yeah.
We don't have much time,
so we'll have to make this count.
Understood. Here we go.
They better enjoy themselves while they can.
I think your best bet is to go for
the FD rather than the Eight-Six.
You're not tryin' to make things
easier just for yourself, are you?
No, I ain't. That guy in the FD
really pissed me off.
He looked at me and scowled, the bastard.
I wanna make that uppity little brat cry!
Fine, okay. We split the money
we get right down the middle.
Hello? It's me. You ready?
The target is...
...the FD.
Are we really gonna do this? If we
get busted, there's gonna be trouble.
Just do it.
Understood. I don't know how
good our aim will be, though.
If we're off, we could get both cars.
If it happens, it happens.
He says the target is the FD.
Having our practice time
cut in half really stings.
I don't have the luxury of thinking
about how to battle a 4WD...
Right now, I just have to
concentrate on the course!
These cracks in the road make the car bounce.
I have to remember all the cracked areas!
The road sur face is a bit rough, but there's
really nothing to this course at all.
Practice is a lot of fun.
Every time I pass him like that, I think
to myself, "I ain't losin' to him!"
The FD feels good today. At this rate,
it should be ready to race in no time.
I'll friggin' show you how it's done!
There's something flowing... Water?
There was nothing there earlier.
It's not water! Oh, no!
Hello, Fumihiro? It's Keisuke.
Yeah. What's up?
Are those guys still there?
By "those guys," you mean
the ones we're racing?
They left a little while ago. Is everything okay?
Hell no, it's not okay!
This is an emergency. Stop the Eight-Six.
Do not let him come back this way!
What's going on?
Somebody tossed a bunch of oil
all over the goddamn road!
What?!
So, are you all right?
I... I'm fine, but...
...the FD is screwed up.
This is terrible. There's no way anyone
could've avoided this. Not even Keisuke.
Who would do this?
It's obvious! Who the hell else was here?!
Whoever spilled this oil
probably fled via that side road.
According to the map, the road
is just wide enough to fit one car
and runs to the next city.
Then if we hurry and get over
there to the other end first,
we can seize the idiot by the neck
as he comes sauntering out!
I'm taking Van #1, brother.
I'll go with you, Keisuke!
Stop, Keisuke. It's a waste of time.
But brother! I can't just let this go!
How can I stand by when they've
wrecked my precious FD?!
We've gotta grab 'em and
knock the hell out of 'em!
I'm telling you to control yourself.
Don't go running off half-cocked!
--How is it?
--It's going to be a bit of work.
The suspension arm is damaged,
and after an impact like that,
we're going to have to
check the alignment, too.
There is 100% no way it can
be ready by tomorrow night.
There's nothing wrong
with the drive system, right?!
Do something to make it run!
Make some emergency repairs!
It doesn't even have to run in a straight line!
I'll make it work somehow!
Don't talk foolishness, Keisuke. If a
car's got trouble with its underbody,
pushing it to the limit amounts to suicide.
He's right. There's no telling
how the car will behave.
Its limits have been pushed way down...
Racing it in this state would be impossible.
Oh dear, oh dear. I thought
things were a bit too quiet.
You got into a wreck here?
That was a pretty damn rotten trick you pulled.
You all did this, didn't you?! That oil!
I don't follow. What're ya talkin' about?
Enough with the weird accusations already.
Well? You got any proof it was us that did it?
Don't screw with me!
I don't need proof, I frickin' know!
Now quit flappin' your mouth
and get outta that damn car!
Stop it, Keisuke.
Oooh, what a surprise!
This "Project D" team of yours
has a real attitude problem, huh?
Yeah, I get it. Not only do ya make
accusations without any proof,
you go around threatenin' the
people you're supposed to race!
Eeew, that's so uncool. I wouldn't
wanna race people like that!
I'm sorry. Please forgive us.
As you can see, our hillclimb
car has gotten into a wreck.
It's been badly damaged,
and it won't be fixed soon.
Yeah, well, that's a shame.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience, but could
we possibly postpone our race for a week?
A week, huh?
Yes. We would definitely be ready
within that amount of time.
I get it. I know just what you're sayin'.
But the answer is, "No."
We ain't made of free time, you know.
I got me a date next weekend.
Bastard!
In motorsport, a car that don't make it to
the startin' line is automatically the loser.
Whatever you all's circumstances,
it's got nothin' to do with us.
Right? Or am I wrong?
We start at 8:00 tonight, as agreed.
Use the Eight-Six or
somethin' instead, whatever.
Don't forget, if yer even
one minute late, you all lose.
Shit!
That guy's gettin' on my last goddamn nerve!
We have no time for you to take your
frustrations out on the guardrail.
Fujiwara and Matsumoto, you work
on setting up the Eight-Six.
--Okay.
--Understood.
However, run the course in halves until
we've finished cleaning up the oil.
All other personnel are on oil detail.
We don't have time. Hurry!
Hold on!
What am I supposed to do?
Brother, aren't we going to try fixing the FD?
If we did, it would be a wasted effort.
I have explored all options, and my
conclusion is that it is not possible.
There isn't enough time.
Your role in this race is no more.
You shall stay on the sidelines.
Brother, please let me race!
At this rate, we're just
playing right into their hands!
Do you still not understand, Keisuke?
The blame for the FD's crash lies with you.
Huh?
Yes. If it were me, I would not have crashed
my car over a simple trick like that.
This was caused by ego and lack of attention.
Calm yourself and think this over!
Let's get to work.
I... I can't accept this.
Ryosuke is being too harsh.
There's no way so much oil
could have been avoided.
No matter how you look at it,
it's just not possible!
No.
My brother could do it. He could've
cleared that oil spill like it was nothing.
It's just like he said, Kenta.
And the truth is, I know it.
I'm angry at myself for falling
right into a cheap trick like that.
That's exactly why,
no matter what, I have to race!
What should I do? Tell me, Kenta!
Keisuke!
Keisuke wants to race, but can't.
If I think about how he feels too much,
I start feeling mixed up myself. But...!
Right now, all I can do is give my total
concentration to the job I've been given.
And I will definitely win. I'll beat them!
A rose that's bloomed on the battlefield,
for the reason they don't know
A caterpillar that can only move forward
tramples it under foot again today
Yo, hates and pain, increasing only hatred
Hates and pain, with those
social conditions transmitted live
Hold me with stronger hands
Your voice in a restless night
(For the reason they don't know)
The world will someday be shedding blood
(All around the world)
Let me forget that kind of news,
I don't want to understand
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie
Check it, conflicting information is
already reported by the mass media
The outnumbered convey the
deep fears of the whole situation
Reason is flammable, an age
lacking the power of restraint, yeah
Devoting yourself body and spirit,
you keep receiving that baptism
Nobody reason, nobody sure where is the end
If rowing a boat that's untrustworthy
and on the verge of breaking...
Nobody reason, no one
confess that it was wrong
Ah, sing gently just a little more, even if it's a lie